{
  "126": {
    "question": "A visitor upgraded a flight to business class, but the department is only paying for coach fare. What are the next steps?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Have payee write a check for the difference between the business and coach class payable to the Trustees of Columbia. The check can be processed for deposit against the departments chartstring",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "393": {
    "question": "ANDRE SHOMORONY (0000208777), with vendor CNR0074450, no longer has access to Concur to resubmit their reimbursements. Please advise.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "CNR0074450\nPAC Termination Date\n06/16/2024\n\n0000208777 Outside party classification. He is not going to have access to concur. Department should process his reimbursement request\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1053": {
    "question": "All of these charges cancel each other out. Can they be removed from CONCUR?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Reopen or submit new ticket if any additional questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "420": {
    "question": "Although this person waited for more than 365 days to get payment approval, we are eager to pay the reimbursement. Because of the 365 days window, Concur is not receiving the report submission and is giving us an error. Is there a way to resolve this situation?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Expenses >365 days can be processed through ARC on a check request with SBO approval( you need to attach SBO approval e-mail as a backup supporting doeumcnet)\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "296": {
    "question": "Am I able to book travel through Concur if I am a 1199/SSA employee?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Support staff do not by default have access to book travel in Concur. However your school's DAF can \"opt them in\" to the Travel module, which would give them this access. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "670": {
    "question": "Am I allowed to purchase a seat for Air Canada for a guest who has a preferred seat? Would this expense be reimbursable?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Reimbursement for purchase of a preferred seat on a long flight is up to departments discretion",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1157": {
    "question": "Anup Das' expenses in Concur seem to be stuck at pending cost approval. Is there anything I can do to help expedite this process? Thanks!",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Any questions please reopen or submit new ticket. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "480": {
    "question": "Are hotel conference rates offered through Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "We have not heard back from you regarding any additional questions you may have regarding this Service Now Incident. The Finance Service Center has marked it as resolved. If you do not feel it was resolved, please respond to this incident within 3 days to reopen. Thank you.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "300": {
    "question": "Are the purchases of supplies reimbursable?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Emergency supply purchases of up to $500 are reimbursable. Any purchase greater than $500 requires SBO approval and if it is >$2500 , it requires Central Purchasing approval",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "634": {
    "question": "Are there any exceptions for the report regarding nn45?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Nydia will enter a comment explaining the presence of the spouse. Amount entered is the amount to be reimbursed (the lower comparison amount).",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "202": {
    "question": "Are visa fees reimbursable?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Expenses for visa fees can be reimbursed if the department approves. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "649": {
    "question": "As Ben Zweig's supervisor, I need to approve his expense report, but I can't find it when I log into Concur. Can you please add me as an approver since I completed the training?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Job aid attached\n\nYour departments DAF has to opt you in for concur supervisor approval role and you will be assigned the required training. Currently you have not taken the training\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "375": {
    "question": "As a TA, I will be arranging travel for students starting next week and will be booking through WTI. If I book these trips using BTA, who will be reconciling in Concur, the TA or the students?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The best business practice would be for the Travel Arranger complete the reconciliation via Concur.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "612": {
    "question": "As a new Registered Nurse at Medical Services-Columbia Health, Mina Wolloh (uni mw3873) is facing an error in her profile while trying to submit a relocation reimbursement. Could you help me resolve this issue?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "New employees will get access to concur once employment document is processed and active PAC profile established",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "351": {
    "question": "As a new postdoctoral fellow, I started my appointment on September 1 and was advised by my program administrator to log into Concur to book my travel for the fall semester. However, I can't access the system. After entering my Columbia credentials and confirming through Duo, I get an error page stating \"Sorry, something went wrong\" with code \"3e299bfe7e83791396b902f21345bdec\". A few weeks ago, CUIT said to wait until my profile is established in PAC, but my administrator believes it has been set up, and I'm still experiencing this error.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Should be able to login to Concur. If you experience any issues with login please reopen this incident.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "641": {
    "question": "As an employee, I understand that I have 45 days after my PAC termination date to access Concur. Can you clarify how I can submit the reimbursement for my conference expenses?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Employees have 45 days after their PAC (HR system) termination date to have access to Concur and to have the employee vendor profile remain active.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "234": {
    "question": "As the CU Concur Initial Reviewer for REQ0243879, can you clarify what I need to do for756800X MHE Medical Humanities&Ethics?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "CU Concur Initial Reviewer for756800X MHE Medical Humanities&Ethics as requested from FSSA REQ0243879.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "487": {
    "question": "CNR0088427 is not populating when I try to enter reimbursements for Matias Alvo as a Non-Profiled Payee in Concur. Can you advise me on this issue?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The reason this student does not come up as a \"non-profiled payee\" is because he has been \"opted-in\" to Concur. This means he can login to Concur and enter the expense report himself (or set you up as his delegate).\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "117": {
    "question": "Can I ask about flight insurance?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Insurance for airline ticket is not reimbursable , but sometimes there  could be instances that allow purchase of insurance and this has to be determined by department",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "503": {
    "question": "Can I book travel over the phone by calling World Travel at 855-961-0313?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "World Travel is available at 855-961-0313",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "456": {
    "question": "Can I buy scrubs and then submit them for reimbursement?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "This is up to the departments discretion",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1275": {
    "question": "Can I charge a business class flight on a private grant? We have received confirmation from the sponsor that it is allowed. Since the flight is over 5 hours, will there be any complications with CU policy or Concur? Thank you.",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Any additional questions please reopen or submit a new ticket. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "524": {
    "question": "Can I charge a business class flight to a private grant? I've received confirmation from the sponsor that it's allowed. The flight lasts over 5 hours. Are there any complications with CU policy or Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "If the grant allows business class flight please attach a document in support of that",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "481": {
    "question": "Can I charge airfare to the Central Pay Air/Rail account so that there are no out-of-pocket expenses, and can I book lodging through Concur using a personal card?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Airfare can be charged to the Central Pay Air/Rail account so there is no out-of-pocket expense.\nLodging can be booked through Concur but must be paid for with a personal card (or a corporate card if you have one).",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "647": {
    "question": "Can I get a reimbursement for the conference fee associated with rz2557?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Student must confirm if address information on profile is correct. If update needed can do so going to Student Services Online(SSOL). Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "323": {
    "question": "Can I get an update on report key 285739? I know PER is reimbursing $1,375.13 for data purchased for PhD student Ricardo Munoz as part of the PER Data Purchase Award.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Entered By Chantel Hover: PER is reimbursing $1,375.13 out of the total cost of $3,375.13 for the purchase of data for a PhD student Ricardo Munoz as part of the PER Data Purchase Award. Attached please find the (1) Invoice, and (2) bank statement.\n\nSee attached Concur screen shot.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "582": {
    "question": "Can I get assistance with my expense report? The Report Key is 296799.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Edit hotel/lodging amount to reflect the actual US dollar amount",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "657": {
    "question": "Can I get assistance with the report for uni gn103, Report Key: 300073?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "No error on Report Key :300073\nReady to be submitted",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "679": {
    "question": "Can I get clarification on the car rental fuel expenses? What needs to be documented?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Car rental and car rental fuel needs to be together in one report. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "244": {
    "question": "Can I get clarification on the workflow for lm2892?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hi Nathaniel, \nCurrently the workflow for lm2892 is as follows: \n-Initial Reviewer-this is just a review to make sure all supporting docs are provided and all polices have been followed. \napprover assigned to this step: Joshua Sakolsky\n\n-Financial Approver-This steps is where the approver ensures the chartstring used is appropriate for the expense \nGNS General Admin (COLUM-4702105)\napprover assigned to this step: Curtis Rodgers\nCurtis Rodgers\n\n-Executive Expense Approver\napprover assigned to this step: Justin Pearlman\n\nAfter Justin, it is routed to central AP for a final review and approval. \n\nYou can find the approval work flow for the reports under the report header then choose report timeline. The approval workflow window is along the left side of the page. \nThanks. \n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "659": {
    "question": "Can I get confirmation of the payment status for report key 288562-R/Concur ID for student sa4168?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Report key 288562 was paid out on 06/21/2024 via ach 2001294135. \n\nPlease note that student sa4168 needs to update his local address to a domestic address in Vergil. The student currently has an address from Japan. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "238": {
    "question": "Can I get help with my Concur access? It seems that my ARC access is inactive.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Your ARC access is locked out\nIn order to reinstate your access you need to submit a Reinstate ARC/FinSys Access Application throug hthe service catalog. Please follow these directions:\n1. Go to columbia.service-now.com and login with UNI and password\n3. Click on \"Finance\"\n4. Click on Security Application Requests\n5. Click on \"Reinstate ARC/FinSys Access\"\n. Complete all the required fields and click on \"Order Now\"\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "293": {
    "question": "Can I get reimbursed for babysitting expenses?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Not sure if this is reimbursable in Concur since there is no Expense Type for this type of expense.  Jeannette will call back if needed or reopen the ticket for more assistance.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "113": {
    "question": "Can I get reimbursed for conference registration before the end of the trip?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Conference registration fee can be reimbursed before the end of the trip",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "153": {
    "question": "Can I get reimbursed for parking fees when driving to a conference?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Parking fee is a reimbursable expense",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "305": {
    "question": "Can I get reimbursement for airfare that includes personal travel dates?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The costs related to an earlier departure and/or later return for airfare or rail fare may be reimbursed when the total cost of the airfare or rail fare is clearly documented and demonstrated to be equal to or lower than it would have been for the dates required for business travel. Payee justification is required on the Expense Report that documents the personal days in the itinerary.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1486": {
    "question": "Can I get some guidance on how to generate a manual per diem report in Concur? What are the steps involved?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Please attach documentation supporting the per diem rate as your receipt. Give us a call if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "274": {
    "question": "Can I get some information regarding the payment information for the Concur report?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Report was approved on 9/20 payments are being released in 2 business days. If any follow up give us a call. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "96": {
    "question": "Can I have multiple receipts for one meal expense if the total does not exceed the meal threshold? Thank you, Melissa.",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Multiple receipts for one meal as long as within the threshold is fine",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "298": {
    "question": "Can I opt-in for travel security in Concur? What does that involve?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Your DAF has to opt you into Concur Travel. No application needed.\nPlease let me know if you have any other questions.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "233": {
    "question": "Can I put multiple day trips on the same expense report?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "If the business purpose is the same, they can entered on the same expense report. If the business purposes are different they have to be entered in separate reports. \nThanks. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "39": {
    "question": "Can I reconcile charges for airfare charged to Central Pay/BTA anytime before my trip end date?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "You may reconcile charges for airfare charged to Central Pay/BTA anytime before the trip end date.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "588": {
    "question": "Can I rent a car for a student through Concur to get Columbia's rates and insurance? How would reimbursement work since the student has to pay out-of-pocket?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Travel arranger can make the booking through Concur to get the Columbia rates/insurance. The student will have to pay out-of-pocket and be reimbursed.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "311": {
    "question": "Can I, as a student, be reimbursed for the pizza I purchased via Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "If there is a Columbia business purpose, the reimbursement can be submitted via Concur. Note the student likely will not have access to Concur. If that is the case someone with access will have to process the reimbursement on his behalf as a non-profiled payee. \n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "377": {
    "question": "Can a PhD student request hotel reimbursement before the conference date? I've booked the hotel for a conference in December and would like to know if I can get reimbursed before the conference date, and which policy I need to follow. Thank you!",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Will contact DAF for PhD student's concur access. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "248": {
    "question": "Can a delegate submit an expense report if I, as the payee, have paid with a personal credit card?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Delegates can submit any expense report on behalf of the payee for whom they are a delegate",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "683": {
    "question": "Can anyone provide me with information about the site in Concur for International travel?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "For International Travel , select the country payee travelled to as the site",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "330": {
    "question": "Can someone check on check # 1002282546?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Check will be available for pick up once reissued",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "812": {
    "question": "Can someone explain how the Concur approval workflow works?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Approval workflow question. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "667": {
    "question": "Can someone explain the Concur approval workflow to me? Thank you!",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Report was recalled to remove the adhoc approver that was added. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "628": {
    "question": "Can someone point me to the instructions for creating a Missing Receipt Declaration? I found a link but I need to know where specifically to look in the document.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Please see pg. 4 with instructions for the payee on how to create the Missing Receipt Declaration:\nhttps://www.finance.columbia.edu/sites/default/files/content/Training%20Documents/Concur/Job%20Aids/Job_Aid_Concur_Receipts.pdf",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "273": {
    "question": "Can someone provide me with the details on the Concur report mll2215?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Report is ready for submission. Please upload the trip confirmation email sent by World Travel. Give us a call if any additional questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "116": {
    "question": "Can someone take a look at my Concur report (Flights to UK/France - on report key 314759) to see what may be the issue? I booked in Concur, and it should have been charged to a chartstring, but it seems my card was charged. The documentation on the Concur report shows an estimated cost, and notes that tickets have not been issued.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Personal card was charged. In the future the traveler can select the Central Pay Card payment method to avoid paying out-of-pocket. Reach out to World Travel to obtain an email confirmation.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "397": {
    "question": "Can someone tell me what the World Travel number is?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The number for World Travel Inc is 1-855-961-0313.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1331": {
    "question": "Can student expenses that are over one year old still be entered in Concur, or do they need to be processed as a check request in ARC?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Any additional questions please submit or reopen ticket. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "349": {
    "question": "Can the user submit air/rail travel reimbursements for report numbers YGBZYQ and 4F750A now that she\u2019s moving departments, or should she wait until after the trip end date, which is after her move?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Good morning Meredith,\nThe Air/Rail can be submitted once the ticket is purchase regardless of trip date.\nThank you.\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1403": {
    "question": "Can we reimburse our visiting professor from Europe for their US visa application fee since they need it to teach their course on the Columbia campus in New York? I believe the fee is around $150 or $200, and I just want to confirm if I can process it as a travel expense in Concur alongside their other travel expenses. Please let me know.",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Please reopen ticket or submit a new one if any additional questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "129": {
    "question": "Can you assist me regarding my Concur profile for university NMS2227 & SE2656?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "uni  nms2227 & se2656  have access to concur and can submit own expense report",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "260": {
    "question": "Can you assist with the Concur report for wpm5?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Adding a site to travel reimbursement. Give us a call if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "50": {
    "question": "Can you clarify the policy for travel expenses? I want to ensure I'm following the guidelines correctly.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Nightly rate in the US should not exceed $350. More information on policy please visit https://universitypolicies.columbia.edu/content/travel-expense-policy",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "586": {
    "question": "Can you clarify the policy regarding expenses over 120 days that do not require SBO, where the payee provides justification and the Financial Approver reviews it?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Does not require SBO - payee provides a justification and the Financial Approver is supposed to review the justification.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "572": {
    "question": "Can you clarify what I need to know about Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Please write \"other\" if hotel name is not an option and write name in the comment box. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1346": {
    "question": "Can you clarify what items fall under 'leaving the university' that can be reimbursed as entertainment expenses for business-related occasions? Does it include meals, refreshments, or local transportation?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Any additional questions please reopen or submit new ticket. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "449": {
    "question": "Can you clarify why the Concur reports for bf2187 were returned? They include Report WDG1OT, ND0GBO, and ME2BTX.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "These have to be submitted by payee, As a delegate you can't submit on their behalf. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "601": {
    "question": "Can you confirm if Chao Lu and Yuan Li have profiles in Concur in order for us to process their reimbursements?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Students have to register through SSOL and enter a local US mailing address in order to maintain active ARC Profile\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "771": {
    "question": "Can you confirm if the expense limit for dinner when hosting an external speaker is $150 per person? This is for a collaborator. Thank you for your advice!",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Dear Customer, \n\nWe have not heard back from you regarding your Service Now Incident. Because several days have passed, the Service Center has marked the incident as resolved. If you do not feel this issue was resolved, please re-open this incident and provide the required information.\n \nThank You\n",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "573": {
    "question": "Can you explain the expense report process to me?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Assisted user with expense report process, on how to create a report",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "169": {
    "question": "Can you explain the expense report process?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Assistance creating missing receipt declaration for ground transportation, for airfare please upload trip confirmation itinerary received on the day of booking. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "307": {
    "question": "Can you help me fix errors for the outside party profile 0000235081 for Matthew Lawlor?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Alicia entered comments under the itemization lines that had the alerts.",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "157": {
    "question": "Can you help me with my hotel expenses in Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hotel expenses can't be submitted in advance. The hotel expense must be submitted after the trip has ended.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "537": {
    "question": "Can you help me with the Concur profile for jm3193? I have some questions about it.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "uni    jm3193  has active concur profile",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "1244": {
    "question": "Can you help me with the expense for uni kc3452, Report Key: 295372?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Report has to be recalled and resubmitted since Ervis  is no longer the Financial Approver",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "410": {
    "question": "Can you help me with the expense report associated with Report Key: 306715?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Assisted with expense report process",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "352": {
    "question": "Can you please expedite the central review of the expense report I submitted on 9/06 for employee Dannie Dinh? The expenses need to be processed by Friday to hit the project on time.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Report was approved by Central AP on 9/11 and is now posted and paid.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "617": {
    "question": "Can you please give Evan (el2910) and Chase (cl4651) access to my account so that they can reconcile my remaining corporate card charges? I have departed from the university.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hi Justin,\n\n\nI've added Evan and Chase to the list. please note, the submit option will only be functional after Ian's Concur account becomes inactive (45 days after departure).\u00a0\n\n\nLet me know if you have other questions. Thank you.\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "27": {
    "question": "Can you please let me know if my expense for Airbnb can be reimbursed?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Air bnb is not allowed to be used.\nTravelers are required to utilize hotels and other traditional lodging options when traveling on University business and lodging options can be reviewed on Concur or you can seek assistance from World Travel.\nIn the event that hotels in a specific destination are completely sold out, please email ColumbiaTravel@columbia.edu details of the accommodations that are needed, i.e. the check in/check out dates, number of rooms required, etc.\nThe reason travelers are required to use hotels and other traditional lodging options, is because there is a lack of consistency in safety and security between one Airbnb private home and another and the safety and security of our travelers is paramount. Therefore, pricing would not be a reason for an exemption.\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "432": {
    "question": "Can you please provide the payment status for my expense report? I sent the Expense Report Status Change email on August 8th, and it was set to the Approval status. Thank you!",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "payment has been confirmed. please see attached.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "338": {
    "question": "Can you provide alerts on the expense report for Erin Annunziato's SER Conference expense of $1,943.86?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Redid the itemization. Entered comments for each of the lodging itemizations to state that the nights were not over threshold.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "816": {
    "question": "Can you provide details on submitting a travel expense report?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Please use credit card statement as receipt and boarding pass. Give us a call if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "357": {
    "question": "Can you provide details on the reimbursement policy? I need to understand how it works.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "You can confirm with student if there was a cost difference between the room preference. The department has the choice of refunding in full or partial. Give us a call if any additional questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1408": {
    "question": "Can you provide details on who the Concur approver ebj2117 is?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Please reopen ticket or submit a new one if any additional questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "645": {
    "question": "Can you provide information on Vendor ID 0000269780?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Vendor ID 0000269780\nVendor with outside party classification\nReimbursement can be processed through concur with a CU non profiled payee report type",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "256": {
    "question": "Can you provide me guidance on the Concur report process?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Creating reconciliation report  with new department information Give us a call if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "414": {
    "question": "Can you provide me with details about Concur report bf2187?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Once intial reviewer approves it will route to financila approver no need to add, the report will then go to Concur team and once they approve payment will be released. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "521": {
    "question": "Can you provide me with information about Concur travel arranger access?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "RITM0253183 was approved and when viewing roles assigned to the UNI travel arranger is listed. Must give 24 hours for access to update. Give us a call if any additional questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "176": {
    "question": "Can you provide me with job aids and tips for using Concur as a delegate?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "When submitting a hotel expense for reimbursement, the payee will receive reimbursement for the hotel. Note tax is included on reimbursements. The tax exemption comes into play when supplies/services are purchased directly by Columbia. \n\nYou can prepare the concur expense report for your colleagues if they add you as a delegate. Instructions to for adding a delegate can be found here: https://www.finance.columbia.edu/sites/default/files/content/Training%20Documents/Concur/Job%20Aids/Job_Aid_Concur_Profile_Delegates.pdf\n\nYou can find Concur tips here, as well as links to policies, etc here: \nhttps://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/\n\nHere is the job aid for hotel itemization, you can find instructions about other itemizations, such as meals,  in the Concur tips section: \nhttps://www.finance.columbia.edu/sites/default/files/content/Training%20Documents/Concur/Job%20Aids/Job_Aid_Concur_Itemizing_Lodging.pdf",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "568": {
    "question": "Can you provide me with the status of refund check #1002271024?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Check#1002271024 was issued on June 24th\nReach out to the Departments Finance office to submit a stop payment and reissue request",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "80": {
    "question": "Can you tell me if it's possible to copy a report in Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hi Renee,\nYes. The \"Copy Report\" button is next to the \"Submit Report\" button.\nThank you.\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "367": {
    "question": "Can you tell me more about the alerts on my report for UNI: js1165?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Reminders regarding the fare comparison will not go away but will not prevent the payee from submitting the report.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "531": {
    "question": "Christine Benanti is no longer in our organization, but her pending approvals are still in her Queue even though we cannot view her profile. Can you help with this issue?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hi Francina,\nSince I don't see any roles under Christine anymore, it means the report went to her when she was still in your department. The only way to resolve this is to recall the reports and resubmit. Please let me know if the reports are still go to her after the recall.\n Thank you.\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "41": {
    "question": "Could I get assistance regarding my expense receipts?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Receipt is not required if expense is$50.00    but proof of payment is required",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "653": {
    "question": "Could someone help me with using Concur as a Barnard student?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Barnard students can be set up with outside party vendor classification to receive expense reimbursements",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "675": {
    "question": "Could someone please review my report in Concur and check for any alert messages related to hotel cost segregation?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Report edited and ready to be submitted by user.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "536": {
    "question": "Could you assist me with the approval workflow for the expense report related to UNI: tp2769?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Cecilio and Jody are currently the only Initial Reviewers for department 8213402. Discussed possibility of Karen applying for the IR role so that in situations like this where Cecilio is out sick and Jody is not appropriate to approve Karen could approve as the IR and the Financial Approver.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "708": {
    "question": "Could you clarify how to deal with the exchange rates in my Concur report?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Because the exchange rate for the Uber is higher than the charge on the cc please request the amount charged on the statement. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "355": {
    "question": "Could you clarify the mileage policy for using a personal vehicle for university business? I want to make sure I understand the reimbursement rates and what is allowable.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "From the Travel policy (https://universitypolicies.columbia.edu/content/travel-expense-policy):\n\nTravel by Private Vehicle                                            \nWhen traveling for business purposes, a personal vehicle may be used in order to save time, transport equipment, reduce costs when several people are traveling together, or travel to locations within reasonable driving distance. If a personal vehicle is used primarily for the convenience of the traveler and the approved travel is to a location more than 500 miles beyond the point of origin, reimbursement will not exceed the lesser of the following: 1) the cost of per- mile reimbursement plus tolls; or, 2) the round-trip airfare between the nearest commercial airport serving the origin and destination cities, plus transfer costs to and from the airport.\n                                                                       \nFor the business-related use of a personal vehicle, the traveler will be reimbursed at a rate based on the Federal IRS approved highway mileage guides. Mileage reimbursement covers fuel, maintenance/repairs, insurance, transportation and operating costs, so these will not be reimbursed separately. The traveler will not be reimbursed for the cost of vehicle purchase or lease.\n                                                                       \nIn addition to the mileage allowance, tolls and necessary parking charges may be reimbursed.\n\n                                                  \n\nThe University does not assume liability for damage to personal automobiles used on University business and does not assume liability for deductibles or any other uninsured loss to the vehicle. Expenses for vehicle repairs are not reimbursable. Under no circumstances will the University reimburse parking fines and moving violations on personal vehicle\n\n \n\nPersonal Vehicle Mileage Rate:\n\n    $.655/miles for travel on or after January 1, 2023\n    $.670/miles for travel on or after January 1, 2024\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "566": {
    "question": "Could you help me understand how to generate a report in Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Report exceeds 365 days please contact department so they can submit reimbursement via ARC. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "623": {
    "question": "Could you kindly confirm the payment status for Diana C Otero? Please see the attachment. Thanks!",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Disregard per user",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "376": {
    "question": "Could you please check on the progress of the payment for Abdirahman Wardhere (AW3358)? He was a Clinical Research Fellow from July 1, 2023, to June 30, 2024. The Expense Report was approved, and the payment status says Sent for Payment. He has updated his forwarding address in MyColumbia but still hasn\u2019t received a check.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "All of the expenses on this expense report (Report Key: 284520) were paid with the Central Pay Air/Rail card so no money was due to the employee.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "259": {
    "question": "Could you please itemize the hotel charges per day? My contact number is 203-898-4970.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "User able to submit report in Concur.\n\nPlease call the FSC service if you need assistance with another transaction.\n\nThank you.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "692": {
    "question": "Could you please opt Matteo Heilbrun (mbh2155, CNR0139341) into the Concur expense module so he may receive reimbursements? Thanks, Lani.",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Job aid attached",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "1169": {
    "question": "Could you please provide me with the status of my expense report with Report Key: 295018?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Report Key :295018\nSubmitted & Pending Approval\nJames Singletary",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "212": {
    "question": "Could you please remove the Concur supervisor eb2724 from the Concur profile of ddm2154? Her reports are currently routing to the wrong initial reviewer. Thank you!",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hi Dianilka,\nOpting-in or Opting-out is control by departmental DAF please contact your DAF.\nThank you.\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "668": {
    "question": "Could you provide guidance on how to generate a Concur report?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Under site must identify country where expenses took place. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "387": {
    "question": "Could you provide information about how I can update my name in my Concur profile? HR has indicated it\u2019s not an issue on their end since my name appears correctly in PAC. I received an inquiry from Mabel Abraham, UNI ma3484, who would like to remove her middle name from her Concur profile to match her travel documents. Specifically, she wants her profile to show: First name: Mabel, Middle name: (blank), Last name: Abraham. What does she need to do to request this change? Thank you for any information you can provide.",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Hi Priya,\nMiddle name for ma3484 has been removed from her Concur profile.\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "622": {
    "question": "Could you provide the status of my report number: 0LXPBP? I was not able to find it. Thank you!",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "To check status go to the Home menu at the top of the page and then select Expense. You should then see the report pending \"cost object approval\" which means it is pending Financial Approver approval (Julie Fisher for this report). ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "285": {
    "question": "Could you review Concur report H2861L? The payee is unable to create a Receipt Declaration. Thanks.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "If the receipt is for under $50 and is not for air, rail, lodging, or car rental the payee will not be able to do the declaration. Or if there is another document already attached to the expense it will have to be removed, the declaration done, and then the document can be reattached to the report as a whole under Manage Receipts>Manage Attachments.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "22": {
    "question": "Could you tell me who the travel arrangers are for department 4710203?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "hj2454 Joy,Hana                         CU Travel Arranger 470200X School of General Studies\n\n,Rafaelina CU Travel Arranger 4702103 School of General Studies\n\nme2002 Enriquez,Maria         CU Travel Arranger 4702105 School of General Studies\n\nes3233 Shamilova,Esfir         CU Travel Arranger 4703105 School of General Studies\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "436": {
    "question": "David Blitzer's Concur access has been deactivated since he transferred to the Congenital fellowship. IT mentioned contacting the department about this. Should we submit a Payment Works invite for reactivation or is there another step? Thank you!",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Catherine,\nDavid has a PAC Termination Date of 07/01/2024\nConcur is available to active Columbia University Employees only. If his fellowship is with Presbyterian Hospital he is not going to get automatic access to concur, however, an affiliate access can be requested through the service catalog. Please reach out to Raquel Marin rm2698@cumc.columbia.edu\n+1 212 305 9622 if that is the case\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "230": {
    "question": "Do I need to upload my receipts individually in Concur, or can I scan them all and upload them as one file?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hi Katherine, \nEach receipt has to be uploaded to each individual expense line. \nThan",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "592": {
    "question": "Do outside parties receive notifications when their expense reports have been processed by the departments?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The notifications go to the account that the expense reports were created in, hence they would get all the notifications.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "360": {
    "question": "Does Robert Hincapie have a profile set up in Concur for reimbursements and expense reporting? If so, does he have to submit the report himself or can I use the non-profiled payee report type?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Robert Hincapie has his own concur ID CNR0143091. He is classified as an employee and can submit his own reports. If he would prefer to have you or someone else in the department do it, he will have to add you as a delegate (see job aid below). His reports are not eligible to be submitted as a non-profile payee, I have provided a job aid for how to submit the report on his behalf below.\n\nHow to add a delegate: https://www.finance.columbia.edu/sites/default/files/content/Training%20Documents/Concur/Job%20Aids/Job_Aid_Concur_Profile_Delegates.pdf\nSubmitting expense report as a delegate (he must first add you): https://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/news/how-do-i-create-expense-report-behalf-someone-else\nPlease note this job aid starts with the delegate process at the top and then the non-profiled payee at the bottom. Please follow the instructions for the delegate. Let me know if you have any questions.\nThanks.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "413": {
    "question": "Does Zihang Su have a profile set up in Concur for reimbursement processing? If so, could you please provide the vendor type and ID number? Thank you.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Reopen or submit a new ticket if any additional questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "648": {
    "question": "Does lk2995 have a CNR?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Yes, this employee has an active CNR. It is cnr0136789. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "222": {
    "question": "Five separate PIs are not able to see my name in the Concur \"Initial Reviewer\" dropdown. Although I've been told that the issue is resolved, I was informed it was due to the PIs selecting the incorrect department. I've been granted access to all relevant departments, so I'd appreciate any support in correcting this issue.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "For the three UNIs you said were having trouble selecting you:\n\n- VAF5 - The issue is with the Admin Department (please see attached screenshot). The Admin Department selected is not a department that you have Initial Reviewer approval rights for.\n- BSW2110 - This individual was able to select you as an Initial Reviewer on their most recent report\n- CHL2159- Same as for VAF5, the Admin Department selected is not a department that you have Initial Reviewer approval rights for.\n\nFor VAF5 and CHL2159 there are two possible solutions:\n\n1. They could be instructed to change the Admin Department (the Division and Sub-Division would also need to be updated since they are connected) to an Admin Department that you have approval rights for or\n\n2. If appropriate you could apply to become an Initial Reviewer for the departments they are using as their Admin Department.\n\nYou can discuss these options with your department.\n\nFor the PIs you wanted to confirm would be able to select you as IR:\n\nNE5 - default admin dept 5701101, would not currently be able to select you as IR\nLG123 - no default admin dept so it would depend on what they select\nDG2121 - no default admin dept so it would depend on what they select\nEW157 - no default admin dept so it would depend on what they select \nAD3324 - no default admin dept so it would depend on what they select \nTH2258 - no default admin dept so it would depend on what they select \nCSS2109 - no default admin dept so it would depend on what they select ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "767": {
    "question": "For Dean Andres' report, ID # EFA031D47E194D3FB250, it appears there are no approvers defined in the workflow. How can we resolve this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Dear Customer, \n\nWe have not heard back from you regarding your Service Now Incident. Because several days have passed, the Service Center has marked the incident as resolved. If you do not feel this issue was resolved, please re-open this incident and provide the required information.\n \nThank You\n",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "34": {
    "question": "For IWS2108, the student profile in ARC - CNR0061134, can the department process reimbursement for her as a Non-Profiled Payee with Student vendor type? Also, how do I opt in the student to get Concur access?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Student Employees and Student Non-Employees by default have not been given access to Travel or Expense, but can be opted-in by a School / department DAF (Student Employees) or Accounts Payable (Student Non-Employees)\n\nAffiliates have not been given default access to Concur; only CU employees have default access.  Affiliates must request access to Concur using the FSSA application.\n\nIn order to opt-in a student non-employee to have access to Concur Travel and Expense or Expense only, a Service Now Incident is required from the department's DAF or SBO. The incident should contain the student's name, UNI, and Vendor Number and must indicate which Concur module is requested: \n\nTravel \u2013 access to book Air and/or Rail to be charged on the Columbia Air/Rail Central Pay. Hotel and car rentals can be reserved as well.\nExpense \u2013 access to create and submit expense reports to reconcile travel and/or business expenses charged on the Columbia Air/Rail Central Pay or for reimbursement of out of pocket expenses. This includes access to the Concur Request module to request pre-trip approval.\n\nGo to  https://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/content/getting-started",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "604": {
    "question": "For Report ID 272E183874854337A4AE, I need help confirming how to clear discrepancies so my reimbursement can be processed. It seems there are mixed meal receipts and meal per diems on the same trip. What should I do?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Recommended deleting the stops on the itinerary:  Travel Allowance>Manage Travel Allowance >Available Itineraries >Edit > select both rows in the itinerary >Delete Rows>Save",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "57": {
    "question": "For our recurring staff meetings where food is provided, should I use the Group Meal as Expense Type for these expenses, or should I use Meetings and Events instead?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "use group meeting is informal",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "254": {
    "question": "For reimbursement related to Supplier ID Dino Alexander Janssen, what steps do I need to follow?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Process reimbursement on a check request through ARC",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "590": {
    "question": "For the CONCUR report RRUTOE, what does \u201cpending cost object approval\u201d mean, and is this causing a delay in reimbursement?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Cost Object Approval = Financial approval",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1260": {
    "question": "From the old department A&S Religion (4030102), it should now reflect the new department Psychology (4048102).",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "please see email response. Email me if you have issues making the updates.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "665": {
    "question": "Good Afternoon, I\u2019m trying to submit a reimbursement in Concur for student Umme Fardina Adil (ua2194), but their CNR supplier ID isn\u2019t showing up in ARC or Concur. Is there something the student needs to do for their profile to appear? Thank you!",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Closing ticket as resolved. No further response/comments received from user.\n\n\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "247": {
    "question": "Good afternoon FSA team, I hope this email finds you well. I\u2019m a Financial approver in Concur. I have two employees who report to me. The update in PAC was made months ago, but whenever they submit reports in Concur, those reports do not route to me for approval. We checked their default expense approvers in Concur, and it appears that the field is blank. How can I fix this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "DAF needs to resolve it",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "165": {
    "question": "Good afternoon, my name is Mairead McGrath, UNI mm6414. After my work-related trip to Las Vegas from July 8-9, I submitted all required documentation to Rosanna, but the approval flow remains greyed out. I haven't received the amount of $556.13 back in my checking account or credit card, and it hasn't appeared in my biweekly pay either. What should I do to resolve this issue?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Report needed to be edited and resubmitted. Currently pending Rosanna's approval again.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "422": {
    "question": "Good morning, I am Christopher Yera, a postdoc with the CSSW CPSP team. I will be attending a conference in November representing our Center. If I register now, I will receive a discount. Can I get reimbursed now ahead of travel to the conference, and if so, what is the best way to proceed? Should I process it as a pre-travel advance in Concur or as a regular reimbursement? Thank you for your advice.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Air fare and registration fee /Membership fee can be reimbursed before end of trip\nHe can submit expense reimbursement request through concur",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "384": {
    "question": "Good morning, I currently serve as the financial approver for Concur transactions in the Department of Mathematics (4046102). About two weeks ago, something changed and I am no longer able to approve some transactions. I receive an error message stating, 'There are no approvers defined in your workflow. Please contact your Expense administrator.' Previously, I approved these transactions, and they went to central AP for audit. Has something changed with the Concur workflow? How do I resolve this error? Thank you. Here are some (but not all) of the Concur report IDs generating the error message: 303121 / Jiakai Li/Pisa Conference 2024, 303167 / Qianhe Qin/Pisa Conference 2024, 303044 / Laura Starkston/Pisa Conference, 303082 / Deeparaj Bhat/Pisa Conference 24. They all seem to be for non-profiled payees with sponsored funding (this batch is for a conference sponsored by a GG project in Math). I don't recall having this problem last year or earlier in the summer. Please let me know if I can provide any additional information.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "SBO approval required due to the issue with expense reports on the same dates entered by the same person.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "32": {
    "question": "Good morning, can you tell me how I can add a vendor ID to my Concur profile?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "For a consultant or temp with Concur temporary access who does not have a CNR vendor profile they would first need to be set up as a vendor through PaymentWorks. Once they have their vendor ID an incident should be submitted asking to link their vendor ID to their Concur profile. In the incident please provide their vendor ID and their UNI.\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "56": {
    "question": "Good morning. I received an email that I have 5 outstanding credit card transactions in Concur, but when I log in, I cannot view any of them. I have attached screenshots. Thanks!",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The transactions appear under Shante's profile. You received the email because you are Shante's delegate.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "132": {
    "question": "Good morning. I'm working on submitting my expenses for a recent conference I attended in Seattle. I had a few meals with another person, but we could not get separate checks. The receipts are itemized, and I know which items were mine. How should I submit those expenses? Thank you.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Catherine ,\nYou just have to enter the amount of the meal you are claiming and add a comment why you are claiming for half of the bill\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "335": {
    "question": "Griffin Danninger, a full-time permanent employee and Officer of Administration, cannot access Concur. He received a denied access message when trying to log in. How can we resolve this since we need to arrange travel for him urgently?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Provided instructions to login to Concur. If Griffin is still having issues please reopen the incident.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "215": {
    "question": "Hello - I'm encountering errors when trying to log in to Concur; please see the attached screenshot.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Estefany\nYou have employment termination date of 08/10/2024 in PAC.\nConcur is available to active employees only. If you are rehired, then you have to wait until your employment data is updated in PAC\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "619": {
    "question": "Hello - My name is Zachary Roberts (UNI zjr2105) and I am writing because I am unable to log in to Concur. I have been able to log in in the past, but my status has changed several times over the years. I am currently hired through the Center for American Studies. My administrator told me that I should be able to log in for reimbursements related to two programs I'm affiliated with, but I received an error message in the attached screenshot. Can you please provide solutions to give me access if this is a technical or permissions issue? Thank you very much.",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Hello, \n\nWe have not heard back from you for several days now and the Service Center has marked the incident as resolved. If you do not feel this issue was resolved, please re-open this incident for further assistance.\n\nThank You.\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "538": {
    "question": "Hello Financial Service Center, I am having an issue where Concur is not saving any of the changes I make to Concur Report No. 2NOGB0/Concur Report ID No. CB5D3E64AD30479B8674/Concur Report Key No. 288668. Can you assist me with this? Thank you.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hi Michael,\nsorry for the late response. i see that you had added comments to the expenses.\nPlease let me know if your issues were not resolved.\nThank you.\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "78": {
    "question": "Hello Financial Service Center, I'm writing about Concur Report Key No. 317488. The financial approver is receiving a warning that this report is a duplicate of another report that was deleted when my report was created. Can you please clarify why there is a warning indicating that Concur Report Key No. 317488 is a duplicate? Thank you for your assistance.",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Hi Michael,\nI'm not able to pull up report ID: EBA1C6FC30B04F36A8DB in Concur as a processed expense. please continue the approval process.\nThank you.\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "48": {
    "question": "Hello! I received an email from Concur about an unreconciled credit card transaction, and I see that it was a refund for a portion of travel I booked on behalf of someone else for $91.67. I have already processed travel expenses for this trip -- Report #8CVJW8. How do I attach this unreconciled refund to an expense report that has already been processed? I never received a receipt from Delta or Concur for the refund, and I'm not sure how to proceed. I would appreciate your help with this. Thank you!",
    "out-of-scope": "unsure",
    "human_answer": "Dear Customer, \n\nWe have not heard back from you regarding your Service Now Incident. Because several days have passed, the Service Center has marked the incident as resolved. If you do not feel this issue was resolved, please re-open this incident and provide the required information.\n \nThank You\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "115": {
    "question": "Hello,\nI am trying to submit an expense report in Concur for a conference, but I cannot see \"Hotel/Lodging\" or \"Airfare\" in the drop-down menu. My colleague made a test submission and was able to see all items in the dropdown menu. Thank you for your help!",
    "out-of-scope": "unsure",
    "human_answer": "change the report to CU travel Expense",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1089": {
    "question": "Hello, Concur team, I can't find the Concur ID in the system for a student named Joseph Lee (jtl2164). He needs to be reimbursed for conference expenses. Could you please advise me on his Concur ID? Thank you.",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Reopen or submit new ticket with questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "540": {
    "question": "Hello, I am a research assistant needing urgent help with getting trip planning access on Concur so I can present my work in October. It's really important that I get this updated ASAP.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "FSSA has been submitted for Concur access. Any questions please submit a new ticket or reopen. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "515": {
    "question": "Hello, I am the Administrative Manager for my department. A travel expense report for Jessica Weaver (jw4324) was approved and sent for payment on 7/25, but she says she has not yet received her reimbursement. Is there any way to check if the payment has been dispersed and to what account? If it hasn't been dispersed yet, is there an estimated date she can expect it? Thank you!",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "If it was for report key 295430 for $369.10, it was paid via ach ref 2001307657 on 07/29/2024. If this is not the payment you are referring to, please provide more details the report number or key and the amount.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "13": {
    "question": "Hello, I am trying to reimburse a student named Batel Levy with CNR0114205 on Concur. Everything seems in order, but I cannot find her information on the system. Can you help me figure out why?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Eliza,\nCNR0114205 had a concur access which is currently inactive. This happened at the end of the semester and this student needs to be opted in again for access and should be able to submit own expense\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "235": {
    "question": "Hello, I can't access Concur to file a reimbursement form for the purchase of a poster printout required by my department. How can I submit this reimbursement? Thank you!",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "As a student, you do not have default access to login to Concur. There are two options to reimburse you:\n\n1. Your department can enter the expense report on your behalf using a \"non-profiled payee\" report type.\n\n2. Your department can request to have you \"opted in\" to Concur so that you can login to Concur and enter the expense report yourself.\n\nPlease follow up with your department to see which option they want to use. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "279": {
    "question": "Hello, I need to reimburse student Alexander Fan, but I cannot find him in the system. He is registered this semester and has a local residential hall address. Can you please tell me why he is not showing up on Concur? Thanks.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Will be added as a delegate for af3340. Reopen or submit new ticket if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1398": {
    "question": "Hello, I submitted Concur TBER Report Key: 221419 (Report Number: TPNABK) on 11/03/2023 for reimbursement to Sacha Toberoff (CNR0110471). Even though it's marked as paid on 11/09/2023 with Check/EFT 221419-1002209734, the student claims he never received the check. Can you check if it has been cashed? Thank you!",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Payment received. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "223": {
    "question": "Hello, I'm a lab technician at the CUIMC medical center trying to book a flight through Concur. I can't access a page to view flight itineraries and wonder if my permissions need to be adjusted.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Jacob,\nYou do not have access to concur travel. You need to be opted in for that access. Please reach out to the DA or Seniot Business Officer of your department\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "661": {
    "question": "Hello, I'm having trouble finding Feiyue Yang (fy2306) in Concur. Feiyue is a DSB admitted student, and I\u2019ve never had issues finding my students in the system before. Can you help me understand why this is happening? Thanks, Chris.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Students must have registered for a current or future semester and have entered a local US mailing address in SSOL to have an active ARC profile",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "388": {
    "question": "Hello, I'm reaching out because a Law School employee, Max Milliken (mm6757), is having trouble logging into Concur as detailed in the attached email. Could you please provide some guidance for him? Thank you.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Jenny,\nThis employee's hiring documents have not been fully processed and I don't see a PAC profile for him. Need to wait until profile is set up in PAC and after that he will have automatic access to concur\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "149": {
    "question": "Hello, I'm trying to report a missing receipt for my Expense Report, but the 'Accept and Create' button isn't active. How should I proceed?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "You're correct, it's below the threshold for missing receipts. See excerpt from the travel-expense policy:\nhttps://universitypolicies.columbia.edu/content/travel-expense-policy\nReceipts must be provided for all air, rail, lodging, and rental car expenses. For all other expense types, receipts must be provided if the expense is equal to or in excess of $50. Otherwise, Payee Justification and Financial Approval is required and a Missing Receipt Affidavit must be completed\n\nSince this is a meal under $50, a missing receipt affidavit is not required and can't be generated.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "428": {
    "question": "Hello, can you please give Emily Padilla Chicas access to submit her travel expenses for reimbursement? She just graduated and will be working for us for a few months. Thanks!",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "profile is active",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1111": {
    "question": "Hello, is there a way for me to access past Concur vouchers if I wasn't the initiator? Thanks.",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Document attached",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1051": {
    "question": "Hello, one of our new faculty members has submitted relocation expenses for reimbursement but wasn't aware of the university's policies on acceptable forms of payment. They thought they'd receive a lump sum like their previous employer and used gift card balances from Amazon. May we request an exception to the policy and allow the reimbursement? The new faculty member is now informed and will follow the policy moving forward.",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Reopen or submit new ticket if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "249": {
    "question": "Hi team, I'm attempting to submit a report for a group meal, but I don't see the usual place to identify the attendees. Can you check on your end? Thanks. Anna",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Must select expense report type in order to insert attendees. Submit a new ticket if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "655": {
    "question": "Hi team, Student Jungyun Han - jh4572 confirmed that he added a local US address to his SSOL account. Can you help confirm if this has been successfully updated? His profile is currently inactive in ARC. Thank you, Anna.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Students should have active SSOL profile with local US mailing address to maintain active ARC profile",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "111": {
    "question": "Hi team, we're unable to locate a number of students in Concur, can someone help figure out what is going on? The students have confirmed they have local addresses in their SSOL profiles and are registered.",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Two students appearing in Concur as non-profiled payees today. Third student needs to add a US address to SSOL profile.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "516": {
    "question": "Hi there, I need to create a report in Concur to get reimbursed for student tickets for a United Nations tour that I purchased with my credit card. I already updated my Concur profile. Which type of report should I file for United Nations student tickets: a travel report, business report, or CU-non profiled payee? Thank you, Jeanne Lambert (UNI: jl3526)",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The report type you need to submit is CU Business Expense",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "253": {
    "question": "Hi there, one of our postdocs is traveling for a conference in January and has already paid for his hotel. He wants to know if there\u2019s a way to request reimbursement before his stay. How should he proceed? He filled out the Concur expense report (#26SZF6) but can\u2019t submit it yet because he hasn\u2019t concluded his stay. He\u2019s worried that if he waits until January, the reimbursement request will exceed 120 days from payment. Is there any way to request hotel reimbursement prior to the trip?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Expenses for lodging/hotel can not be reimbursed before the end of the trip. The only expenses that can be refunded before completing the trip are Airfare and registration or membership fee\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "363": {
    "question": "Hi, Concur team: I purchased gifts for a Postdoc in his farewell party. What expense type should I select in Concur? Should I segregate this expense to an unrestricted fund? Thank you!",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Please refer to Training Library site, which contains many helpful Concur Job Aids, including the \"Itemizing Gifts in an Expense Report in Concur\" Job Aid, also attached in this email. Thank you. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "571": {
    "question": "Hi, I recently submitted a request to reinstate my Concur account (INC2665270). I was advised to reach out to my Department Administrator for assistance. However, I've been told to file another incident through Finance. Can you help me with the reinstatement of my Concur account?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "As a student employee your access to Concur is handled directly by the DAF for CUMC, Raquel Marin, rm2698@cumc.columbia.edu. Please have your DA reach out to Raquel directly to request to have you re-opted in to Concur. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "557": {
    "question": "Hi, I'm trying to log into Concur, but I'm just getting an error message when I enter my UNI information. Can someone help me resolve this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Thomas ,\nConcur is available for Columbia University employees only and not for Presbyterian Hospital employees, however, an affiliate temp access can be requested through the service catalog. Please reach out to\nRaquel Marin who will assist you with the process\n\nAVP,Int Cntrls Compl,Dep Cntlr\nrm2698@cumc.columbia.edu\n+1 212 305 9622\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1079": {
    "question": "Hi, I've been pending a reimbursement of $2446.96 from a conference in July. Could you please let me know the status and if I should expect payment soon? It says it is pending approval from Barbara Rosenberg. Thank you!",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Please follow up with Barbara Rosenberg directly about approving this report.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1160": {
    "question": "Hi, this expense report, Concur Report ID: MH40CI for $11,518.42, has been pending for months. I've contacted the approver with no update. Can you expedite it for review and approval? Thanks!",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Reopen or submit new ticket if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "167": {
    "question": "How can I add my hotel Epic Sana Lisboa in Lisbon, Portugal to my expense report if it's not already in Concur? Can it be added?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "When the hotel name or the parent company name is not available, please select other and put the hotel information in the comment field.\nLet me know if you have any other questions.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "669": {
    "question": "How can I add per diems for multiple students attending the same conference with the same exact dates when the system won\u2019t allow me to use those dates again?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "If you receive the overlapping issue you need to do the per diem manual calculation instead of using the itinerary option\nThe last two pages show how to do that\n\nhttps://www.finance.columbia.edu/sites/default/files/content/Training%20Documents/Concur/Job%20Aids/Job_Aid_Concur_Per_Diem.pdf\nYou can use the expense type Per Diem (Manual Calculation) for these meals.\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "499": {
    "question": "How can I add someone to Concur? Do I need to sign them up for training? We have a new coach who needs a corporate card, so please advise!",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "FSSA must be submitted to give any access to Concur. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "124": {
    "question": "How can I allocate my expense report to two different chartstrings for GT008619 and 7582302?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "In the report select all the expense lines, then click Allocate. Add a second chartstring, then can adjust the amount going to each chartstring.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "467": {
    "question": "How can I assign a seat to my booked flight? I need guidance on this process.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "If the option is not available please contact WTI 1-855-961-0313 they can assist with your airfare  booking. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "24": {
    "question": "How can I get access to the Concur reporting manager?",
    "out-of-scope": "unsure",
    "human_answer": "Please reopen ticket or give us a call if any additional questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "303": {
    "question": "How can I reconcile airfare expenses for multiple participants?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Each posted expense has to be reconciled separately",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "267": {
    "question": "How can I reconcile my travel expenses with my personal bank account?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hi Myrriam,\nPlease follow the below link on options to refund the University.\nhttps://www.finance.columbia.edu/content/return-funds-university\n\nPlease note, when reconciling the charge, under itemization, you need mark the charge as \"Personal\" so that Concur know to note that the expense is the amount owed by you. \n\nThank you.\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "107": {
    "question": "How can I reduce the amount of per diem to exactly $2500 when the calculation is showing over by $20?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Can use the expense type Per Diem Reduction or directly in the manual calculation there is also a box called \"Total Amount of Provided Meals / Reduction Amount.\"",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1184": {
    "question": "How can I submit an expense reimbursement request?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Job aid attached",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "633": {
    "question": "How can I tell if a Corporate Card was used for payment?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "If Corporate Card is used, you will have a transaction in 'Available Expenses' section in Concur that is pending reconciliation.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "21": {
    "question": "How can payees view past expense reports in Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Under Expense they can change the View drop down to view past expense reports.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "530": {
    "question": "How can students get access to Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "If the student is registered in a the current semester and has a domestic address in their student portal, they should have an active CNR ID that will allow the department personnel to submit expenses on their behalf. If the department wants the student to have their own access a self-service ticket has to be submitted by Department DAF & it should contain the students name, uni , & the kind of access requested(either Business expense Travel Expense or both).\nYou can more information here in section 8: https://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/content/getting-started\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "423": {
    "question": "How do I allocate alcohol on Concur when the project number is a UR? Thanks.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "I'm not sure what your question is. Please clarify and provide more details.\nIf this was for a group meal, you choose the group meal, add attendees, and itemize.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "64": {
    "question": "How do I allocate ps2087 to multiple chartstrings?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "As a recap to our call, \nWe allocated the group meal to the 3 chartstrings. Here is a job aid for future reference: https://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/news/how-do-i-allocate-expenses-multiple-chartstrings\n\nWe also added attendees. Here is a job aid for future reference: https://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/news/how-do-i-add-attendeesrecipients-group-meal-entertainment-or-gift-expense\n\nAs always, you can always call us if you have any questions or need help with the steps, do not hesitate to give us a call at 212-854-2122. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "20": {
    "question": "How do I arrange travel?",
    "out-of-scope": "irrelevant question",
    "human_answer": "Here is the job aid we discussed: https://www.finance.columbia.edu/sites/default/files/content/Training%20Documents/Concur/Job%20Aids/Job_Aid_Concur_Profile_Delegates.pdf\nAs long as you have the travel role, you should be able to book travel on their behalf. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "340": {
    "question": "How do I book a flight in Concur through World Travel Inc.? I found the links for more information but need guidance on the booking process.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "World Travel Inc. link:  https://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/content/world-travel-inc\nHow to Pay for Travel link:  https://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/content/travel-how-tos.  Then go to item #3 for more information.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "319": {
    "question": "How do I book travel using Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Travel booked through concur on central Air/Rail will show up as available expense within 3-5 business days",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "213": {
    "question": "How do I calculate mileage for travel by private vehicle?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Per the policy this can be done. Here it is https://universitypolicies.columbia.edu/content/travel-expense-policy\nTravel by Private Vehicle                                            \nWhen traveling for business purposes, a personal vehicle may be used in order to save time, transport equipment, reduce costs when several people are traveling together, or travel to locations within reasonable driving distance. If a personal vehicle is used primarily for the convenience of the traveler and the approved travel is to a location more than 500 miles beyond the point of origin, reimbursement will not exceed the lesser of the following: 1) the cost of per- mile reimbursement plus tolls; or, 2) the round-trip airfare between the nearest commercial airport serving the origin and destination cities, plus transfer costs to and from the airport.\n                                                                       \nFor the business-related use of a personal vehicle, the traveler will be reimbursed at a rate based on the Federal IRS approved highway mileage guides. Mileage reimbursement covers fuel, maintenance/repairs, insurance, transportation and operating costs, so these will not be reimbursed separately. The traveler will not be reimbursed for the cost of vehicle purchase or lease.\n                                                                       \nIn addition to the mileage allowance, tolls and necessary parking charges may be reimbursed.\n\n                                                  \n\nThe University does not assume liability for damage to personal automobiles used on University business and does not assume liability for deductibles or any other uninsured loss to the vehicle. Expenses for vehicle repairs are not reimbursable. Under no circumstances will the University reimburse parking fines and moving violations on personal vehicle\n\n \n\nPersonal Vehicle Mileage Rate:\n\n$.655/miles for travel on or after January 1, 2023\n$.670/miles for travel on or after January 1, 2024\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "184": {
    "question": "How do I calculate my personal car mileage expense using the provided link?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Here is the Job Aid for Mileage Calculation:\n\nhttps://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/news/how-do-i-calculate-my-personal-car-mileage-expense",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "832": {
    "question": "How do I create a Non-Profile Payee expense type if I am signed in to my account? If I am a Delegate and signed in as the account holder, should it be either a Travel or Business Expense?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Create a NPP expense type.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "500": {
    "question": "How do I create a new expense report rather than going under Requests? Can you help me confirm the chartstring information with my department?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Creating a new expense report rather than going under Requests. Confirm chartstring information with department.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "700": {
    "question": "How do I create a report for a Non-Profiled Payee in Concur using either a Student or Outside Party vendor type? I need to search for the vendor ID.",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Create a report Non-Profiled Payee in Concur with either Student or  Outside Party vendor type (depends on how the student profile is classified in ARC).  Search for vendor id.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1406": {
    "question": "How do I delete an existing Request in Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Deleted/canceled by user by clicking the Delete icon.",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "262": {
    "question": "How do I get removed as a delegate for another user in Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Needs to be removed as a delegate from a former faculty. Give us a call if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "228": {
    "question": "How do I go about submitting an expense reimbursement?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Receipt is not required for expenses of <$50.00 unless it is Airfare and Hotel lodging",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "672": {
    "question": "How do I handle guest bookings in Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Can book rail ticket on behalf of the vendor. Will need vendor id at the time of processing reimbursement. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "358": {
    "question": "How do I itemize first class airfare in my expense report? Can someone guide me through the process?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "When itemizing first class airfare you must enter the economy amount in the airfare field and the difference in airfare segregated field.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "206": {
    "question": "How do I itemize hotel charges that exceed the threshold? I adjusted amounts on expense lines and added a justification, but I'm not sure if I did it right.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Adjusted amounts on Hotel/Lodging expense lines to $350, added two new lines for the Hotel - Segregated amounts, entered justification comments on the itemization lines.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "528": {
    "question": "How do I itemize meals and hotel expenses when they exceed the threshold for my expense reports?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Went over itemizations for the meals and hotel that were over threshold.",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "342": {
    "question": "How do I log in to Concur? I also found a job aid on creating expense reports. Can you provide more details on that?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Here is the job aid on creating expense reports:\nhttps://www.finance.columbia.edu/content/creating-expense-reports-concur",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "270": {
    "question": "How do I look up previously approved reports in Concur? I need to go to Approvals > Reports, then change the \"view\" menu and use the search options to narrow it down, right?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Approvals>Reports then change the \"view\" menu and use the search options to narrow it down.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "196": {
    "question": "How do I manage my delegates for Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The only way to add delegates is for the concur user to log into their profile and follow the steps in this job aid: \nhttps://www.finance.columbia.edu/sites/default/files/content/Training%20Documents/Concur/Job%20Aids/Job_Aid_Concur_Profile_Delegates.pdf",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "182": {
    "question": "How do I obtain comparison flights when booking a flight through Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "If flight is on business class a comparison flight for economy /coach class should be obtained at the time of booking",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "88": {
    "question": "How do I pay the Concur transaction fee with my credit card?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The transaction fee has already been paid on the Columbia Air/Rail card, it just has to be reconciled. Since you stated that you can't put it on the grant, please reach out to your department admins to find out what unrestricted chartstring you can use to reconcile it. If they require that you pay them back you can inquire with them the process for reimbursement. Here is a job aid for reconciling the charge: https://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/news/how-do-i-reconcile-corporate-card-or-airrail-central-pay-transactions\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "356": {
    "question": "How do I process the reimbursement for a Visa extension fee through Concur? The expense type is Passport/Visa Fees.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Process through Concur, expense type = Passport/Visa Fees.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "68": {
    "question": "How do I put the amount over $350 into the 'hotel-segregated' itemization expense type on the itemization tab, and reduce the night to $350?",
    "out-of-scope": "unsure",
    "human_answer": "On the itemization tab, put the amount over $350 into the \"hotel-segregated\" itemization expense type, then reduce the night to $350.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1141": {
    "question": "How do I receive reimbursement?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "User is directed to department' s Finance Office",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "108": {
    "question": "How do I reconcile airline credit for a cancelled trip?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Credit will post under available expenses and can be moved to a report page and reconciled",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "30": {
    "question": "How do I reimburse a student using the 'non-profiled payee' report type in Concur? Can you provide more details?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Use the \"non-profiled payee\" report type in Concur.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "417": {
    "question": "How do I segregate a tip that exceeds the allowable threshold?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The amount of tip that is  over the threshold should go in the personal/non reimbursable category of the itemization tab.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1003": {
    "question": "How do I separate alcohol from the rest of the meal in Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Provided instructions to itemize and then allocate the alcohol itemization line to a non-sponsored project.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "136": {
    "question": "How do I set up direct deposit in Concur for my reimbursements?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Your AP Reimbursement method is related to your Direct Deposit settings for Payroll with one of the following defaults, which you can change as desired:\n\nIf your Payroll is not setup with Direct Deposit, your AP Reimbursement defaults so you are paid by check.\nIf your Payroll is set up with a single Direct Deposit account, your AP Reimbursement defaults so that you are paid using the same Direct Deposit account.\nIf your Payroll is set up with multiple Direct Deposit accounts, your AP Reimbursement defaults so you are paid using the method marked as \"Remaining Balance\" in the Direct Deposit module.\n\nFor more details, please go to https://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/news/remember-update-your-ap-reimbursement-using-pac-self-service.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "172": {
    "question": "How do I submit receipts and per diems for the same trip? I need to justify using both and require financial approval.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Enter the itinerary and then check off to exclude the days that receipts will be provided. Then enter the individual meals as separate items on the report.\nWill need to provide a justification for using per diems and actuals on the same trip and will require Financial Approval.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "626": {
    "question": "How does Concur calculate the Personal Car Mileage rate? I see that it is currently $0.67 per mile when using the \"Personal Car Mileage\" expense type.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Concur will calculate this when using the \"Personal Car Mileage\" expense type - it is currently $0.67/mile.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "618": {
    "question": "How does an outside party get reimbursed if they booked for themselves through the World Travel website? Do they receive a receipt and then we would reimburse them through Concur as a non-profiled payee?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Gordon,\nThat is correct, you will process the reimbursement as NPP with Outside Party vendor type.\n\nThanks,\nJudy",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "577": {
    "question": "How is the reimbursement process through Concur disbursed?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Expense reimbursement will be deposited directly to the account you receive your payroll payment",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "631": {
    "question": "How long does it usually take for the Concur system to be updated for vendor ID 0000269930? It's not available yet, and I understand it might have just been created.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Profile now appears in Concur. Takes about 1-2 business days from when the profile appears in ARC for it to appear in Concur.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "597": {
    "question": "I added two more lines to the Itemization tab for amounts over the threshold and adjusted the original lines to $350. Is this correct?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "On Itemization tab added two more lines for the amounts over the threshold, then adjusted amounts on the original lines to $350.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "239": {
    "question": "I am Dr. Moise Desvarieux, a faculty member in Epidemiology. I purchased airline tickets through World Travel in June and September 2022. The charges have not been reconciled, and I've been receiving notices. I need assistance resolving this issue. Do I need to be designated as a delegate in Concur to proceed?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The alerts on the two reports that Dr. Desvarieux created will go away when he submits the reports. You cannot submit the reports as his delegate, he must do this step.\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "145": {
    "question": "I am Sonali Ragan, a faculty member, and I need assistance with reimbursement for sr2345. I have a CNR vendor profile and can access Concur. Can you help me?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Has a CNR vendor profile and access to login to Concur.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "203": {
    "question": "I am a GRA and need access to Concur to submit a reimbursement request for a conference. Can you assist with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Needs to be opted in by DAF to have concur access and will discuss with supervisor. Reopen or submit new ticket if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "195": {
    "question": "I am a retiree paying for my own hotel and would like the Columbia rates. Where can I find this information?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Here is the website for visitors and personal travel:\nhttps://www.worldtravelinc.com/columbia.visitors.portal",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "281": {
    "question": "I am a student affiliate and I am unable to access Concur for reimbursement. I am also unable to add as a non-profiled payee.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Students concur access is inactivated every time the semester ends. Please reach out to the DA to have student opted in again for access",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "85": {
    "question": "I am a student in the Urban Design program. I traveled to Pennsylvania for my studio class two weeks ago and am expecting a refund check to cover my travel and lodging fees. I've recently updated my permanent address in my SSOL account to my current address in New York, and I hope the check can be sent there. Could you help me with the status of this refund? Best regards, Maissa Eid.",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Dear Customer, \n\nWe have not heard back from you regarding your Service Now Incident. Because several days have passed, the Service Center has marked the incident as resolved. If you do not feel this issue was resolved, please re-open this incident and provide the required information.\n \nThank You\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1230": {
    "question": "I am a student named Giulia Crosio (Uni: GC2956) and I need access to Concur for Vendor Number: CNR0088338.",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "486": {
    "question": "I am an incoming assistant professor at DBMI and I am having trouble logging into Concur. I encountered an error and would appreciate any help.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Concur is available for active employees with active PAC profile",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "302": {
    "question": "I am arranging a hotel reservation for a visitor between 12/1-12/7, but the Warwick Hotel is blacked out on 12/4. Can I use my corporate card to book the stay and have the guest pay the difference for the night that is over the agreed rate, and how do I reconcile that?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Spoke with CU Account Manager at Warwick and opened up all nights of the stay at the CU preferred rate. No further action required on the part of the card team.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "429": {
    "question": "I am currently unable to access Concur to submit reimbursement for my trip expenses with the NCDP at Columbia. I was able to access it successfully last year for a similar trip, but now I'm encountering difficulties. Can you help?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Duplicate of  INC2686137",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "3": {
    "question": "I am encountering an error when logging into CONCUR. I have attached a photo of the error message. Can you help me resolve this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "concur is available for those who receive payroll check from Columbia University, If you are an employee of NYP please reach out to Raquel Marin , rm2698@columbia.edu who can assist with affiliate concur access\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "52": {
    "question": "I am encountering an issue where my Concur report user is marked as inactive.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "User shows as PAC terminated in ARC as of 09/16/24. Reimbursement will be processed via voucher. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "37": {
    "question": "I am experiencing a Concur Login Error. What can I do to resolve this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "To get access to login to Concur as an affiliate you would need to apply for Concur Temporary Access on the Financial Systems Security Application. This job aid has the instructions on how to do this: https://www.finance.columbia.edu/sites/default/files/content/Training%20Documents/Travel%20and%20Expense/Job_Aid_Concur_Affiliates_FSSA.pdf\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1114": {
    "question": "I am having issues booking a flight through Concur as it is very slow, but the information eventually came up.",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Very slow but the information eventually came up.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "620": {
    "question": "I am having technical issues approving an expense report in Concur. It is not allowing me to move forward without inserting someone else. It was approved by a financial approver, but it keeps asking to add additional approvers. We do not have additional approval. Please see the attached file (screenshots). Thank you.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "per our conversation, Michelle will recall the report and send to Amanda as initial Reviewer or Janet. once Amanda or Janet approves, Concur will route to Kristina for Financial approval.\nThank you.\n-Kin",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "488": {
    "question": "I am inquiring about the payment of $2,450.77 for the NAMDC Meeting-UMDF Conference in June 2024.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Eileen helped Iris to resolve issue.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "627": {
    "question": "I am looking for a comparison flight for my past travel. Can anyone assist with that?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The comparison quotes are required at the time of booking. In rare circumstances, where this does not take place- the only comparison or documentation that can be provided is to look at the same date range for future dates since there is no way to look back in the airline reservation system. AP needs this documentation for audit requirements.\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "613": {
    "question": "I am looking for information about accessing the Concur system as support staff. Could you provide me with the necessary details?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "DAF has the capability to opt in support staff for concur travel access",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1201": {
    "question": "I am looking for information on the Concur workflow for Department 7542502. Does anyone have insights into this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "See attached file for Security Roles for dept 7542502 .",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1081": {
    "question": "I am looking into my Concur profile aq2261. Can you provide details or assistance?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Give us a call if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "84": {
    "question": "I am looking to find out about reimbursing an alcoholic beverage that I included on a meal expense. Can you provide information on how to go about this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "It is up  to  departments discretion to reimburse or not to reimburse for alcoholic beverage on an expense report",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "493": {
    "question": "I am looking to opt-in as a student in Concur with UNI GC2956.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "In order to opt-in a student non-employee to have access to Concur Travel and Expense or Expense only, a Service Now Incident is required from the department's DAF or SBO. The incident should contain the student's name, UNI, and Vendor Number and must indicate which Concur module is requested: \n\nTravel \u2013 access to book Air and/or Rail to be charged on the Columbia Air/Rail Central Pay. Hotel and car rentals can be reserved as well.\nExpense \u2013 access to create and submit expense reports to reconcile travel and/or business expenses charged on the Columbia Air/Rail Central Pay or for reimbursement of out of pocket expenses. This includes access to the Concur Request module to request pre-trip approval.\nCentral Accounts Payable Process \nUpon receipt of the incident, Accounts Payable (AP) will verify the request was submitted by the department's DAF or SBO, verify the student's name, UNI, and vendor number matches the student non-employee profile in Accounting and Reporting at Columbia (ARC). AP will also verify the incident specifies which Concur module is being requested for access for the student non-employee.\n\nAP will grant access to Concur and mark the incident as resolved, which sends an email to the DAF or SBO signifying that access to Concur will be provided within 24 hours for the student non-employee. \n\nAP will grant access to Concur and mark the incident as resolved which sends an email to the DAF or SBO signifying that access to Concur will be provided within 24 hours.\n\nStudents should refer to the Travel and Expense Portal Student sectoin for regarding Concur Travel and Expense.\n\nhttps://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/content/getting-started",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "558": {
    "question": "I am looking to process a payment to a translator. Can you help me with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Faculty will pay for the services and request reimbursment via Concur",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "131": {
    "question": "I am not able to select a reviewer or an approver in Concur for RAF2002. Can you please advise on this issue?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Natalia,\nThe concur approval workflow is designed in a way that expense reports route to a Supervisor if there is an assigned supervisor in PAC by skipping the initial reviewer. KATRINA ARMSTRONG is the assigned supervisor for uni RAF2002. For Katrina to be able to approve the expense report she must be opted in concur for supervisor approver and complete the assigned training.\njob aid is attached how to opt in a supervisor. Once she sis opted in a required training will be assigned to her\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1004": {
    "question": "I am not receiving emails as a delegate for UNI: msc129. Can you look into this issue?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Provided individuals who did not check off for the delegate to receive emails. md3605 does have this checked off so Michael should get emails regarding her expense reports.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "139": {
    "question": "I am processing a check request for supplier 0000139615 associated with Afiya, Desiree Walker, who prefers transactions in the company name. It\u2019s a travel reimbursement. Can you please activate this supplier for me, or do I need to go through Payment Works? Thank you!",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Reimbursement can not be processed for a company only to individuals",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "482": {
    "question": "I am processing a reimbursement for a lab member, Alessandra Franceschini from the Christine Denny Lab, and I noticed the chart-string for her grant is not populating. Can you help me add it?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Denny,\nConcur only carries projects with valid fiscal year budget and project PG009771 doesn't have a valid budget both on the department and sponsored projects side\nPlease reach out to your departments Administrator to have budhet enterd\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1149": {
    "question": "I am reaching out about a CONCUR issue regarding my expenses. Can you provide assistance?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Disregard per user request",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "224": {
    "question": "I am reaching out regarding the unresolved issue of INC2703446. I've noticed that student access in Concur gets inactivated at the end of each semester. Can you help me get back in touch with the DA to restore access? Elizabeth Ferrari indicated that my Concur vendor profile (CNR0139722) shows it as 'Active', but we still don't have access in social work. Please advise me on what to do next.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The CNR for Tejaswi does populate in Concur for the non-profile payee report (see attached). After you select Non-profiled payee as the report type, further down on the page two fields for vendor type and vendor ID will appear. If you find that nothing populates when entering the vendor ID in the vendor name field, you should change filter for that field to \"either\" by clicking on the down arrow next to the funnel icon. Then enter CNR or vendor ID, it should then populate if the vendor ID is active. If it does not please go back to the vendor type and make sure that the correct type was selected. Continue to fill out the rest of the report and submit.\nPlease note: Students are not given default access to transact on their own in Concur. If you would like Tejaswi to submit their own or others reports, please have your DAF opt them per the instructions on the previous INC.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "702": {
    "question": "I am receiving a \"Failed to validate\" error message when trying to log into Concur. The error code is c95aebe1d4be026ab7bd3e899d750208. Can you help me solve this issue?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Able to login after clearing cache.",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "66": {
    "question": "I am reconciling my Corporate Card for a hotel advance deposit, but I cannot submit my report before the trip end date. Also, I have a question about meal threshold overages. Can someone assist me?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Please segregate the amount over the meal threshold.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "544": {
    "question": "I am requesting access to itinerary information from someone who has transferred departments. Can anyone assist with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hi Catherine,\nPlease email me directly (kc2802@columbia.edu) if you have other questions regarding this matter.\nThank you.\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "462": {
    "question": "I am requesting guidance on filing a Concur reimbursement for a planned Columbia trip in October, since payment was made in July and the system won\u2019t let me submit it. How should I address this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "A traveler can be reimbursed in advance of a flight for an airline ticket, conference registration or membership fee. Lodging can not be reimbursed before the end of the trip\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "615": {
    "question": "I am seeing a warning that exceeds the threshold on the report entered by ad3270. However, the person who entered the report is not seeing the warning, but Carol, the approver, is. Can you help clarify this situation?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Issue in Concur where it adds together non-profiled payee expenses on the same day. Carol will enter the comment saying it's not actually over the threshold.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "444": {
    "question": "I am submitting a reimbursement for Dr. Delivette Castor who paid for hotel invoices for four South African visitors. I'm receiving alerts that the daily rate exceeds the threshold. Can we have these alerts removed? The report number is HC1GV7.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Assisted user with clearing of red alerts on expense report\n report number is HC1GV7.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "477": {
    "question": "I am trying to access Vendor Id 0000269993, but it is not available through Concur.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Wire payments can not be processed through concur. Please process  this through ARC on a check request",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "608": {
    "question": "I am trying to find information regarding vendor id 0000205534.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Vendor has to be invited to register through PW for any updates",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "504": {
    "question": "I am trying to prepare an expense report in Concur, but I can't edit the number of attendees for a 10+ Attendee event. This issue is preventing me from submitting my report, which has the number 6JR6UD.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Unfortunately, you cannot make any edits as you \"Submitted\" the expense, corresponding screenshot below. As such, you must click on the \"Recall Report\" button (corresponding screenshot below) in order to make the necessary edits and resubmit it. Thank you. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "494": {
    "question": "I am trying to process my travel reimbursement for a conference I attended in June 2024. I just switched my Columbia ID from contractor to student status, which may be causing an error with logging into Concur for the first time. Could you please help me?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Reopen or submit new ticket if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "53": {
    "question": "I am trying to reconcile booking fees that are over 365 days old and need help.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The report type should be updated to \"Travel Expense\" and Travel Date to the current date. (like 10/24/24)",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "408": {
    "question": "I am trying to reimburse Mathieu Lecarpentier for travel expenses due to his visit to the university in February 2024, but his supplier ID does not appear in Concur. I've selected the correct report type (Cu Non-Profiled Payee) and vendor type (outside party), but I'm having no luck. Can you please advise?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Foreign vendor must submit in ARC. Reopen or submit new ticket if any additional questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "286": {
    "question": "I am trying to submit a Concur report, but my manager, Cody Vermillion, is not showing up as an approver option. Cody confirms he approves other reports in Concur. Can you please advise? Thank you.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "CODY VERMILLION has not taken the concur supervisor training yet and wouldn't be able to approve concur expenses . Have the Department Administrator or Senior business Officer Opt- in Codi for Supervisor Concur Approval role and the appropriate training will be assigned .Once the training is completed Codi would be able to approve expenses\nJob aid is attached in case needed\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "79": {
    "question": "I am trying to submit an expense report for airfare charged to Columbia/Central Air. Can you help me with this process?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Charges paid by the Columbia/Central Air are not reimbursable to the payee as the payee didn't pay for it",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1365": {
    "question": "I am unable to access Concur. Can you help me with this issue?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Directed to  Raquel Marin\nAVP,Int Cntrls Compl,Dep Cntlr\n rm2698@cumc.columbia.edu\nfor temp. concur access",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "562": {
    "question": "I am unable to access Concur; when I try to log in, it says \"Sorry, something went wrong\". My ID is 7011471559fcd5679da06023ed7affea. Can you help me regain access as I need to request reimbursement promptly? Thank you!",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "FSSA -Financial System Security Application must be completed to get Concur access. Reopen ticket or submit new one if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "287": {
    "question": "I am unable to locate the following vendor in Concur. The vendor number assigned is 0000269388. The company legal name is Spinelli, Antonino, and the DBA is Antonino Spinelli. Can you help me with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "supplier ID 0000269388 is set up to receive payments by wire and wire payments can not be processed through concur\nExpense report has to be submitted on a check request through ARC\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "827": {
    "question": "I am unable to login.",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "no response",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "210": {
    "question": "I am unable to submit my report and need help resolving this issue.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The report must be submitted by the payee. As discussed, you should enter a justification on the segregated itemization line for the airfare. \nThanks. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "435": {
    "question": "I am unable to upload a receipt for Courtney Chan. She has made me her delegate to prepare her expense report, but I don't see an option to upload her receipt. This is a problem only with her. Can you help with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "If you are uploading a report level supporting document ie, conference flyer or email, please select the manage receipts dropdown and chose manage attachment, upload the document here.\nIf you are trying to upload a receipt for an expense, you must add the expense line. After you click add expense and choose a category, the new expense detail page will appear and you will see a receipt box on the right where you can add the receipt.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "833": {
    "question": "I am unclear about what I need to complete a report for someone. I will call back once I have an idea of what I need.",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "User will call back she said once she has an idea what she is needs.User",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "344": {
    "question": "I am using Concur for the first time to purchase an airline ticket for Martin Uribe, who has a visual impairment. How can I add this information to ensure he receives the assistance needed for travel? Also, can I purchase an Economy Plus ticket for flights over 5 hours? Thank you!",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Please reopen ticket or submit a new one if any additional questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "469": {
    "question": "I am working on reconciling my air travel and lodging expenses in Concur. Does anyone have tips or steps I should follow?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "For Air/Rail booked through Concur, you can reconcile by creating an Report and may submit before the trip end date. \nFor Hotel booked with Corporate Card, you can create the report to reconcile but cannot submit until trip end date.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "556": {
    "question": "I am working on submitting Lailer Maher's expense report (6V0RS9), but she needs to complete the missing receipt declaration and can't attach the form. Can you advise me on how to proceed? Thank you.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Nekeia,\nReceipts must be provided for all air, rail, lodging, and rental car expenses. For all other expense types, receipts must be provided if the expense is equal to or in excess of $50. Otherwise, Payee Justification and Financial Approval is required and a Missing Receipt Affidavit must be completed. In this case I see the expense is only for $25.00 and receipt is not required but need to attach the proof of payment\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "460": {
    "question": "I am writing to follow up on a refund for a flight that does not appear on the Concur profile for one of our faculty members after a last-minute change. The original flight locator is SDBYQL and the new one is KDMZVO. Can you help?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "All posted transactions including credits need to b reconciled",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1339": {
    "question": "I approved an expense report that has not shown up in my manager's approval queue. The audit trail has an unusual note about athletics compliance. Can someone help clarify this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Confirmed approval routing for the report.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "220": {
    "question": "I assume Caroline Arout (CNR0003987) has access to Concur? I wanted to double check with you if that is the case.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Caroline Arout, CNR0003987 has access to concur",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "508": {
    "question": "I believe I'm ready to submit my report for reimbursement of ticket fees for a United Nations tour. I've set up my profile, created the report, included attendees, and attached the UN receipt. Is there anything else I need to do before I submit the report?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "We are not trained to audit these reports, but I took a quick look and it looks good to submit. If edits are required either your department or the AP auditor will send it back and let you know what is missing.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "546": {
    "question": "I booked a block of hotel rooms and a conference room for a site visit in April. What do I need to do next?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Christine will put the expense under Group Travel and itemize to Hotel Advanced Deposit.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "677": {
    "question": "I booked a flight for a conference via Concur and it's showing as booked, but I'm unsure how to match the expense to a chart string. How will the charges for this trip be processed?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "You have to wait until it shows up in the available expenses, Once it's there, you'll have the option to move it to your expense report.\nHere is a video tutorial for when it does appear: https://www.finance.columbia.edu/content/reconciling-corporate-card-and-columbia-airrail-central-pay-transactions-concur\nLet me know if you have any questions.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "121": {
    "question": "I booked a train fare through Concur. When will this expense appear under my Concur profile so I can add it to my expense report and submit it for approval?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The expense will appear under your Concur profile under Available Expenses. At that point you will add this expense to an expense report and enter the required information, submit for approval, etc.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "142": {
    "question": "I booked a trip through Concur that I left on 10/9, but it is not showing up as an available expense yet. Can you help me with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Expense was not charge to BTA. it was charged to card ending in 5258.\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "587": {
    "question": "I can pull up Jiayao Wang (jw3514) in Concur. Is there something wrong with his status in the system or do I need him to make me a delegate?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Jiayao Wang has access to concur and he can submit his own expense report",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "15": {
    "question": "I can't access Concur.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "There is nothing flagged on your profile. You might need to clear your cache. Please follow these steps:\nClear cache, follow the complete instructions here: https://www.cuit.columbia.edu/clear-cache\nLog into concur here: https://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/\nUse only your uni (do not include the @columbia.edu) and password.\nLet me know if that works.\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "401": {
    "question": "I can't approve a faculty report in Concur. What should I do?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hi Manidipa\nYou cannot approve Lambert's report in Lambert's account, you need to log into your own account to approve Lambert's report as Concur have routed the report to your account.\n\n-Kin",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "431": {
    "question": "I can't book travel in Concur. Can you help me with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hi Jessica,\nI have updated and removed all the special characters on Veronica's travel profile settings. Please have her try booking again.\nemail me if she continue to experience difficulties.\nThank you.\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "43": {
    "question": "I can't find Nicholas Lemann (nl2124) as the initial reviewer for my expense reports. Tanya Motley from Finance confirmed that he's listed as an initial reviewer for my department (5410217). Could you help me add him as my initial reviewer?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Hi Jaime,\nNicholas is not a initial reviewer. please see email response.\nThank you.\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "252": {
    "question": "I can't find UNI JBB2194 JOHN BISHOP CNR0130950 Student in Concur for NPP expense. Can anyone help?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Hi Raquel,\nProfile is there. please see screen capture.\nThank you.\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "395": {
    "question": "I can't find a way to notify the approver of my expense report through Concur since it's still pending Francine's approval.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Not a way to do this through Concur. Pending Francine's approval.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "89": {
    "question": "I can't find my hotel in Concur. What should I do?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Please type other in the hotel name field and enter the name of the hotel in the comments/justification box.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "682": {
    "question": "I can't find my hotel in the Concur dropdown. Can someone help me with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "You can type the word other in the vendor field and select it when it comes up in the drop down, then put the name of the hotel in the comments/justification section. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "454": {
    "question": "I can't log into Concur with her UNI. Even though the user's access is active, we need to reset her UNI password. How can I do that?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Please contact CUIT at 212-854-1919 to request to resent your UNI password.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1052": {
    "question": "I can't log into Concur. I'm getting an error message, and when I used the chat feature to find out why, it mentioned that the type of error might be due to my PAC affiliation being either not enabled or expired. I'm not sure what that means, but I need to submit a pre-trip request and would appreciate any help. Thank you!",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Reopen or submit new ticket if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "69": {
    "question": "I can't seem to find the expense category for airfare in Concur.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Recapping our conversation. \nThe airfare expense category can be found only under the Travel expense report type. We updated this in the report header section. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "593": {
    "question": "I can't submit Request ID: 4TTD. Can someone help me with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Report was submitted. Give us a call if any additional questions. Thank you, Dralca",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "473": {
    "question": "I cannot access Concur because I received an email stating that my account is inactive, and now I cannot issue requests for reimbursement.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Ubaldo,\nYour current ARC status indicates that you were an employee. When did you become a student?\nConcur is not automatically available for students. In order for you to get access to concur your schools Department Administrator has to submit a request through the service CatLog and also to do that you must have registered and have active profile in SSOL with a local US mailing address. Till then your profile in ARC is not going to be active\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "366": {
    "question": "I cannot access Concur to log in due to the \"Zero Record\" from being a retiree. Can you discuss the option of getting temporary Concur access as an affiliate or if I should just pay out-of-pocket and get reimbursed?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "No access to login to Concur due to the \"Zero Record\" being retiree. Discussed option of getting temporary Concur access as an affiliate or paying-out-of-pocket and getting reimbursed. For any reimbursements an Outside Party vendor profile will be needed.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "266": {
    "question": "I cannot log back into Concur because the password reset function is not sending me an email. What can I do?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Her current PAC profile shows a termination date of 06/30/2024. Please have her contact her HR representative to discuss and correct. The PAC profile is what governs the concur access for employees. If the records is not active in PAC, their concur access will not be active",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "492": {
    "question": "I cannot log into Concur even though I received an email confirming my username as cgr2126@columbia.edu.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hi Catherine,\nyour status classification is \"Student Employee\", your Concur access need to be opted-in by your departmental DAF. Please contact your supervisor and find out who has that role. Also see page 4 of the attached PDF for more details regarding opt-in for Student Employees.   \n\nThank you.\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "54": {
    "question": "I cannot log into Concur for reimbursement; I keep getting an error message with the following code: 0ecb3d91dfeec88dd31ac8c00f1c6775.",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "User is directed to Raquel Marin (rm2698@columbia.edu)  for affiliate concur access",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1307": {
    "question": "I cannot select the Missing Receipt Affidavit in Concur. Can you help me resolve this issue?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Please remove all documents uploaded if claiming no receipts.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "178": {
    "question": "I cannot set up a delegate to submit my report; this must be done by me, the payee.",
    "out-of-scope": "irrelevant question",
    "human_answer": "Cannot set up a delegate to actually submit the report, this must be done by the payee.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "123": {
    "question": "I cannot submit the expense for UNI SMT2214 because it doesn't have a vendor profile in ARC. What should I do next?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "UNI SMT2214 does not have a vendor profile in ARC.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "705": {
    "question": "I cleared my browser cache and closed the browser, and now it\u2019s working. Can you confirm if there\u2019s anything else I should do to ensure my access stays clear of issues?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Cleared browser cache, closed browser, reopened and now working.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "662": {
    "question": "I created a report for a previous student to receive per diem meals from June 30th to September 2nd. Now, another student is requesting per diem meals for similar dates, but Concur won\u2019t let me process it because of the previous report. What should I do?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Samantha,\nIf you receive the overlapping issue you need to do the per diem manual calculation instead of using the itinerary option\nThe last two pages shows how to do that\n\nhttps://www.finance.columbia.edu/sites/default/files/content/Training%20Documents/Concur/Job%20Aids/Job_Aid_Concur_Per_Diem.pdf\nYou can use the expense type Per Diem (Manual Calculation) for these meals.\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "282": {
    "question": "I created a vendor in Vendor Management, but I am unable to find Yunung Lee as a non-profiled outside party in Concur with the ID 0000268064.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Wire payments can not be processed in concur.\nHave expense reimbursement processed in ARC on a check request",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "399": {
    "question": "I created an expense report for lam2048 as a delegate. However, when I try to approve it, it switches me back to acting as lam2048. Even after deleting the report several times and clearing my browser cache, I still can't approve it. What can I do?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Grace has already approved the report. it is pending Jennifer's approval.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "29": {
    "question": "I declared a missing receipt for airline fees related to extra baggage after I removed the proof of payment document from the expense. What else do I need to do?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Removed the proof of payment document from the expense, then able to do the missing receipt declaration for this item.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "663": {
    "question": "I deposited checks from two staff members who made personal/non-reimbursable charges on their corporate cards into our accounts. These were reconciled in Concur as 'personal/non-reimbursable' and sent for approval. Now, when the reports post, they show both an expense and a credit, separate from the credit of the check written to reimburse the University. Should these check payments go to a different account to avoid confusion?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hi Ryan,\nAs per Tier2's suggestion, please submit journal voucher crediting dept expense and debit the account the check was deposited to.\nThank you.\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "290": {
    "question": "I did not receive my reimbursement issued on 7/2/24 via check. I have now added ACH to my SSOL, but I do not see it reflected in Concur. How can I reissue this payment via ACH?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Nathalie ,\nI don't see ACH location under the profile. When was this done? usually it takes 48 hrs for the change to integrate to ARC.\nOnce the ACH information is reflected in ARC ,you just have to submit a stop payment request and ask that the payment be reissued via ACH .\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "207": {
    "question": "I don't have access to Concur Travel and need help with this issue.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Advised to reach out to Raquel Marin to ask to have the individual opted in to Concur travel.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "276": {
    "question": "I entered an expense report as a delegate for dl3365. Can someone confirm that it has been processed correctly?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Payee must submit the report when you create it as the delegate. Payee can select the delegate as the Initial Reviewer.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "427": {
    "question": "I finished all my classes for the summer semester and am not registering for fall. Shouldn't my profile remain active for up to 45 days from the last day of class? The department needs to process a reimbursement.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hi Jeehyun,\nSince the issue will be handle in payment works, i will close this incident.\nThank you.\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127 ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "535": {
    "question": "I found a link that may provide more information about the Travel Arranger role in Concur. Can you direct me to that link?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "You may go to the link below for more information.\n\nhttps://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/content/getting-started#\n\nSubmit a Financial Systems Security Application (FSSA) in Service Now.  Select Concur Travel Arranger in section 2.1.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "268": {
    "question": "I found some information about hours of operation for travel services through WTI. Can you provide guidance on how to get help with Concur travel bookings?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hours of Operation\nTravel services through WTI are available 24/7/365 by calling 1-855-961-0313.\n\nColumbia designated Travel Counselors are available during regular business hours from  8:00 a.m. - 8:00 p.m. ET, Monday through Friday (excluding holidays).\n\nPlease note: After regular business hours and on weekends and holidays, travel services are available through WTI's Emergency Service Center.  Travelers and Travel Arrangers must have their Employee ID number available to provide to the WTI Travel Counselor.\n\nTravel Counseling\nTo speak with a Columbia University designated Travel Counselor, please call: 1-855-961-0313\n\nIf calling from outside the United States please call: 1-484-948-2514\n\nRoutine queries may be emailed to a Columbia University designated Travel Counselor. If your query is time sensitive or if you require immediate assistance, please call a Travel Counselor at 1-855-961-0313 \n\nSupport\nFor navigational support with the Columbia University Concur Travel Online Booking Tool please call: 1-800-221-4730, Monday - Friday 8:00 a.m. - 8:00 p.m. ET\n\nRequest assistance via email with the Concur Travel Online Booking Tool.\n\nFor more information please visit https://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/content/wo",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "348": {
    "question": "I had an expense report returned. Can someone please advise on who this should be sent to? Thank you, Krystina.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Provided instructions to update the School/Division/Sub-Division and Admin Dept to the department that is being charged.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "458": {
    "question": "I had to book a hotel reservation using my corporate card as direct payment since the only hotel that fit our needs was not on Concur. What is the reconciliation process for this type of payment?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The charge will show up in our concur available expenses in 3-5 business days, at which point you should reconcile like you would any expense. Please be sure to upload the supporting documentation.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "189": {
    "question": "I have a Concur report for Trip to Athens (UNI SM4680) that has a duplicate Corporate Charge for $30.02. How should I proceed with reconciling both items? Should I provide justification for one of the disputed charges as a duplicate?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "UNI SM4680 concor report Trip to Athens: Pt.2 $958.52 has duplicate Corporate Charge for $30.02.  Advised to reconcile both items and put justification on one that charges are disputed as duplicate.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "676": {
    "question": "I have a Concur report that I need to review; it was returned because the itemizations don't match those on the folio. The preparer insists that the itemizations were entered correctly. Can I approve this report as it currently stands? Please advise. Thanks!",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Please let preparer know the lines need to be adjusted to show the actual nightly rate of the hotel, taxes and parking must be all separated. Any questions please reopen or submit new ticket. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "6": {
    "question": "I have a Concur report to review for Fuller William and wanted to double check: he went to a conference for one day (9-5). Is this considered a travel or business expense? Thank you.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Olga,\nIf there is no overnight stay then it is a business expense. For travel expense there should be an overnight stay outside of the home state\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "294": {
    "question": "I have a Concur transaction that is stuck and will not accept SBO approver names or UNIs, which is preventing it from being advanced for approval. The employee is Jianwen Que, and the report date is 8/7/24 for $446.35. Can you help?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Report is now pending Barbara Rosenberg's approval.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "564": {
    "question": "I have a Missing Receipt Declaration that can only be completed by the payee and not the delegate. It should appear for expenses over $50 without documents attached, but I\u2019m uncertain what to do. Can you help?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Can only be completed by the payee, not the delegate. Will only appear for expenses over $50 (not including air, rail, lodging or car rental) that have no supporting documents attached.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "331": {
    "question": "I have a Travel Expense charged through Concur. Is there anything I need to be aware of?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Travel booked through concur will post as available expense  in concur under users profile and can be moved to expense page for reconciling",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "552": {
    "question": "I have a UNI of ey2112. I\u2019m encountering two issues: 1. I received a flight credit for cancelled flights, but I understand that per policy, I'm not reimbursed for credits from personal travel related to business tickets. Should I remove the personal credit part and leave the business credit amount with an explanation for AP to review? 2. The FA is having trouble selecting an SBO. Can I get help with the instructions on how to select it, and if there's still a problem, can they provide a screenshot?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "1. Flight returned regarding credits for cancelled flights. \nPer the Travel Expense policy \"Travelers will not be reimbursed for credits issued by an airline from personal travel used to purchase airline tickets for business travel.\"\nRecommended removing the credit portion that was for a personal flight and leaving the amount that was a credit for a business trip, with an explanation. AP will review and return if necessary.\n\n2. FA is having trouble selecting an SBO. \nHere is the tip with instructions on how to select the SBO. If the approver is still having problems after following these instructions if he can attach a screenshot of the problem:\nhttps://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/news/how-do-i-update-approval-flow-senior-business-officer",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "137": {
    "question": "I have a corporate card charge issue with a hotel that was charged $509.03, but they mistakenly charged for parking twice on 9/22 and later credited the amount back. The actual charge should be $482.03, but I can't change the amount in Concur because it is grayed out, and the itemizations won\u2019t balance. Can you advise me on how to resolve this?",
    "out-of-scope": "other",
    "human_answer": "Good morning Maya,\nThe original expense cannot be change, you have to note duplicate parking portion as an error. i see that there's a credit of -$27 dollars is also on the report, that will offset your total and should balance your erroneous charge.\nThank you.\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "404": {
    "question": "I have a general question about Concur.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Concur question for breakfast expense",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "514": {
    "question": "I have a general question about travel. Can you help me with that?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Basic economy- seat fee is not listed as a non-reimbursable. Department will also look into booking trip via Concur",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "445": {
    "question": "I have a graduate student staying in Berlin for rental from October to December for research purposes. What steps do I need to follow?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Renting a place for long term research activity is reimbursable as long as the grant allows",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "506": {
    "question": "I have a meal charged by the hotel for 4, but I only have the total charged and not an itemized bill. What should I do?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Advised to enter as group meal and note in the details that cannot obtain itemized receipt from the hotel and for food only for 4 people.  Submit for AP's review and approval.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "317": {
    "question": "I have a payee, CNR0088427 (MA4177, MATIAS ALVO), who is unable to submit reports unless they attach a request in Concur first. Two different admins have tried to prepare a report for them as a non-profiled payee, and one could do it while the other couldn't. Can someone explain why that might be happening? Also, they have a report pending submission but can't proceed due to this request issue. What can we do?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Provided options. Jamie will ask SBO to put in a ticket to have the student opted-out.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "595": {
    "question": "I have a problem with Report Key: 294401; it was paid to the wrong vendor. Can someone assist me in resolving this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Kimberly submitted a stop payment for the check and will enter a new expense report for the correct vendor.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "433": {
    "question": "I have a question about Concur access. Can you assist?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Please reach out to \nRaquel Marin\n rm2698@cumc.columbia.edu",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "513": {
    "question": "I have a question about a Concur transaction date related to my 2024 ICML report id 6E4A9E1F6793495BB857. Should I put 6/19 or 6/20 as the date for airfare expenses? The charges are complicated because they were booked through a travel agency in China and there\u2019s a 12-hour time difference. The actual charge was dated 6/19 at 10:45 PM (US time) and 6/20 at 10:45 AM (China time).",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "You should the the date from the credit card statement that you uploaded in Concur, see below. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "144": {
    "question": "I have a question about a premium economy fare ticket and its reimbursement process.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The difference between premium economy and basic economy fare needs to be segregated",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "170": {
    "question": "I have a question about a report in Concur.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Additional charges for airfare will need to go under airline fees. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "12": {
    "question": "I have a question about a student reimbursement. A student purchased a roundtrip non-refundable ticket for the holidays but needs to change his flight for a conference that begins on January 23rd and costs about $300 to change. Can he request reimbursement for those airline fees?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Changes in airfare are an allowable expense as long as it is for university business. Reopen or submit new ticket if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "72": {
    "question": "I have a question about adding a finance approver in Concur. Mirela Trofin in Medicine is the finance approver and Susanne Sullivan is the DA, but I'm unsure of which other finance approver I should input in the field provided. I've attached a screenshot for reference.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Provided the additional financial approvers in the department. Reopen or submit a new ticket if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "46": {
    "question": "I have a question about catering expenses for events. How do I handle that in Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "use Expense type  Entertainment\nReport purpose  Meetings & events",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "548": {
    "question": "I have a question about how to allocate expenses for Dr. Gliklich, who has made me his delegate for entering expenses on his behalf. Can someone provide guidance on this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Please see this tip for information on itemizing a business class trip:\nhttps://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/news/how-do-i-itemize-business-class-flight ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "534": {
    "question": "I have a question about making a hotel booking through Concur. Can you assist me?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Travel policy can be found here https://universitypolicies.columbia.edu/content/travel-expense-policy. Any additional questions give us a call or reopen ticket. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "464": {
    "question": "I have a question about the Concur report bf2187. Can someone help me with the approval workflow?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Please recall reports. Once Josh can confirm the financial approver is Jacqueline Jenkins you can resubmit. Give us a call if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "166": {
    "question": "I have a question about the Concur report reimbursement process. Can you provide more details?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Please submit reimbursement via concur  for the expenses on your credit card. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "380": {
    "question": "I have a question about the approval workflow.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Discussed with James via phone. The report was being returned due to issues with the agenda/conference flyer. James is an Initial Reviewer for department 5711203 and Kathleen approved the report as the Financial Approver. At this time do not see any issues with the workflow.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "403": {
    "question": "I have a question about the reimbursement for my drupal training ticket.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "You didn't get back to me with information I requested to assist you with this. The service center has now closed this ticket. If you need further assistance please feel free to reopen this ticket or submit a new one",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1208": {
    "question": "I have a question about travel booking.",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Directed to  Columbia University designated Travel Counselor at World Travel, Inc. (WTI) at 1-855-961-0313.                         ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "4": {
    "question": "I have a question about updating my payment method to ACH so I can receive ACH direct deposit for my Concur reimbursement. Where can I make this change? Is there a portal?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Students can update their payment method in SSOL",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "73": {
    "question": "I have a question regarding Concur reimbursement that I need help with.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Reimbursement can be submitted every time there is a payment for the course. Please provide all the necessary information on the report. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "451": {
    "question": "I have a question regarding a booking fee that was charged to my card, can someone help me with that?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hi Getachew,\nCharges on the BTA account can be reconcile independent of each other. Reconciling the Agent Fee on a different expense report is not an issue, Concur will automatically allocation the charge to the Columbia BTA account without additional action.\nIn responses to your request to move the agent fee to your credit card is not a normal process and WTI would most will not do it, as they have to credit the BTA account, you will still have to reconcile the existing agent fee plus the WTI credit in another expense report to offset each other.\n\nPlease add the Agent Fee to a new report by itself and submit it into workflow for processing.\n\nThank you.\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "643": {
    "question": "I have a question regarding a hotel charge in my Concur expense report. Can someone assist me with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Payee has to check in with own credit card and receipt (folio() will be provided upon check out .This should be uploaded in concur when submitting reimbursement request",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "541": {
    "question": "I have a question regarding a meal that went over the threshold. What should I do?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Segregate the over threshold portion under meal segregated. Any questions give us a call. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1119": {
    "question": "I have a question regarding concur access for cp3210.",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Concur access is inactive.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "484": {
    "question": "I have a question regarding my travel reimbursement for faculty.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "both charges on the report were BTA charges, not out of pocket.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "412": {
    "question": "I have a question regarding the Concur report NN45.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Extending Travel beyond the Minimum Days Required for Personal Reasons                                                     \nThe costs related to an earlier departure and/or later return for airfare or rail fare may be reimbursed when the total cost of the airfare or rail fare is clearly documented and demonstrated to be equal to or lower than it would have been for the dates required for business travel. Payee justification is required on the Expense Report that documents the personal days in the itinerary.\n\nThe University will not assume the cost or reimburse the cost of lodging, local transportation, meals or other costs in excess of the minimum days necessary for travel or conference attendance. If the traveler does not have a legitimate business purpose for expenses (not including air or rail fare) incurred for their extended stay, all costs charged to either the University's Business Travel Account (BTA)/Air/Rail Central Pay Account or Travel & Expense Corporate Card will need to be reimbursed to the University.  Out of pocket expenses will also not be reimbursed to the traveler.\n \n\nDocumentation Required                              \n\nIf air or rail expenses related to an earlier departure and/or later return are being reimbursed, the total cost of airfare or rail fare should be compared to the costs for traveling on the dates required for business travel. Documentation should include a price quote from either the air carrier and/ or rail carrier for the dates that would have been used if the travel was not extended. All documentation requirements for the specific expenditure type apply.\n\nhttps://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/content/policies\n\nPrice comparison for the same carrier, date (if available), fligt number/time.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "8": {
    "question": "I have a question regarding the expense for mbh2155. Can I get more information?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Aurelia,\nStudent, CNR0139341 was opted in for concur access last semester, Students concur access becomes inactive every time the semester ends and needs to be opted in once the new semester begun. Reach out to the DA to have the student opted in again\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "146": {
    "question": "I have a question regarding the security access for Concur, specifically related to UNI PEA2124. Can someone help me with that?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "UNI PEA2124 concur access - Supervisor Name\nNICHOLAS VINCENT.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "337": {
    "question": "I have a question regarding travel reimbursement. Can someone assist me with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Will need a comparison flight going from Greece to nyc. That will be the amount to reimburse. Give us a call if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "271": {
    "question": "I have a reconciling question that I need clarification on.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Will reconcile at the end of the trip in November. Give us a call if any questions, Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "9": {
    "question": "I have a reimbursement inquiry.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Purchase was done as one transaction no need to separate. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "188": {
    "question": "I have a report named Benitez-HVTN FGM for Seatlle WA totaling $2,882.72. What should I do with it?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Report reviewed and pending approval.  Report with returned cash advance.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "339": {
    "question": "I have a report number DLNYEE for the 3rd Annual GFA Conference costing $811.20. I'm getting an error message to reenter the number of attendees, but I can't find the field for the number of attendees under the Details tab. Can you help?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Report Type needs to be selected.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "35": {
    "question": "I have a tip for itemizing a meal over the threshold with alcohol. Should I put the alcohol amount under Alcohol - Segregated, then calculate the total amount of the food plus drinks that is over threshold and put this amount into Meal - Segregated? I saw an example on the website: https://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/news/how-do-i-itemize-meal-expense.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Put the alcohol amount under Alcohol -Segregated, then calculate the total amount of the food + drinks that is over threshold and put this amount into Meal - Segregated. \nThis tip has an example: https://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/news/how-do-i-itemize-meal-expense",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "630": {
    "question": "I have an active profile with CNR0017206, but I cannot access Concur. Can someone help with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "School or administrative unit DAFs will have the ability to disable access or opt-in employees individually using a Concur School / Division setup page in ARC. The exception is student non-employee access which will be granted per department request and maintained by central Accounts Payable. Department requests to opt-in Student Non-Employees can be requested by either DAF or Senior Business Officer (SBO).\n\nhttps://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/content/getting-started",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "625": {
    "question": "I have an alert on my Concur reimbursement that prevents me from moving forward. I asked my supervisor Chantel about this and she provided me with your contact information. The report is LUXTS2, for Hotel/Lodging $1,301.33. The alert I received is: \"This hotel charge is over $400/night. Please provide a justification.\" However, this hotel expense is $313.42/night, with tax totaling $11.91 ($11.92 for the last night), which is under $400. I don't understand why I received this alert message. I tried deleting the itemization and adding them again, but it remains the same alert. I have also attached the hotel receipt with each night\u2019s rate for your reference. Could you please let me know how I should resolve this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "There is a known issue in Concur, where, when you enter multiple Non-Profiled Payee expenses (or multiple corporate card expenses) for the same dates the system adds them together, because it doesn't realize they are for different people.\nThere is not a fix in place for this at this time so the resolution is to enter a comment stating that the rooms are not above threshold. The expense reports may route for SBO approval but the SBO should see the comment and approve. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "483": {
    "question": "I have an expense for ky2004, associated with Report Key: 296723.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Segregated meal is over the threshold amount and should not be personal non reimbursable expense",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "637": {
    "question": "I have an expense for mw3114 and the Report Key is 297367. Can you help me with that?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Sonia,\nLook at the attached screen shot\nThis is a corporate card expense and not payable directly to the employee.\nHe used a University corporate card for the expenses and the fund will go back to the University & not to him\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "441": {
    "question": "I have an expense for tfo2103, can you provide guidance on this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "uni    tfo2103  has both travel and expense access in concur",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "639": {
    "question": "I have an expense for uni jrs2259, and the Report Key is 300534. What do I need to do next?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Assisted with clearing red alerts on hotel itemization",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "372": {
    "question": "I have an expense report for $2500 for daycare service from 5/13/24 to 6/14/24. Can you help me with that?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Expense report for $2500 for daycare service from 5/13/24 tp 6/14/24 (per attached invoice).",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "724": {
    "question": "I have an expense report for UNI IDD2001. What should I do next?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "CU policy does not permit reimbursement for expenses incurred for non-employees\nFaculty retreat should only include Columbia Faculty",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "584": {
    "question": "I have an expense report that is more than 365 days old. What should I do?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Process reimbursement on a check request with SBO approval",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "598": {
    "question": "I have an expense that is 365 days old. What do I need to do about this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Expenses 365 days old can only be processed through ARC on a check request with SBO approval",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "92": {
    "question": "I have an inquiry on fuel receipt related to Report Number 94ER9R. Can you help me with it?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "please see email response.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "804": {
    "question": "I have an issue with supplier ID CNR0130197 being inactive. Can anyone help me with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Employee has a PAC termination date of PAC Termination Date\n09/01/2024",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "640": {
    "question": "I have an unsubmitted Concur expense for id imd2002. What should I do to resolve this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "if more time is needed, please email me directly on the day access is needed.\nThank you.\nKin ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "289": {
    "question": "I have been designated as the proxy preparer Delegate for several people in Concur, but for some individuals, I am not receiving copies of the Concur notifications like I do for others. How can I set this up so that I receive those notifications? Thank you for your assistance.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Dear Customer,\n\nWe have not heard back from you and because several days have passed , the Service Center has marked the incident as resolved. If you do not feel this issue was resolved, please re-open this incident and provide all of the required information.\nThank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "660": {
    "question": "I have created two reports for two separate hotel charges for two speakers on the same hotel and dates, but Concur flagged my report as a duplicate. How can I resolve this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Advised to enter notes in the Comments/Justification section and should be able to submit..\nCredit from hotel will  need to be reconciled separately.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "320": {
    "question": "I have international travel expenses that include foreign bank fees. How should I handle this in Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Advised to use Miscellaneous for the fees and note on the description type of bank fees.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "16": {
    "question": "I have outstanding air/rail charges for yj2812. Can someone assist me with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Yj2812 has already added these air/rail charges to a report, but it was returned requesting a flight comparison quote: \nHere are the notes from Kazue Tomiyama: Please upload comparable airfare just to engage your business - in order to justify the actual airfare is the same of cheaper than the comparable airfare (Please discuss this with the department).  Once the document is uploaded, please resubmit the report.  Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "426": {
    "question": "I have reconciled the cash advance, but I am still receiving notifications to reconcile for the MC21. Could you please clarify this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "4PDR cash advance has been closed as it has been reconciled by report  key-296695.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "102": {
    "question": "I have some questions regarding Concur; can you assist me?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "You can also find guidance here: https://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/content/travel-how-tos\n Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "517": {
    "question": "I have submitted two reimbursement requests through Concur; the first one was approved and says \"payment confirmed\" from 8/2/24, but I have not received a direct deposit with the funds. Can you discuss further on the phone? My cell is 914-406-5711. Thank you.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The address and payment method (ACH) has been updated. Please have your department request a stop pay reissue for check ref 1002282202 dated 08/07/2024. If they need this information the associated report key is 300815 and associated voucher is 06481930. When they make the request they should be sure to ask for it to be reissued as an ach/direct deposit in the comments.\n\nNOTE: You currently have a pending expense report for SAHM membership $191.00. You should probably recall the report and resubmit because if it was submitted before the address and payment method change went through in the system it will likely generate another check and send it to the wrong address.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "255": {
    "question": "I have two Concur expenses that haven't received approval. Can you let me know whom I should contact to correct any issues? I've attached a screenshot for reference. Thanks, Gesenia (ga2030)",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "please recall reports and modify financial approver list.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "407": {
    "question": "I have two travel and business expense reports that are now over 365 days and were initially submitted on time. Due to Concur's usability issues, I'm unsure if we can resubmit electronically since it indicates the end date for this trip is more than 365 days old. Can these be processed as check requests or any other way for reimbursement? Here are the report details for your review. Please let me know how to proceed.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Reimbursement will be processed in ARC with a check request. Thank you!",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "656": {
    "question": "I haven\u2019t received my reimbursement. Can someone assist?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Completed form to request payment be reissued.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "574": {
    "question": "I heard that a delegate can prepare the expense report in Concur and then click \"submit\", but isn\u2019t it true that the payee must submit the report themselves? Can you clarify this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Delegate can prepare the report and click \"submit\" but the payee must actually submit the report.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "62": {
    "question": "I heard that students do not have default access to log into Concur. How should I process a reimbursement then?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Students do not have default access to login to Concur. Process reimbursement as a non-profiled payee.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "518": {
    "question": "I just a few days ago submitted an expense report. When passing it to the next approver, I didn\u2019t see any way of selecting my supervisor Chris Dowden, either via drop-down or write-in. I think I missed something. Instead, I assigned it to Ramon Marino in our CUIT Finance department. This report number is NFUVXB, $2133.46 for the \"HELUG 2024 Conference.\" Can this report be assigned to Chris Dowden? Ramon Marino says he does not have any recourse at this point. Thanks.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "1) You could recall the expense and resubmit it, selecting the Approver you need to select\n2) Ramon Marino needs to reject the expense and send it back to you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "539": {
    "question": "I just have a short description 'Concur Travel Columbia'. Can someone help me with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Lucy,\nI see that you do not have access to concur. Are you receiving a payroll check from Columbia?\nConcur is available only to Columbia University employees.\nIf not a temporary concur access can be requested by your Departments Administrator\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "614": {
    "question": "I logged into Concur through travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu. Can you confirm my access?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Logged into Concur through travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu, Login to Concur.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "684": {
    "question": "I made a booking under the wrong name. What should I do?",
    "out-of-scope": NaN,
    "human_answer": "Contact a Columbia University designated Travel Counselor at World Travel, Inc. (WTI) at 1-855-961-0313.                         ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "227": {
    "question": "I mistakenly processed a report under my profile instead of using the delegate function. How can I correct this issue and return the funds to the university?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "You can pay the funds back to your department via check. It can be made out to the department or The Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York.  Speak with your department if you have more questions about their process. It will be credited back to the project it was drawn from. \nYou can submit the proper report as a delegate at any time as long as the funding source has funds to support it. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1414": {
    "question": "I need a copy of Report Key 284219 and Voucher ID 06416878. Can you assist me with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Sent via email.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "490": {
    "question": "I need access to Concur.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Directed to Raquel Marin for temp concur access",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1123": {
    "question": "I need assistance regarding the Concur Report SEH26I.",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Working on another ticket. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "755": {
    "question": "I need assistance related to Report Key: 320944.",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Report Key :320944\nPending submission",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "479": {
    "question": "I need assistance with Concur access for GRA.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Expense report can be submitted by the student if he/she has access to concur",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "141": {
    "question": "I need assistance with Concur report D1MELM. Can someone guide me on this?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Creating itemization for over the threshold meal. Give us a call if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "547": {
    "question": "I need assistance with Concur trip booking. Can someone help me out?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Air and travel can be booked when user has travel arranger role. User who does not have role can have department book trip or request reimbursement after. Thank you, Dralca",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "332": {
    "question": "I need assistance with Report Key 303525 for Juliana Bol. She has been trying to close out her hotel charges for a group, but the system is interpreting her entries incorrectly. Can we delete the drop box entries with all the expense dates as 07/29/24? Also, can you confirm if everything is okay with the receipts from the travel agency for her hotel and airfare?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Yellow alerts   are just warnings , do not stop approval process. Expense is ready to be approved\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1129": {
    "question": "I need assistance with Report Key: 304616.",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "User added a justification, error alert is cleared",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1375": {
    "question": "I need assistance with accessing Concur. Could you help me with that?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Directed to \nRaquel Marin\nAVP,Int Cntrls Compl,Dep Cntlr\n rm2698@cumc.columbia.edu\n +1 212 305 9622",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "134": {
    "question": "I need assistance with an expense report for a hotel stay I booked. I was charged for four nights instead of the intended two, and there were credits returned to my corporate card. Can the Concur Admin team confirm that my expenses and credits are itemized correctly?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "the credits are not part of the $1258.28 itemization.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "520": {
    "question": "I need assistance with an expense tip that was paid by cash. The Report Key is 300916.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "For ground transportation enter the exact amount as reflected on the receipt\n\\Enter additional expense line for the tip and indicate in the comment box that it was paid by cash",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "0": {
    "question": "I need assistance with booking rail travel. What is the right process?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Booking rail can be done via Concur using air/rail travel card and can be booked for guest. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "63": {
    "question": "I need assistance with correcting itemization on my Concur report. Can someone help me?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Correcting itemization for group meal  to show correct reimbursement amount. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "119": {
    "question": "I need assistance with creating a Concur profile for a new hire.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "PAC profile has to be created first for employees to have concur access",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "559": {
    "question": "I need assistance with making changes to my Concur delegate. What steps do I need to take?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Leidy Scott has been removed from the Hashim AlHashimi's profile as delegate.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "726": {
    "question": "I need assistance with my per diem for Report Key: 303874. Can you help?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Report Key :  303874\nReady for submission",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "51": {
    "question": "I need assistance with reimbursement for student mtw2156. How should I proceed?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Assistance finding student as non-profile payee. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "416": {
    "question": "I need assistance with report key ey2289, which is associated with Report Key: 305892.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Assisted user with meal itemization on report key 305892",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "7": {
    "question": "I need assistance with segregating a flight expense on my Concur report. Can someone help?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "See Travel Policy https://universitypolicies.columbia.edu/content/travel-expense-policy\n\nFirst or Business Class Travel\n\nTravel must be booked utilizing the Lowest Logical Fare (LLF) as defined above. Business class may be used for travel if your department's or school's financial approver confirms that appropriate funds are available (prior to purchase), and if any of the following conditions are met:\n\nAny flight segment that has a scheduled in-air flight time* in excess of five hours.  (Connecting flights involving at least one flight segment with a scheduled in-air flight time in excess of five hours may also be booked in business class).\nA documented medical condition which requires a reasonable accommodation that has been approved by the University's Leave Management office.   \nIf a flight meets the criteria for business class but business class is not offered (e.g. 2-class plane) the forward cabin will be considered business class, even though the ticket may be issued in first class.  The traveler is responsible for documenting this exception on the Expense Report.\n \n*Air time means the amount of time a traveler is continuously in the air on a single flight/leg.\n\nIf a traveler elects to fly in business or first class on a flight of less than five (5) hours duration, has not met the above mentioned conditions, and has not obtained the necessary financial approval, they will be reimbursed only for an amount equivalent to an economy/coach airfare.\n\nSegregation of airfare above the economy/coach rate is required in all cases.  First or business class airfare can only be charged to a government grant in cases where the grant explicitly allows such expenses.  It is important to note that the cost of the lowest logical available economy/coach airfare when purchasing a business/first-class fare should be obtained by the traveler at time of initial purchase.\n\n \n\nThe amount above the economy/coach fare must be segregated to the appropriate expense type, a comparison of the coach/economy and business/first-class airfare costs must be provided, along with payee justification is required.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "455": {
    "question": "I need assistance with the Concur report meant for faculty jb39.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Business class flight must provide comparison flight for coach fare making sure the flight shows the same time as the original flight. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "465": {
    "question": "I need assistance with the Concur security roles for department 1611104 and Division 16IT00X. Can someone please check the attached document?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "See attached Concur Security roles for dept 1611104  Div 16IT00X Sub Div161100X.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "71": {
    "question": "I need assistance with the journal voucher for Daniella Sodera, with transaction ID 06480075.",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Expense report attached",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "154": {
    "question": "I need assistance with the reimbursement for 0000218395.",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Reimbursement will need to be submitted as outside party by the department. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "291": {
    "question": "I need assistance with travel booking on Concur. Can you help me?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Jason,\nHere is guidance on how to register international trips with ISOS\nhttps://globaltravel.columbia.edu/content/isos-mytrips\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "368": {
    "question": "I need clarification about Concur report as ab5613. What should I do with it?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Personal days will need to be listed as personal/non-reimbursable. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "240": {
    "question": "I need clarification on entering all my moving expenses in Concur. I'm asked to categorize them under \"Movement of Household Goods for Relocation,\" but I'm confused about whether the hotel receipts need to be itemized, especially since the fields gray out. Can someone help me with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hi Sean,\nCategorizing all expense into a single expense type would most likely trigger Audit review to push back. Please do break out expenses accordingly and provide as must information as possible for Audit review to analyze.\n\nThank you.\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "164": {
    "question": "I need clarification. I cannot do the missing receipt declaration as a delegate since it's required for the payee to complete it themselves. Is that correct?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The payee must do the declaration themselves.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "17": {
    "question": "I need guidance on how much to deduct from the per diem since the payee stayed at a bed & breakfast with breakfast included. Should I deduct $16 or $10?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "use the per diem rate",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "209": {
    "question": "I need help adding a student employee as a Delegate to my Concur profile so I can process an expense report. I tried to do it, but I can't find her in Concur even though she has an active student employee profile. Thank you for your assistance.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hope you are well. It looks like she was initially opted into Concur, but it expired on 9/30/2024. They must be opted in by the DAF again. You can find instructions for opting the student in here in section 8: https://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/content/getting-started\nLet me know if you have any other questions.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "769": {
    "question": "I need help adding an airfare expense to an existing report, but I'm unable to find the option for airfare. I had to put it under miscellaneous, but my administrator wants me to change it. What should I do?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Please submit new ticket if any additional questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "135": {
    "question": "I need help because someone needs to add me as a delegate for Concur. How do we proceed with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "He needs to add you as his delegate.  See attached for current status.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "28": {
    "question": "I need help logging into Concur. Can you assist me?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "You can log in using your uni. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "217": {
    "question": "I need help reconciling travel expenses for a guest in Concur.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "When you are reconciling you don't do it under the non-profile payee, that is used to reimburse the traveler. In this case, you do it under your own profile, since you're just reconciling no payments will be issued. Here is the\nJob aid: https://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/news/how-do-i-reconcile-corporate-card-or-airrail-central-pay-transactions\nvideo job aid: https://www.finance.columbia.edu/content/reconciling-corporate-card-and-columbia-airrail-central-pay-transactions-concur",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "318": {
    "question": "I need help reopening an old incident report (INC2695345). I'm unable to find Kenneth Colin Roedl in Concur, even though he has a US address in his SSOL profile. What should I do? Thank you, Sandra Overo.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Timing issue as information needed to feed from SSOL to ARC to Concur. Kenneth appears in Concur today.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "711": {
    "question": "I need help resolving alerts on my expense report for the Hutchinson DR/PR trip totaling $4,966.55.",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Changed the \"meal segregated\" itemization to \"individual meal lunch\" since it was not over the lunch threshold.  Will upload the email confirmation/boarding pass as the receipt for the flight booked through Concur.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "138": {
    "question": "I need help with Concur access for UNI CMS2369, where the individual still has active access and can create her own report or assign me as a delegate for preparation. What should I do?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "CMS2369 still has active Concur access so she can create her own report, or assign a delegate to prepare for her. \nIf issues logging in, try clearing browser cache , restart and log in again.  Try also using a different browser(clear cache first).",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "666": {
    "question": "I need help with V06366950 backup. Can anyone assist?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Department needed backup attached to Concur report. Reopen or give us a call if any additional questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "147": {
    "question": "I need help with a Concur expense for a business class. Can someone guide me through the process?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Instructions  for itemizing a business class ticket\nhttps://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/news/how-do-i-itemize-business-class-flight",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1148": {
    "question": "I need help with a payment issue. The payee was paid $296.24, but the approved amount is only $229.84, and the amount due to the employee is $309.72, which is more than what was paid. Can you please advise? Thank you.",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Resolved.\n\nYou are welcome Alicia.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "354": {
    "question": "I need help with an expense report that was returned. Luisa mentioned that she will do the itemization by manually adding the itemization line and then copying them and changing the date for each night.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Luisa will do the itemization by manually adding the itemization line and then copying them and changing the date for each night.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "545": {
    "question": "I need help with expense reconciliation for a deposit for a conference in April. Who can assist me with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Expense has to be reconciled by the hard close date",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "576": {
    "question": "I need help with my Concur account. Could someone assist me?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Concur is available only to Columbia University Employees. If you are Presbyterian Hospital employee a temporary affiliate access can be requested . Please reach out to Raquel Marin\nrm2698@cumc.columbia.edu",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "596": {
    "question": "I need help with my Concur report related to the AAIC Meeting 2024. The itemization shows more than $7.08. Can someone contact the hotel to clarify this charge?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Itemization is over $7.08.\nContact the hotel why they charged over $7.08.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "374": {
    "question": "I need help with my meal expense report - can you guide me on how to itemize the meal, tax/tip, and segregate overages?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Meal expense must be itemize - food/meal, tax and tips, and segregate overage.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "130": {
    "question": "I need help with the expense for university PDK3. The report key is 293260.",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Expense type miscellaneous can be used for currency exchange fee",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "542": {
    "question": "I need help with the reimbursement process as a student. Can someone guide me?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Reimbursement for students can be proceed by the Finance Office of the department",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1102": {
    "question": "I need information regarding the Concur reimbursement FAA exception form.",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Give us a call or reopen ticket if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "654": {
    "question": "I need some advice on how to complete a couple of travel expense reports. My department no longer has administrative support. Can I have a brief Zoom discussion about this? Thank you, Simon.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Please reopen ticket or submit a new one if any additional questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1109": {
    "question": "I need temporary Concur access for a NYP employee. Is there a process for this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Please reach out to Raquel Marin\nrm2698@cumc.columbia.edu",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1189": {
    "question": "I need to access the requests I approved this month in Concur, can you help me with that?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "No response von follow up question",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "560": {
    "question": "I need to add Chase Licata as my reporting manager in Concur, but I can't select him as an option. Can you assist me with that?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Provided instructions to set up Chase as the Reporting Manager.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "180": {
    "question": "I need to assign a delegate to my profile in Concur (UNI PT140). Can you provide guidance on how to do this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "UNI PT140 she will need to assign delegate to her profile see attached.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "33": {
    "question": "I need to book airfare and hotel for a guest speaker. Can you advise me on the process?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Travel and Lodging can be booked before the guest is a vendor. Please make sure to get the guest all the required information for the bookings.  Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "183": {
    "question": "I need to complete the Missing Receipt Affidavit in Concur for my report. I understand that I cannot have receipts or documents uploaded if I am declaring Missing Receipts. Can you confirm this process?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The accountholder will need to submit and complete the Missing Receipt Affidavit in Concur and you cannot have receipts/documents uploaded in Concur for the item if you are declaring Missing Receipts.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "326": {
    "question": "I need to find a hotel that isn't listed in Concur. What should I do?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Select Other and enter hotel name in the Description/Justification  box.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "438": {
    "question": "I need to find out why Virginia Gao, Profile ID number CNR0113184, can\u2019t be found in Concur for reimbursements. Can you let me know what her vendor type is or if she has access to Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "CNR0113184 is an employee with concur access, , can submit own expense report",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "610": {
    "question": "I need to follow up on the status of the reimbursements. The vendor profile CNR0107186 is currently inactive, and I couldn't find any NPP reports under UNI: cqz2001. Eunice will confirm tomorrow if her vendor profile has reactivated after adding a local or permanent address to her SSOL profile.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Eunice will call back tomorrow to confirm that her vendor profile CNR0107186 has reactivated after adding a US local or permanent address to her SSOL profile. She will need to follow up with her department on the reimbursements as I could not find anything pending at this time.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "495": {
    "question": "I need to know how to complete the reconciliations for jtb2192, who left the university with unreconciled expenses. The department can't submit as delegates. How can we proceed?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "This has been done the 2 expenses below are now in your Concur queue. Thank you.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "471": {
    "question": "I need to know if I should reconcile my Concur travel purchase/reimbursement charges before or after my trip. Can someone confirm this for me? Thank you!",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Air fare, registration fee, membership fee can be reimbursed before the end of the trip. Other expenses have to be submitted after the trip end date\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "836": {
    "question": "I need to know the correct person to send my expense report to. Someone in my Epi department mentioned either Vincent O Grady or Shana Young, but I can't find them listed as initial approvers. Can you assist me?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Marisol,\nReach out to one of the people below\nMirtha Delvalle 821200X Department of Epidemiology EPI Epidemiology Assoc Dir, Grants & Finance md2300@cumc.columbia.edu 212/305-6226\n\nMs Dilenny Roca-Dominguez 821200X Department of Epidemiology EPI Epidemiology Program Manager dr146@cumc.columbia.edu 212/305-6718\n\nMs Reina Burdie 821200X Department of Epidemiology EPI Epidemiology Department Administrator ryb2001@cumc.columbia.edu 212/305-0695\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "773": {
    "question": "I need to make changes to my Concur profile, specifically correcting the name under the travel information. My preferred contact is listed as 'Requested by' and my contact method is email, which is ka2933@columbia.edu.",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Hello,\n\nWe have not heard back from you regarding the additional information we need to assist you with your Service Now Incident. Because several days have passed since we requested additional information, the Service Center has marked the incident as resolved. If you do not feel this issue was resolved, please re-open this incident and provide the required information.\n\nThank You\n",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "371": {
    "question": "I need to obtain a comparison flight to see if it would cost more or less to not extend my travel and then decide from there.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Need to obtain a comparison flight to see if it would cost more or less to not extend the travel and then go from there.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "350": {
    "question": "I need to perform a flight comparison related to a recent business trip. What is needed to facilitate this comparison? I appreciate your help in advance.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Please contact the airline and ask them for a flight comparison. The parameters of the flight details should be as close to the original flight as possible, same departure city, day of the week, time of day, and arrivals. Once you receive it you should upload it along with the supporting documentation for the actual flight. You can follow this job aid for details on how to itemize the flight: https://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/news/how-do-i-itemize-business-class-flight\nLet me know if you have any other questions",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "55": {
    "question": "I need to perform corporate card expense reconciliation, but I would like to do this before my trip's end date.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Posted corporate card transactions can be moved to a report page until trip completion date",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "636": {
    "question": "I need to reimburse an outside party named John Gershman, but I can't find him on Concur. He updated his information on PaymentWorks recently. Can you check his Concur status for me? Thanks!",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Willson,\nThis vendor has a classification of supplier and is not going to be available through concur. Vendors must have a classification of Outside Party in order to process reimbursement through concur and I don't see any update request he submitted\n\nYou can pass the instruction below to the vendor to submit update request\n\n1..Log into your PaymentWorks account and navigate to the Home or Customers pages to view your Customers. click view /edit for the Columbia registration\n2. Click the View/Edit Form link for Columbia University. The form appears where you will be able to make updates.\n3 Access the Additional Information section of the form and change your selections\n\n1. Under 1099 tax information for individuals select \"None of these apply\"\n2. Under vendor classification select Other payment types\n\n3. As a US individual What are you receiving payment for\nSelect the appropriate kind such as honoraria, reimbursement etc.\n\nAfter making the changes vendor needs to submit\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "151": {
    "question": "I need to reimburse my travel expense covered by Columbia Global Center Santiago, but I'm having trouble accessing Concur. It shows an error when I try to log in. Can I get help with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Students are not granted access to concur. Your expense reimbursement should be processed by your schools department. So please reach out to the Department Administrator in the Finance Office\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "398": {
    "question": "I need to request Concur access for uni djc2244. Can you help me with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "uni, djc2244 has access to concur",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "185": {
    "question": "I need to review report 315157 for UNI PAG2123. Is the Expense Type 'Group Booking Deposit / Fee' correct for our venue deposit payment? If not, could you please advise me on which one to use?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "HI Kieshia,\nI don't see anything wrong with it. Please approve and AP with review further.\nThank you.\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "162": {
    "question": "I need to seek approval from Jose Corniel for the UNI: sap2216 request before it can be submitted for approval. Can you help?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Jose Corniel needs to approve the request. Then the request can be linked to the report and it can be submitted for approval.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "211": {
    "question": "I need to segregate a group meal over the threshold by changing the amount to $35x5 and putting the remaining balance under meal - segregated. Is this correct?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Under the Itemizations tab changed the amount under group meal to $35x5 and put the remaining balance under meal -segregated.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "171": {
    "question": "I need to submit an expense report for my trip to the Joyce SAFE States Conference, but there were charges on the traveler's card that I need to adjust due to being charged twice. How should I handle this?",
    "out-of-scope": "other",
    "human_answer": "\nHotel - adjusted total amount to since the traveler's card was charged twice.\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1154": {
    "question": "I need to submit an expense report to reimburse survey fees used for a research project. Can someone assist me with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "User Miscellaneous as Expense type.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "605": {
    "question": "I need to update Lucia Li's profile in Concur as it still reflects her previous position in SPS. What steps should I take?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hi Carolina,\nDue to the Lucia's PAC information (821000X) with an X. Concur can only use full 7 digit department codes. In this case, Lucia will need to update her profile manually.\n\n\nLet me know if you have other questions. Thank you.\u00a0\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "580": {
    "question": "I need to update a vendor's address, but I heard that the request for Zachary Tumin was rejected since he is a Columbia employee seeking reimbursement. Can someone guide me on how to proceed with the Non-Profiled Payee report?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Per Vendor Managemet:\nThis New Vendor Request for Zachary Tumin has been rejected as the vendor has identified themselves as a Columbia employee seeking reimbursement. Transactions of this type are to be completed using Concur with the employee's already assigned CNR number/profile (CNR0057333).\n\nConcur id CNR0057333 is active, please create a Non-Profiled Payee report with Employee vendor type.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "19": {
    "question": "I need to update my address for reimbursement purposes. Can you assist me with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Students update their addresses in SSOL",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "59": {
    "question": "I need to update the Concur expense header and am looking for assistance with that.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Updating report header to route to correct department. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "511": {
    "question": "I need to update the address in Concur for account 0000265790; it should be 7I instead of 7H. Could you help with that?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Please tell the vendor to log into PaymentWorks and submit an address update. They keyed in 7H in the initial PaymentWorks request. \nYou can go ahead and process the Concur report if it is being paid via ACH while she updates her address. It should not cause an issue. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "94": {
    "question": "I need to view Expense Report 288442 to get the backup. How can I do that?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Navigated through Approvals>Reports>View = Last Quarter.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "101": {
    "question": "I no longer have access to log into Concur for UNI: aa4085. However, I have an active student vendor profile CNR0080704, and Sherry will enter a non-profiled payee report. What should I do?",
    "out-of-scope": "unsure",
    "human_answer": "No more access to login to Concur, however she has an active student vendor profile CNR0080704, so Sherry will enter a non-profiled payee report.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "578": {
    "question": "I noticed that Sara Taylor was automatically added as the Executive Expense Approver for Mark Mazower (UNI: mm2669). In the past, it was Mark Hawkins, and his assistant Michael Lane handled the reviews and approvals. Can you confirm if this change is permanent or was it done in error?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hi Lawino,\nI can confirm that Mark Mazower's report workflow will require Sara's approval. This setting was structured by Mark Hawkin. Please email me know if this needs to be modify.\nThank you.\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "392": {
    "question": "I noticed that Tianjiao Wang (0000270724) is not appearing in Concur even though their onboarding was completed on 9.3.24. Could you kindly advise? Thanks, Anthony.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Finding vendor profile in Concur. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "678": {
    "question": "I noticed that an initiative is not available. Could anyone provide more information on this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Please use undefined initiative if it is not available",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "450": {
    "question": "I noticed that employee Karen Cover's expense reports are routing directly to Central AP instead of our department. The report number is C08E01CFC051447897B0. Can you investigate what the issue is? Thanks.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Please have DAF add approvers for department 5002111.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "955": {
    "question": "I noticed that money has not been credited to my account. Can someone help with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "I didn't hear back from you with the additional information I requested to assist you with your inquiry. This ticket is now closed for lack of response",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "58": {
    "question": "I noticed that the hotel name is not appearing in Concur, and I am unsure how to handle this issue.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Emily will use the \"other (comment required)\"option.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "120": {
    "question": "I noticed that there are no Initial Reviewers currently set up for department 7006602. Should I change the Admin Department on my report to one that has Initial Reviewers, or can I set them up through the Financial Systems Security Application? I understand I can't approve my own expense report.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Since the existing expense reports were created before you updated your Profile defaults you will need to update the School/Division/Sub-Division/and Admin Department directly on the reports. After you have opened a report click on Report Details then Report Header. You will then be able to update the fields, save, and then submit the report.\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "485": {
    "question": "I noticed there is a duplicate entry for INC2679599. What should I do?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Duplicate of  INC2679599  which is already submitted to A/P payments to be rejected",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "442": {
    "question": "I ordered books from Cyprus and want to know if the department can pay for the expenses directly to avoid vendor setup, or should I use my personal credit card and request reimbursement?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Expense for purchase of book can be reimbursed",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "148": {
    "question": "I paid for a hotel booking for a guest using PCard. What steps should I follow for reporting this in Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "PCard can no longer be used to pay or any travel related expense.  Please provide details/information on the last travel expense so we can review how this was paid in Concur.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "474": {
    "question": "I paid for a training and need to be reimbursed, but my request was returned because I need proof of approval. Since my supervisor did not send an email confirming this, I'm not sure how to provide the necessary proof. What should I do?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Laura,\nAsk your supervisor to send you an e-mail that this training was approved by him and you can upload the e-mail as supporting document\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "229": {
    "question": "I paid for my airfare through someone else, who I reimbursed via Venmo. Is there a way to reconcile this in Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Submit report with explanation and wait for Central to review and approve.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "415": {
    "question": "I previously worked at the School of Law and have transferred to CUMC. I need to book hotels in my new role, but my Concur account still shows my previous manager's name and department's chartstring. How can I get this updated?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Please go under your profile setting and update your departmental information.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "100": {
    "question": "I purchased a flight ticket through Concur, canceled it, and received a credit that now requires reconciliation. How can I reconcile this credit since there was never a charge? I've attached a screenshot for reference. Thank you!",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Corporate card expenses must be reconciled. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "322": {
    "question": "I purchased two business class flights with ticket code dh2994 but only need to get reimbursed for one. How can I itemize this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "In the itemization, enter the economy airfare amount for one flight in the airfare field. Place any excess amount in the segregated airfare field, and record the total amount for the flight he is not requesting reimbursement for in the personal non-reimbursable field. Please upload the supporting documents with the comparison to the expense line and enter a comment in the justification box explaining why he is requesting reimbursement for only half of the expense. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "510": {
    "question": "I received a job aid with instructions on how to apply for Concur temporary access. Can you confirm if I need anything else to proceed?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Here is the job aid with instructions on how to apply for Concur temporary access:\nhttps://www.finance.columbia.edu/content/applying-temporary-concur-access-affiliate",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "389": {
    "question": "I received a message that says, \"Sorry, something went wrong. We encountered an error processing your request.\" If the issue persists, should I contact my Company Administrator or Help Desk with correlation_id d6f090f68e1b107e2a48a9e90c633c5b for additional help?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "You must be an employee of Columbia (not NYP) in order to have default access to login to Columbia's Concur system. If you need to be reimbursed there are two options:\n\n1. The Columbia department can enter the reimbursement for you as a Non-Profile Payee in Concur or\n2. You can request access to login to Concur as an affiliate. This job aid has the instructions on how to do this: https://www.finance.columbia.edu/sites/default/files/content/Training%20Documents/Travel%20and%20Expense/Job_Aid_Concur_Affiliates_FSSA.pdf\n\nFor either of these options you MUST first be set up as an Outside Party vendor through the PaymentWorks system. You should discuss with the Columbia department which option would be more appropriate in your situation. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "609": {
    "question": "I received a reimbursement request from a faculty member for a dinner for 22 people at a private home in Knoxville, TN for $1650. Does this expense require a purchasing review or contract? I know it\u2019s usually required for off-campus events of 30 or more people, but I wanted to double-check before proceeding. Thank you!",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Please reach out to Thomas Brown in purchasing\nThomas Brown\nSenior Category Manager, Events and Contracts\ntb2354@columbia.edu\n+1 212 853 4378\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "478": {
    "question": "I received a reminder regarding my unused airline credit for cancelled trip UNI: kja2103. There is nothing to reconcile, but I need to know how to use the credit with the airline.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "There is nothing to reconcile at this time, this is a reminder that the credit with the airline is available. Please call WTI to use the credit.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1121": {
    "question": "I received a returned Concur report for my ll3196 report number: LXBQGV. Can you assist me with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Needs to reach out directly to Robert Hunter.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "95": {
    "question": "I received a warning on Expense Report db2920 regarding an unreconciled cash advance. Will this warning prevent the report from being approved and paid? I understand Sonia will reconcile the outstanding advance at the same time.",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "This is a warning but should not prevent the report from being approved and paid. \nSonia will work on reconciling the outstanding advance at the same time.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "370": {
    "question": "I received an email from Ms. Lynch saying that I do not have to do anything else on my part for my expense submission. Can you tell me what else is needed from me regarding the email confirmation of the expenses?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "This is for the department creating the report. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "629": {
    "question": "I received an email regarding a 2023 advance that has been reconciled. What should I do next?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hi Justin,\ni am confirming that Jen had reconciled the cash advance with report (report Key:153363) and that i have closed the cash advance. She should no longer receive the email notification.\nThank you.\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "264": {
    "question": "I received an email stating that my delegate submitted a Concur report for medical license fees that needs my review, but I cannot access it. Can you help?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Per our discussion, the report for your medical license fee was approved and paid on on 07/31/2024 via ach reference 2001308320 in the amount of $600. \n\nThanks.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "74": {
    "question": "I received confirmation that my Concur access was approved on 10/22. Can you provide further details?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Dear Customer, \n\nWe have not heard back from you regarding your Service Now Incident. Because several days have passed, the Service Center has marked the incident as resolved. If you do not feel this issue was resolved, please re-open this incident and provide the required information.\n \nThank You\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "40": {
    "question": "I recently had to cancel my trip that was booked on Concur via central pay. The flight is marked as cancelled in the airline's app and I received a confirmation email, but the payments are still showing as available expenses to reconcile. How should I proceed?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The expense needs to be reconciled. Andra will speak to World Travel regarding any refunds/credits.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "589": {
    "question": "I recently reached out about being unable to find a student in Concur, and I was told it was due to unregistered status. The student confirmed that he has registered. I'm still unable to find Feiyue Yang (fy2306) in the system to complete his reimbursement. Can you help?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Christopher,\nStudents should also have their local US mailing address entered in SSOL in order to have their concur/ARC profile active.\nI checked and Feiyue has not entered a local address. Please advise him to do so and once done his profile will be active within 48 hrs.\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1135": {
    "question": "I recently received an unrestricted discretionary fund to support large-enrollment classes in the epidemiology department, but I'm unable to find the correct chart string in Concur to charge against the account. The chart string is COLUM-01-8231202-UR008725-01-10268-0000000-USNY. Can you please advise?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Please reopen or submit new ticket if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "651": {
    "question": "I requested reimbursement through Concur, and it was confirmed, but I don't see it in my paychecks. Who should I speak to about this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Soojeong ,\n\nPayment was made by ACH on 7/15 and 7/17\nThese are separate payments are not combined with your paycheck. Please review your bank statement where you receive your payroll payment\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "110": {
    "question": "I saw that the booking fee and exchange fee were refunded to a personal credit card, can someone help with that? Report Key: 318584.",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Personal check made out to the Trustees of Columbia can be processed by the Departments Finance Office to credit back the funds",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "325": {
    "question": "I saw the UNI YP2184 reference. How can I assign you as a delegate in Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "UNI YP2184 see attached screen shot. She will need to assign you as a delegate.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "533": {
    "question": "I see that Employee Edward Dijoseph's Concur request is stating (pending Cost Object Approval) Report# VJJU5R. Can you please let me know what's needed to push this through? Thank you, Katherine.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Report pending financial approval. Reopen or submit new ticket if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "383": {
    "question": "I see that I am not authorized to use Concur as per the user preferences listed below. Can you clarify further?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Reopen or submit a new ticket if any additional questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "218": {
    "question": "I selected the \"attendee type\" for a group meal with more than 10 attendees and entered the event name, but I had to change the number of attendees under the Attendees link. Can someone help me with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Selected the \"attendee type\" group meal 10+ attendees and entered event name. Also had to change the number of attendees under the Attendees link.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "364": {
    "question": "I still need the comparison flight because the amount over economy must be segregated. I will submit the comparison that I found and AP will review it when the report is submitted. Can I also notify the traveler that they must obtain the comparison flight at the time of booking even if the flight is over 5 hours?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The comparison flight is still needed because the amount over economy must be segregated. \nAshley will submit the comparison that she found and AP will review when the report is submitted. \nPlease also notify the traveler that they must obtain the comparison flight at the time of booking even if the flight is over 5 hours.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "333": {
    "question": "I submitted Report Key # 302950 for Marina Triplette, but I need to know if the expenses for dinners with alcohol on 7/16/24 and 7/18/24 are acceptable. Can you please advise?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "A lot of helpful Concur information could be located in the Training Library site, under Expensing Group Meals in Concur, corresponding Job Aid attached. Which covers segregating alcohol. Thank you. ",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "1381": {
    "question": "I submitted a CONCUR reimbursement for my business travel to South Africa without the airline and hotel taxes, thinking they wouldn't be reimbursed. Can I still get reimbursed even though the airline receipt is over 120 days old, but the hotel folio is within 120 days?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Any additional questions please reopen or submit a new ticket. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "468": {
    "question": "I submitted a Concur expense under the ID 0ch2107, and I can\u2019t find the status. Can someone help me with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Debasmita,\nWhen submitting a request what you should enter is the start and end date of the trip. The expense lines should only matter when submitting the actual expense reimbursement request as such each expense line has to be entered based on the transaction date or the date of purchase. A pre trip request is required only to show that the trip is approved by the department for those specific days\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "269": {
    "question": "I submitted a ticket last week because I was unable to locate a student in Concur (PID: C004675303). This student updated their mailing address in SSOL on 9/17, but she still does not appear in Concur. Can you please advise?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Sylvia,\nLook at the attached screen shot. Student doesn't have a local US mailing address entered in SSOL. That is the one address that can activate the profile. Please advise student to do so\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "76": {
    "question": "I took a trip back in 2023, and my total airfare was $364.92. I received approval for a pre-trip request (ID 4KH9) that was approved back on 10/17/2023, but since it is over a year old, I can't add it to my expense report. I need it to completely reconcile the airfare costs in expense report number BMNQE7. Can you please advise on the steps I need to take to import the pre-trip request into my expense report so that it can be reconciled?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "pre-trip request was closed, there's no way to reactivate.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "419": {
    "question": "I traveled from India and would like to know if I'm eligible for reimbursement of flight fare, which is approximately 1200 USD.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Any questions submit new ticket or give us a call. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "489": {
    "question": "I tried to reimburse Leonhard Heinrich on Concur, but he is not listed anywhere. He is a student with the university ID lrh2159. Can you assist me with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Students ARC profile gets inactivated every time the semester ends. In order to maintain active profile students must be registered for a current or future semester, have active status in SSOL with a local US mailing address",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "60": {
    "question": "I understand that Concur will pull my US address and banking information from SSOL for my reimbursement. Is there anything else I need to do?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Concur (the system for reimbursements) will pull your US address and banking information from SSOL.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "99": {
    "question": "I understand that the date should be entered in MM/DD/YYYY format for Concur. Is that correct?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Should be entered MM/DD/YYYY.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "509": {
    "question": "I updated the Concur Financial Approver for department 5218104 to myself (mwt2112) this morning, but expense reports are still directed to Mindaugas Paunksnis (mp2594). What else do I need to do for this to take effect?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Waiting for role to be updated in Concur. Submit new ticket or reopen if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "261": {
    "question": "I urgently need help accessing Concur. Can you please assist?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Ralph,\nYou are not a Columbia Employee, and the only vendor profile for you is an outside party which won't grant you access to Concur either. However, you can have someone enter a reimbursement on your behalf as a non-profile payee if you incurred expenses for business or travel at Columbia's Expense. If it's for Barnard, though, you'll need to use their systems and follow their policies.\n\n-John",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "642": {
    "question": "I used a corporate card for a payment, but when I submitted for reimbursement, it doesn't show as reimbursing Columbia, instead it shows reimbursing me. Can you advise me on this situation?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Available expense was coming from the ExpenseIt app. Recommended deleting in the app because deleting in Concur was not working.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "452": {
    "question": "I want to find out if Miriam Callahan (mc4027) has access to Concur to submit her reimbursement. Thank you!",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Miriam's PAC status has a termination date of 06/16/2022, she currently doesn't have access to concur",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "555": {
    "question": "I want to inquire about the reimbursements that have been processed but have not yet been received. What might be causing the delay?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Directed to departments Finance Office to submit a stop payment/reissue request",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "122": {
    "question": "I want to know about the per diem for my trip. If I already received reimbursement for some meals, can I still claim a per diem? If I haven't been reimbursed for any meals, can I create a separate expense report for the per diem?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "If the post doc already got reimbursed for some or all of the meals for the trip then you can't go back and modify to do a per diem.\nIf the post doc hasn't been reimbursed for any meals for the trip then you could create an expense report just for the per diem.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1485": {
    "question": "I want to know if a supervisor can automatically have the initial reviewer role in Concur or if an FSSSA form needs to be completed. Can someone clarify this for me?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Karen,\nSupervisors have to be opted in to have a supervisor concur approval role and must complete the training which will be assigned once the request to be opted in is submitted\nI have attached a job aid\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1": {
    "question": "I want to know if we can submit travel advances for non-CU Students and non-CU Employees who attend community advisory board meetings/focus groups related to our grant. Can you please advise?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Travel advance is available only to Columbia Employees and students",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "42": {
    "question": "I want to understand what is causing my Expense Report to require SBO approval. Is there something I can do to avoid it?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "In this case, it's appears to be a known system limitation, and not an actual policy violation. Per the travel arrangers job aid on page 4 in the note section under number 7 found here: https://www.finance.columbia.edu/sites/default/files/content/Training%20Documents/Concur/Job%20Aids/Job_Aid_Concur_Travel_Arrangers.pdf\nNote: Individual meal thresholds apply to Non-Profiled Payee Expense Reports. However, due to system limitations the calculation includes tip and tax. The amount over threshold\nmust be segregated. SBO approval is required when meal expenses exceed individual meal thresholds. This info can be found here\n\nOn 10/5 a lunch expense was submitted for $36.98, the lunch threshold hold is $35 before tax and tip, but since this is a non-profiled payee the system thinks it went over the threshold which triggers SBO approval. The SBOs are aware of this issue. You will have to segregate the \"overage\" and secure the necessary approval. You may also need to check the other meals to ensure they also don't need to be segregated.\n\nSBO approvals are needed for certain policy exceptions, there is no way to avoid them.\nThe following scenarios require SBO approval\n\u2022 Meals over thresholds\n\u2022 Lodging over $525 domestic, $600 international\n\u2022 Entertainment expense is greater than $1,500 or the per person cost is greater than $75\n\u2022 Business performance or de minimis gifts to employees exceeding $100\n\u2022 Years of Service or Retirement Gift to employees exceeding $400\n\u2022 Gifts to non-employees exceeding $600\nThis information can be found here: https://a-bedrock-kendra.s3.amazonaws.com/travel-expense-job-aid-files-24-1011/Job_Aid_Concur_Policy_Exception_Approval_Workflow.pdf\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "551": {
    "question": "I was informed that if I leave the expense as hotel-segregated on a Private Grant project, the voucher will have an error in ARC that prevents payment. I need to categorize it under a non-segregated expense type and upload documentation showing that the grant supports the over-threshold amount. Can someone confirm this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "If you leave the expense as hotel-segregated on a PG project the voucher will have an error in ARC that will prevent payment. \nNeed to put it under a non-segregated expense type with documentation uploaded showing that the grant allows the over-threshold amount. AP would have to approve this as an exception.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "49": {
    "question": "I was scheduled to travel for work in June, but I cancelled my trip due to severe weather. I received confirmation emails from Concur saying my trip was successfully cancelled, yet I'm still seeing charges for the flights under 'Available Expenses' in Concur. Any assistance would be greatly appreciated.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "All posted transactions whether a credit or debit should be moved to a report page and processed",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "658": {
    "question": "I would like clarification on the hotel rate threshold as outlined in the university travel expense policy. What are the requirements for lodging costs exceeding the set limits?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "https://universitypolicies.columbia.edu/content/travel-expense-policy\n\nThe cost of a hotel stay in the US should not exceed $350 per night (excluding taxes). International travelers should obtain room rates that do not exceed $400 per night (US dollars, excluding taxes). Lodging costs in excess of $350 per night in the US and $400 per night in an International location (by no more than 50%) requires payee justification and Financial Approval. Additionally, lodging costs in excess of $525 per night in the US and $600 per night in an International location (more than 50%) requires Senior Business Officer approval.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "161": {
    "question": "I would like to confirm if the attached invoice for a group meal using a corporate card meets the threshold limits. Does the meal threshold limit include the alcohol amount as well? If we use the corporate card, how should we reconcile the invoice, especially since Concur often does not allow bypassing the threshold limit if exceeded?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "For business meal thresholds please refer to the business expense policy below\nhttps://universitypolicies.columbia.edu/content/business-expense-policy\nIf a meal threshold is exceeded you need to segregate the over threshold amount\nAll charges posted on the corporate card must be reconciled by the hard close date\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "543": {
    "question": "I would like to confirm if the tickets I paid for with my personal credit card will be reimbursed properly. The Concur report shows $0 due to Employee, and these were charged through Central pay. How should I proceed with reconciling my expenses?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Unfortunately, we have not heard back from you, as such we will be closing this Incident.  If you require assistance with this matter, please reopen this Incident, open a new Incident, or send an email to corporatecard@columbia.edu. Thank you. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "621": {
    "question": "I would like to kindly request the status of the expense report named Diana C Otero Mostacero for the purpose of attending CRF-NY Valves June 5-7, 2024, with a requested amount of 739.10 USD.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Alicia ,\nThere is no expense report submitted for June",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "75": {
    "question": "I would like to know about the reimbursement process for UNI: az2888, who is currently an employee with Concur access to enter his own report or set up a delegate.",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Currently an employee with Concur access so he can enter his own report or set up a delegate.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "87": {
    "question": "I'm David Eppenstein, an employee of CU, and I need to create and submit my own expense report in Concur. I also want to assign a delegate to prepare the report for me.",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "CNR0144133 DAVID EPPENSTEIN employee of CU, he has to create and submit his own expense report in Concur.  He can assign a delegate to prepare report.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1099": {
    "question": "I'm Dr. Soojin Park, and I'm unable to book travel via the Concur home page. An error message saying \"Sorry, something went wrong. We have encountered a problem with your travel profile. Please contact your travel agent for immediate booking and contact your Company Administrator or Help Desk for support.\" appears. I also can't book flights for her as a delegate. A plane ticket is needed for an upcoming conference. Please assist me.",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "In this situation please contact the Concur booking tool support number for assistance: 1-800-221-4730.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "90": {
    "question": "I'm a delegate for Alan Stewart, a Columbia faculty member. I'm trying to create an expense report for him, but he doesn't have the option to allow me to do so. Can you please help me with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Issue with checkmarks not being checked.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "173": {
    "question": "I'm a first-time user trying to submit a reimbursement request, but I can\u2019t find the correct approver in Concur. I work as a full-time Program Coordinator at the Workplace Center at the School of Social Work, and my expense is for dinner during my shift. Can someone help me submit this correctly?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Ethan,\nThe concur approval workflow is designed in a way that whenever there is a supervisor assigned in PAC the expense report routes to the supervisor for approval rather than you selecting an initial reviewer. You have assigned supervisor , GWYNETH KIRKBRIDE , this supervisor has first to take the concur supervisor training in order to be able to approve expense reports.\nSupervisors can be opted in by the DAF of the department and required training will be assigned. Once the training is completed she will be able to approve your expense report\nI have attached a job aid for supervisor opt in if needed\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "424": {
    "question": "I'm a new postdoctoral fellow at Columbia and began my appointment on September 1. The administrator for my program advised me to login to Concur to book my travel for the fall semester, but I can\u2019t access the system. When I enter my Columbia credentials and approve it through Duo, it successfully logs in but then shows a page saying, \"Sorry, something went wrong\" with the error code \"3e299bfe7e83791396b902f21345bdec.\"",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Anatol,\nAre you a new employee?\nIf so you must wait until your profile is established in PAC, I don't see any profile yet\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "232": {
    "question": "I'm an approver delegate for Ye Lu (sl4932). There are a few expense reports pending Ye's approval where I'm supposed to act as Ye, but I don\u2019t have the button to approve. Can you help me with this? I\u2019ve attached a screenshot for reference. Examples of the expense reports include under mm4338 \"TE072824-Maleki-Arian-ISIT $6,638.73\" and under am6292 \"Hotel for EC 2024 $571.27\"",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Ye Lu did not set you up as approver on her behalf.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "525": {
    "question": "I'm attending two conferences one after another in different cities and need to book my travel through Concur. Can you confirm if there are any buffer days in between the conferences?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Post-doc can book through Concur. Justine is confirming there are no buffer days in between the conferences.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "343": {
    "question": "I'm booking a flight on behalf of Nida Williams, but the name on her driver's license is Nida Wala Saleem, while her UNI name is Nida Wala Williams. The name associated with her profile is greyed out, and I can't change it. What should I do to ensure the boarding pass matches her ID?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Reopen or submit a new ticket if any additional questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "1177": {
    "question": "I'm booking a flight to a conference in Italy near Bologna, but I plan to return from Venice. Do I need to provide a price comparison for the flight back from Bologna, or can I go ahead and book the flight directly?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Give us a call or submit a ticket if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "475": {
    "question": "I'm checking on the expense related to cjh26 with Report Key: 301839.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Meal expense whether group or individual, it needs to be itemized",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "440": {
    "question": "I'm encountering an error message when trying to book travel.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hi Thomas,\nConcur Travel profile setting is very particular on information containing special characters. i've removed all the (' and -) on your profile setup. Please give booking another try.\nThank you.\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "731": {
    "question": "I'm encountering an error on Report Key: 305390.",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Assisted clearing red alert on \nReport Key :\n305390",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "97": {
    "question": "I'm encountering an issue where the hotel rate exceeds the $350 per night threshold. Shawnda Chapman was charged $463.50 per night instead of the original $309 for 3 nights. How can I segregate the hotel charge to address this error message?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Closing ticket as resolved. No further response/comments received from user.\n\n\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "341": {
    "question": "I'm experiencing a glitch with the attendees in Concur. Can you assist me with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Glitch when adding attendees fixed. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "346": {
    "question": "I'm experiencing an SAP Concur error, but I'm unsure what to do about it.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "As a student, you do not have default access to login to Concur. There are two options to reimburse you:\n\n1. Your department can enter the expense report on your behalf using a \"non-profiled payee\" report type.\n\n2. Your department can request to have you \"opted in\" to Concur so that you can login to Concur and enter the expense report yourself.\n\nPlease follow up with your department to see which option they want to use. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "447": {
    "question": "I'm experiencing an issue with my Concur report, can you help me troubleshoot it?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The Concur report must be submitted by the payee.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "159": {
    "question": "I'm experiencing problems logging into Concur. Can you assist me?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Meritxell,\nYour concur access has expired when the semester ended. You need to reach out to your DA(Department Administrator) or Senior Business Officer to be opted in for access\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "258": {
    "question": "I'm facing a login error and unable to access Concur. Can someone help?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Your PAC (HR) profile is not active. It shows a termination date of 06/15/2024. You must have an active PAC profile for access to Concur. Please reach out to your HR rep to discuss how to resolve this issue.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "143": {
    "question": "I'm facing a login error when trying to access Concur. The message states that something went wrong and provides a correlation_id for support. Can you assist me with logging in so I can submit my reimbursement?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hye-Min ,\nYour access to concur was inactivated at the end of the semester. Please reach out to your schools Department Administrator in the Finance Office to be opted in for access\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "179": {
    "question": "I'm facing an urgent issue submitting my Concur report (UNI KJA2103). The report name is DAR California Tour Sep 2024, and I'm getting an error message saying: You must attach a request for this report. I have attached a request already, but I still get the error upon submission. How can I resolve this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "please consolidate the reports. see email for more details.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "93": {
    "question": "I'm getting an error message when attempting to book travel for DK2757 in Concur, can you please assist?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "you need Travel arranger role",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "402": {
    "question": "I'm having issues trying to add delegates for reimbursements. Could you please advise? Thank you.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Catherine,\nAll of those users have access to concur, Their log on ID is their uni@columbia.edu, not their uni @cumc.columbia,edu\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "245": {
    "question": "I'm having issues with a Concur report on behalf of Mark Hansen. I keep getting an alert saying 'This expense type is not available for this policy. Please change the expense type.' I initially tried changing it to group meal, but I still face issues. Can you please assist with this report? Thank you.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Need to change all Group Meal 10+ Attendees expense types to Group Meal expense type on both the details tab and the itemizations tab of all the Group Meal expenses. May need to re-itemize the expenses after changing the expense type.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "400": {
    "question": "I'm having problems with my Concur login. Can someone assist me?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The department that is to reimburse you would need to get you set up as a vendor and then process the reimbursement for you.\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "14": {
    "question": "I'm having trouble accessing my Vendor/Supplier/Payee Profile with ID No. 0000270812 in Concur to make reimbursements. Can you help?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Supplier , 0000270812 has a default wire payment location. Wire payments can not be processed through concur. You need to process reimbursement through ARC on a check request",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "602": {
    "question": "I'm having trouble changing the initial expense approver on the SAP Concur app for reporting travel expenses. I've checked the",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Amirreza,\nYou do have an assigned supervisor, REBECCA HIRADE and your concur expense directly routes to her\nIn order for you to select Harold as your initial reviewer there are 2 options\n1, Rebecca has to be opted out as a concur superior (This might affect others who are under her supervision)\n2, Rebecca has to be removed from your PAC profile and this can be achieved by submitting a PAF, you need to reach out to the departments Finance office to carry out either one\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "381": {
    "question": "I'm having trouble logging into Concur (correlation_id 09cdab68b58e08c806cf6536fa81fa31), and I'm not quite sure who I should contact to get this fixed. I assume IT isn't responsible for Concur-related issues since it's a third party, but I can't seem to find a Concur Helpdesk reference on the Columbia website. Would you happen to know who the right person is to reach out to? Thank you! Kind regards, Kevin",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "PAC status was reactivated 9/9. Able to access Concur today, 9/10.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "382": {
    "question": "I'm having trouble logging into Concur (correlation_id 09cdab68b58e08c806cf6536fa81fa31), and I'm not sure who I should contact to fix this issue. I assume IT isn't responsible for Concur-related issues since it's a third party, but I\u2019m reaching out to them as well. Could you please point me in the right direction for who to contact? Thank you! Kind regards, Kevin",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "INC2692367 Kate is assisting with this incident and will keep opened until further notice. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "309": {
    "question": "I'm having trouble logging into Concur and I can't access my account.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "As a student, you do not have default access to login to Concur. There are two options to reimburse you:\n\n1. Your department can enter the expense report on your behalf using a \"non-profiled payee\" report type.\n\n2. Your department can request to have you \"opted in\" to Concur so that you can login to Concur and enter the expense report yourself.\n\nPlease follow up with your department to see which option they want to use. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "409": {
    "question": "I'm having trouble logging into Concur because it keeps giving me an error message. I need help getting access to Concur in order to process my reimbursement.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Sultona\nYou do not have access to concur. Concur is available to full time employees. Your reimbursement could be processed by your department or contact your department administrator if they can provide a temporary concur access\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "103": {
    "question": "I'm having trouble logging into Concur for reimbursement. I see an error message about my request not being processed and it suggests I contact the Help Desk with a specific correlation id. What should I do?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Polly,\nYour concur profile is currently inactive and this happens every time a semester ends. Please reach out to your  Home Departments Finance Office/Administrator to be opted in for access\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "125": {
    "question": "I'm having trouble logging into Concur to book travel for several days now. I keep getting an error. What can I do?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Alia,\nYour concur access is currently inactive and this happens every time a semester ends. You need to reach out to your schools Department Administrator in the Finance Office to be opted in for access\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "156": {
    "question": "I'm having trouble pulling up the chartstring listed below in Concur. Can you kindly advise? COLUM 7534601 GENRL GT006825 01 70574 00000000 30",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "There is no FY25 budget for project GT006825. If this is the correct project number a budget will need to be set up in the Budget Tool for FY25 for the combination of project GT006825 and department 7534601.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "570": {
    "question": "I'm inquiring about the reimbursement for a transportation expense from the airport to my residence, as I arrived two days before the conference. Can I get reimbursed for this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Advised to submit with full justification/details and AP will review for approval.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "491": {
    "question": "I'm inquiring about videographer service.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "This service requires a PO with a SOW only. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "391": {
    "question": "I'm looking for assistance with changing the name on an expense report under Report Details>Report Header.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Under Report Details>Report Header",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "257": {
    "question": "I'm looking for assistance with finding a less expensive hotel. I understand if the hotel is over $350 per night but under $525 it needs department approval. Over $525 would require SBO approval. Can you confirm this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "For assistance with possibly finding a less expensive hotel suggested reaching out to World Travel, our travel agency.\n\nIf the hotel is over $350 per night but under $525 this would need to be approved by your department's Financial Approver. Over $525 would require SBO approval.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "216": {
    "question": "I'm looking for assistance with my expense reimbursement as a postdoc.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Travel Expense Policy\nhttps://universitypolicies.columbia.edu/content/travel-expense-policy",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1055": {
    "question": "I'm looking for backup for report numbers 228319 & 266208. Can you provide that?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Please find attached the requested backup.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "5": {
    "question": "I'm looking for guidance on how to segregate airfare for business class expenses. Can you help?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "As discussed, please speak with Dr. Hailey about the canceled flight for $8475.10. As he booked this flight on his personal credit card, when he canceled the credit would have gone back to his personal credit card.  You can leave the cancelation fee on there and note in the comments that it's for a canceled flight and why it was rescheduled. \nTo segregate business class airfare: \nObtain the cost of the lowest logical economy/coach airfare for the same flight at the time of booking the business/first-class fare.\nIn your Concur expense report, enter the economy/coach airfare amount under the appropriate expense type (e.g. Airfare).\nEnter the difference between the business/first-class fare and the economy/coach fare under the expense type \"Airfare Segregated\".\nProvide justification for taking the business/first-class flight, such as flight duration over 5 hours or medical accommodation.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "243": {
    "question": "I'm looking for help with the moving expense report for a postdoc.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Use expense type\nMovement of Household Goods for Relocation",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "70": {
    "question": "I'm looking for information regarding a comparison flight.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": " The comparison quotes are required at the time of booking. In rare circumstances, where this does not take place- the only comparison or documentation that can be provided is to look at the same date range for future dates since there is no  way to look back in the airline reservation system. AP needs this documentation for audit requirements.                         ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "133": {
    "question": "I'm looking for recommendations on using either Group Meal or Event Supplies for food and supplies for our interoffice Coffee Hour. Can I get some guidance?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Recommended using either Group Meal or Event Supplies.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "160": {
    "question": "I'm looking to understand more about the hotel segregation in the hs762 expense report process.",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Here is the lodging itemization job aid: https://www.finance.columbia.edu/sites/default/files/content/Training%20Documents/Concur/Job%20Aids/Job_Aid_Concur_Itemizing_Lodging.pdf\nTo recap our call: \nWe created itemizations to segregate the over the threshold amount of the hotel expense. \nPer our discussion, please allocate the segregated charges to a UR (unrestricted) project. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "581": {
    "question": "I'm not appearing as a vendor in Concur for reimbursement because there's no address in my SSOL profile. Hasan will add a local or permanent address in the U.S. Could someone confirm if my Vendor ID will be created and appear in Concur soon?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "No address in SSOL. Hasan will add a \"local\" or \"permanent\" address in the US in his SSOL profile. Vendor ID should be created tomorrow and appear in Concur on Saturday.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "263": {
    "question": "I'm planning a trip to Spain, but one of my faculty members is extending their stay for personal reasons. Can you help me with the flight option from Greece to New York instead of from Spain?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Price comparison needed for Spain to NY if leaving on the 13th.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "472": {
    "question": "I'm preparing a Concur report for db3526. Is there anyone who can guide me through the process?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Dept will let student know to contact us in order to walk the student. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "439": {
    "question": "I'm reaching out with a Concur inquiry.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Travel must be reconciled and submitted by the user. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "313": {
    "question": "I'm receiving an error message when trying to submit a report with Report Key: 310536. Can someone help me with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Assisted with clearing red alerts on \nReport Key :310536",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1491": {
    "question": "I'm submitting a Concur report that has extended days for personal reasons. Is there anything specific I need to include?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Submit a price comparison for travel from start to end of business travel dates.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "742": {
    "question": "I'm submitting an expense report for uni taf2134 with Report Key: 321357. What are the next steps?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Assisted with hotel itemization\nReport Key :321357  is submitted",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "140": {
    "question": "I'm the Concur delegate for Dr. Katherine Keyes in the Department of Epidemiology at MSPH, and I'm encountering issues with one Individual Meal - Dinner expense for a conference report. Despite itemizing the meal to align with the $75 policy, I'm getting alerts in Concur. I also allocated alcoholic beverage charges to Dr. Keyes' discretionary. Can someone help me troubleshoot these alerts?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Meal threshold is is calculated excluding tips and taxes only. Drinks are included with meal",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1432": {
    "question": "I'm the travel arranger for UNI: sme2159, and I'm trying to reconcile Central Pay transactions over 365 days old. Since I can't change the dates on these transactions, how should I proceed?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "change is to travel expense",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "327": {
    "question": "I'm trying to access Concur to submit a travel/expense report using my account (tm3229@columbia.edu), but I can't log in. How can I resolve this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Reach out to one of the following to be opted in for concur access\n\nMs Janna Long 521300X Department of Computer Science ENG Computer Science\nSenior Business Manager janna.long@columbia.edu 212/853-8417\n Ms Jonnett Romano 521300X Department of Computer Science ENG Computer\nScience Manager-Student Operations jr4228@columbia.edu\n> Thanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "681": {
    "question": "I'm trying to approve report ODIC3k for ama2223, but I'm receiving an error message that says the approver was not selected. I don't have this problem with my other reports. I've already recalled and re-submitted the expense report, and I've approved it twice, but it still shows as pending in my queue. Can you advise me on this?",
    "out-of-scope": NaN,
    "human_answer": "please recall the report and have Dionida approve once only. do not add herself as adhoc approver. Anne Taylor is next in line to approve your report.\n ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "379": {
    "question": "I'm trying to book work travel through Concur, but I can't book a flight because there's an issue with my travel profile and I don\u2019t know what the issue is. Can anyone help me troubleshoot this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Please see this job aid with instructions on setting up your profile for Travel: https://www.finance.columbia.edu/content/setting-your-concur-profile-travel-and-expense-users\n\nIf that does not help resolve the issue please reach out to the Concur Online Booking Tool Support Center: 1-800-221-4730, Monday - Friday 8:00 a.m. - 8:00 p.m. ET ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "329": {
    "question": "I'm trying to complete an expense report for ey2126, but I didn't obtain a comparison flight at the time of booking. What should I do?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The comparison quotes are required at the time of booking. In rare circumstances, where this does not take place- the only comparison or documentation that can be provided is to look at the same date range for future dates since there is no way to look back in the airline reservation system. AP needs this documentation for audit requirements.                         ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "345": {
    "question": "I'm trying to create an expense report in Concur but need help getting started. Can you assist me?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Once the report is ready reach out to user for submission. Give us a call if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "505": {
    "question": "I'm trying to log into Concur but I'm getting the error code: 022751c314e4677e284b1ae7dc1fbb36. Can you check if there are still system-wide access issues or if this is just a problem for me?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Reach out to  the DA\n\nMs Reina Burdie 821200X Department of Epidemiology EPI Epidemiology Department Administrator ryb2001@cumc.columbia.edu 212/305-0695",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "208": {
    "question": "I'm trying to reconcile a travel advance for Tiffany Troy (CNR0051934), but their CNR is inactive. Can you please advise on how to proceed to close this advance and ensure it posts to the natural account 17110 PREPAID VOUCHERS FROM AP in our reports? Thank you.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hi Andrew,\nRe-activation only stays active for one day. Please email me on the day  Tiffany can perform the submission.\nThank you.\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "673": {
    "question": "I'm trying to reimburse Ninh Nguyen, a participant of the Secondary School Field Research Program, but her profile is not showing up on Concur. What should I do to proceed with her reimbursement? Thanks!",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Magdaly,\n\nNinh Nguyen has a vendor classification of  \"Supplier\" , vendor id 0000268310\nReimbursement for supplier can not be processed through concur. If you have a reimbursement to process you need to do it through ARC on a Check Request and you should also make sure to uncheck the withholding applicable box on the withholding information page\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "704": {
    "question": "I'm trying to reimburse a student, but I'm having trouble. The UNI CRW2160 has no vendor profile in ARC, and for UNI FH2486, FATHIMA HAKEEM has an inactive student profile. What should I do to resolve this?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "UNI CRW2160 no vendor profile in ARC.\nUNI FH2486 FATHIMA HAKEEM inactive Student profile in ARC.\nPW - PURPOSEFUL LEADERSHIP LLC email to brian.mckeon@purposefulleadershipllc.com - no record found in PW under vendor's name and email address.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "448": {
    "question": "I'm trying to reimburse someone using PG013229. It is on FDS but not in Concur. I tried department numbers 5218104 and 5218210. Can you please advise?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The correct department number is 5218210, however there is no fiscal year budget for 2025 on this project. Someone must enter a fiscal year budget in budget tool before it can be used.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "65": {
    "question": "I'm trying to select the Hotel/Lodging Expense Type on my report but couldn't. How can I change the Report Type to CU Travel Expenses?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Needed to change the Report Type to CU Travel Expenses.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "214": {
    "question": "I'm trying to submit a reimbursement for Han Ngoc Linh Huynh (vendor id 0000265477), but her name does not come up in Concur.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The vendor has a classification of \"Supplier\" and he is not going to be available through concur. Vendors only with \"Outside Party\" classification are the ones who can be available through concur\nIf you want to process reimbursement for this vendor you have to do it on a check request through ARC by unchecking the withholdings applicable box on the withholding information page\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "308": {
    "question": "I'm trying to submit a reimbursement request for a CC student (Yiyu (Anna) Chen), but I can't locate her in Concur with her PID C004675303. Can you assist?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Sylvia,\nThis student currently has inactive ARC profile. Students must be registered for current or future semester and should have a local US mailing address entered in SSOL in order to maintain active ARC status\nPlease advise student to do so. Once done the profile will be active within 48 hours and you should be able to find her in concur\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "563": {
    "question": "I'm trying to submit invoices for a student organization called CIPHER through Concur, but I can't log in today. I've attached a screenshot of the error code I'm getting. Can you help me fix this? Thanks!",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Anna has been opted back into Concur and should be able to login. If you experience any issues logging in please reopen the incident.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "635": {
    "question": "I'm trying to submit my report (Key: 293970, Name: TX/SPER/SER), but I'm getting an error stating that I need to create a Travel Allowance Itinerary first. What should I do?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Report has been approved by the dept and pending Central.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "446": {
    "question": "I'm trying to understand the Concur report process.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "If hotel name is not available please type other and provide the name on the comment/justification box. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "315": {
    "question": "I'm trying to understand why UNI RCBV2107 can only see her own Concur transactions. If someone else submitted an expense for her, shouldn't that be visible to her as well?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "\nUNI RCBV2107 can only see her Concur transactions that she created and submitted.\nIf someone submitted an expense for her, this transaction will only show up for the person who submitted the report in ARC.\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "674": {
    "question": "I'm unable to approve the expense report key 298503 for ehs2109 because I keep getting an error prompting me to select an approver. Can you help me resolve this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Per our discussion, you realized she needed to add Barbara as an approver. Please have her try that and if it doesn't work reply to this incident. I will leave it open.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "163": {
    "question": "I'm unable to forward my Concur report for approval to the specific approver ss819 for payee lbg9002. Can you assist me with this issue?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Per our discussion earlier, ss819 does not have approval rights to any departments beginning with 75197XX. Please find a list of the departments she does have approval rights to. \nChermaine was able to add ss819 to the approval workflow for lbg2124 is because she added her as an adhoc approver. \nIf ss819 needs approval rights to the departments beginning with 75197xx she will have to submit an fssa to request it. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "607": {
    "question": "I'm unable to log in to Concur to file my travel expenses because it shows something is wrong. Can someone assist me?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Lathika ,\n\nYour position as a Staff Associate ended on 6/1/24 and so does your access to concur\nIf you are no longer an employee who receives payroll check you will not get automatic access to concur. The department DAF can ask for temporary concur access though through the service catalog\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "26": {
    "question": "I'm unable to log in to Concur to submit my expense report. I received an email asking me to submit the report, but after I sign in, I get an error. How can I resolve this? Thank you, -Jan Janak",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Jan,\nYour employment has a termination date of 8/15/24. Concur is only available to active employees who receive a payroll check from Columbia. Your reimbursement should be processed by your departments Finance Office so please reach out to the Departments Administrator\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "594": {
    "question": "I'm unable to log in to my Concur account. The error message says: \"We encountered an error processing your request. If you continue to experience problems, please contact your Company Administrator or Help Desk.\" What should I do?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Temporary concur access can be requested through the service catalog",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "61": {
    "question": "I'm unable to log into Concur and I keep receiving an error message saying: We encountered an error processing your request. What should I do?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Marina,\nI see that your employment had an end date of 1/1/24.\nIf this has been renewed then you need to wait until all paperwork approved and an active PAC profile established. Otherwise you need to reach out to the Department Administrator in the Finance office\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "575": {
    "question": "I'm unable to log into Concur for UNI MG4163. I've ensured that all my Concur access is active, but can someone help me troubleshoot this? I've already cleared my browser cache, restarted my computer, and tried logging in with a different browser, but it still isn't working.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Per user, she was able to log into Concur successfully.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "385": {
    "question": "I'm unable to log into Concur. I am encountering an error after signing in, and we tried two different browsers for this. It's my first time signing in with TWO UNIs: rs4603 (current UNI) and rh3287.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hi Ryan,\nPlease give the login another try with login email (rs4603@columbia.edu).\nThank you.\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "277": {
    "question": "I'm unable to make travel arrangements on behalf of someone else. What should I do?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "In order to make travel arrangements for someone else, you must have the travel arranger role. You don't appear on our list of travel arrangers. To apply for the role, please click here: https://www.finance.columbia.edu/content/apply-access-finance-systems You will find the link to the application, as well has other helpful information. You will need to select the travel arranger role under section 2.1 roles. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "265": {
    "question": "I'm unable to reset my Concur password because the email with the link never arrives. It's not in my junk mail either. What should I do?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "I see that your access to Columbia's Concur is currently locked out due to your status in PAC (the HR system). You are not an active employee in PAC as of 6/30/24 and Concur access locks out 45 days after your PAC termination date.\nIf you are currently a Columbia employee please speak to your department about having your status updated in PAC. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1210": {
    "question": "I'm unsure what action needs to be taken on my Concur expense report, Report RZ2ST9. It says pending cost object approval, and my finance office at GS was not able to help me.",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Reopen or submit new ticket if questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "316": {
    "question": "I'm wondering if the foreign transaction fee I was charged for using my credit card internationally during my conference travel is reimbursable. I have an example statement showing the fee but it's already converted to USD. Can someone clarify this for me?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Ammie,\nYes that is reimbursable expense as long as it is associated with the business trip\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "591": {
    "question": "I'm working on an expense report (#51F1NS) where I need to request only $164.8 out of a total hotel fee of $1075.84, due to an award reimbursement limit of $600. If the amount doesn't match the itemization, should I adjust it or can I submit it with a comment explaining the discrepancy?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "On the itemization only put in one entry for $164.80 and in the \"Details\" section included a detailed explanation as to why you only put $164.80 on the \"Itemization\" page, as these two amounts must match.  ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "31": {
    "question": "I'm working on my expense report and have run into issues with an individual meal - lunch expense. I've segregated alcoholic beverages from the meal since sponsored funds cannot pay for alcoholic beverages. I've made sure that meal plus alcoholic beverages equals $35 and segregated the difference between the total and the $35 as a difference expense with type meal segregated, excluding taxes and tip. However, I continue to have issues with the alert for the alcoholic beverages itemization. I've itemized meals and alcoholic beverages for other expenses and haven\u2019t had any issues. Can you please help me troubleshoot? I'm acting as a delegate; my UNI for the payee is kmk2104 and the name of the expense report is 'WPA Conf 10062024.'",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Report was successfully submitted.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "809": {
    "question": "I've been designated as an expense delegate by Winnie O'Kelley. However, when I log in as her in Concur, I don't see any options to create a report. Could you let me know if we might have set this up incorrectly? Thank you!",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Issue with check marks not being checked.",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "549": {
    "question": "I've been told that the amount over the alcohol is going into Personal/Non-Reimbursable, and the payee is only being reimbursed for the meal. Do I need to segregate the alcohol as well?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Do not need to segregate the alcohol as well.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "418": {
    "question": "I've been trying to log in/create an account with Concur to submit a reimbursement request, but after the DUO authentication, I keep getting this error code: 116955f48309b9332f16417b89104272. I've tried for the past 24 hours and it's consistently the same. The system says that I should contact the Help Desk to resolve the issue. I'm attaching a screenshot of the error message page for reference.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "New employee document has to be processed and active PAC profile established",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "38": {
    "question": "I've changed the report type to CU Travel Expenses, but I'm having issues with travel expense types not appearing. Can you help?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Changed the report type to CU Travel Expenses.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "599": {
    "question": "I've encountered a known issue in Concur where, when entering multiple Non-Profiled Payee expenses for the same dates, the system adds them together. Can I include a comment to clarify that the rooms are not above the threshold?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Provided instructions to itemize the hotel bill.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "680": {
    "question": "I've noticed that project GT005470 is not appearing in Concur. Can anyone tell me what might be going on?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Concur only carries projects with valid fiscal year budget\nGT005470  doesn't have FY25 budget",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1282": {
    "question": "I've noticed that vendor 0000230998's outside party address is not showing in the Concur report for NPP. Could you help me resolve this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "User found address from the list.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "174": {
    "question": "I've received error messages for request 4Q7Y while trying to submit for reimbursement. I need help correcting them. Can someone assist me?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "You are not a delegate for cr2238, so you will not be able to submit expenses on her behalf. She currently has Stefanie Petersen listed as a delegate. \n\nTo add you as delegates, have the payee follow the instructions here: https://www.finance.columbia.edu/sites/default/files/content/Training%20Documents/Concur/Job%20Aids/Job_Aid_Concur_Profile_Delegates.pdf\n\nOnce added you can find instructions on how to process an expense report as a delegate here: https://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/news/how-do-i-create-expense-report-behalf-someone-else \nFollow steps 1-5 at the top and then continue with the expense report as you would any other. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "150": {
    "question": "I've requested temporary access on REQ0248795 for Concur. Can someone confirm that Irina will be able to login after it's closed?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "One day delay from when the access is granted to be able to login to Concur.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "219": {
    "question": "I've submitted three tickets regarding Anna Chen (PID C004675303) not appearing as a student in Concur. She has an active local mailing address in SSOL; please advise on the issue.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Student, Anna Chen (PID C0046753030 is available through concur",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "231": {
    "question": "If I purchased a flight using credit card points, can I still submit that expense for reimbursement through Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Gordon,\nYou can refer to the official travel policy but this is not allowed:\n\nhttps://universitypolicies.columbia.edu/content/travel-expense-policy\n\n-John",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "127": {
    "question": "If my department will be paying the amount over the threshold, can I leave the entire amount for tax in the hotel tax expense type? Is there no need to prorate that?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "If dept will be paying the amount over threshold can leave the entire amount for tax in the hotel tax expense type, no need to prorate that.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1106": {
    "question": "If my home department is GSAPP but I was awarded a grant from a different school (not our chart string), who should be approving these reimbursements in Concur? The grant does not belong to GSAPP, and we can't approve charges in ARC or Concur for a chart string that doesn't belong to our school. Can you please confirm? Thanks.",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Reopen or submit new ticket if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "221": {
    "question": "If someone booked a flight through Concur, can they submit it to reconcile the CU air/rail card early? The trip end date is a month away; do they have to wait until the end of the trip to submit?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Airfare, registration or membership fees can be reconciled before the trip end date",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "109": {
    "question": "If someone is set up as a \"supplier\" in the system, can I reimburse them for travel, or is it only allowed for individuals set up as \"outside party\"?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Kristi,\nA supplier would have to invoice Columbia for expenses. \n\nThe following vendor types can be reimbursed via Concur: - Employees - Outside Parties (vendors) - Student Employees - Student Non-Employees\n\n-John\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "118": {
    "question": "If the hotel is not on the list, should I just select Other and type in the hotel name in the Comments section?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "If hotel is not on the list, select Other and type in hotel name in the Comments section.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "443": {
    "question": "If we reimburse a faculty for relocation expenses, should I code everything in Concur as the movement of household goods, including cab rides, trains, supplies, and related expenses?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Relocation expense can be  submitted  as one expense line under expense type of Movement of Household Goods for Relocation",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1145": {
    "question": "Is Concur down right now? I\u2019ve tried logging on multiple times this morning but it isn't working. I keep getting a message saying, \"Sorry, something went wrong. We have encountered a problem with your travel profile. Please contact your travel agent for immediate booking and reach out to your Company Administrator or Help Desk for support.\"",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Concur working fine",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "275": {
    "question": "Is Paypal a valid payment method for expense reports?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The T&E policy does not state Paypal is not an allowable form of payment, but it does say the proof of payment portion of the receipt requires one of the following: \n\"Cash Tendered\"\n\"Paid\"\nA zero balance due\nDebit/Credit card payment (card type, last four digits of card and/or signature)\n\nIf the document does not have one of the above, then I would suggest you reach out to the payee and request the actual credit card receipt that the PayPal charge went to. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "502": {
    "question": "Is RADIO HOTEL still on the preferred list? I\u2019m trying to book it for 3 guests (2 rooms), but it keeps appearing greyed-out and disappears. I\u2019m currently on hold with them for nearly 10 minutes!",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "RADIO HOTEL is still on the referred hotels list\nhttps://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/content/hotels",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "347": {
    "question": "Is Sulekha ready to have her full access to Concur? She needs the same access that I have. She's not able to access the Process Reports yet. Can you please advise? Thanks, Jess.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hi Jess,\nSulekha's Concur account is active. \nLet me know if you have other questions. Thank you.\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "519": {
    "question": "Is chartsring required to book travel through Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "When travel is booked through concur it is charged to the central Air/Rail system. Chartstring is required upon reconciliation of the expense",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "527": {
    "question": "Is it possible for the department to provide a travel advance for a student employee? I heard that this is allowed but the student needs to be opted into Concur.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "This is allowed if the department wants to do it. The student employee UNI: dmr2204 would need to be opted in to Concur by the CUMC DAF Raquel Marin, rm2698.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "632": {
    "question": "Is it possible to delegate more than one Concur Financial Approver for a single level? For instance, can a payee select multiple financial approvers while submitting expense reports?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hi Malcolm,\nThere can only be one person assigned as financial approver per specific dollar threshold per department. multiple people can hold the approver role, but the DAF can only assign one person to the slot. Individuals with the role can be added as approver delegate to the assigned person if they are on leave. Otherwise, DAF would need to update the assigned list.\n\nThank you.\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "288": {
    "question": "Is it possible to freeze a current employee's Concur profile so their expenses cannot be submitted or approved?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Provided the user with the Job Aid which provided instruction for DAF to manage the employee access Defaults.  Link:  https://www.finance.columbia.edu/content/using-arc-custom-pages-manage-concur-settings-defaults-and-approvals\n\nTHank you.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "306": {
    "question": "Is it possible to request a rush on re-activating student profiles for 300 students who incurred expenses during orientation after being terminated in PAC earlier this month?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Student profile activation is an automatic process that occurs once the\nstudents are registered & have active profile in SSOl with a local US\n mailing address entered under their profile\n Thanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "197": {
    "question": "Is ll3479 Student Employee's access to login to Concur now available? I heard she was opted in today.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "LLOXCI's Concur access is now active and she should be able to login to Concur. Employees should also now be able to select her as their delegate.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "425": {
    "question": "Is the project UNI NML2179 still active in ARC?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Expense report was just approved today by Central AP.  Please check back Monday or Tuesday for payment details.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "181": {
    "question": "Is the reimbursement for a Barnard Professor processed through Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Reimbursement for a Barnard Professor should be processed through concur",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "561": {
    "question": "Is the service fee for fast clearance upon checking in reimbursable through Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "This is up to departments discretion",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "453": {
    "question": "Is there a Job Aid available showing how to process a Concur reimbursement for expenses that are subject to Government GSA rates?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Jeser,\nHere is the link to the Job Aid is it's on page 2.\n\nhttps://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/sites/default/files/content/Finance%20Training/Job%20Aids/Job_Aid_Concur_Itemizing_Lodging.pdf\n\nLet me know if you have more questions.\n\nJudy",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "476": {
    "question": "Is there a Job Aid available to show how to process a Concur reimbursement for expenses that are subject to Government GSA rates?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Government GSA rate reimbursement job aid\n\nhttps://www.finance.columbia.edu/sites/default/files/content/Training%20Documents/Concur/Job%",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "671": {
    "question": "Is there a way to adjust the USD equivalent on a Concur report for Jose's Summer School Program report? I need to reduce it to the remaining balance of $824.50 from what shows as $949.76 due to the exchange rate. Please advise.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "If you only want to reimburse $824.50, then, as per the below screenshot, only enter the amount in USD of $824.50. Be sure to enter detailed comments in the \"Comment/Justification\" section explaining why the total amount is $949.76 USD, but per the department/school, the payee is only getting reimbursed $824.50.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "369": {
    "question": "Is there a way to change the user account for a report mid-way through? I realized halfway through creating an extensive report that it's for the wrong user. I tried copying, but it's not clear how to make it transfer or if that's even possible. Thank you, Alexa.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Unfortunately no way to move reports between profiles.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "606": {
    "question": "Is this a request or a report? I noticed that there is a hotel name missing from the list in Concur.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "1. You will create a report in ARC.\n2.  Select 'Other' from the dropdown and enter hotel name in the comments section.\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "696": {
    "question": "It looks like these expenses were not charged to the project. Could you please advise?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Cost Object Approval = Financial Approval",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "226": {
    "question": "I\u2019m contacting you regarding an unreconciled Central Pay airfare expense from June 2023 related to my trip that was cancelled. It was supposed to result in a refund of $859.80, but I haven\u2019t received it yet in my profile. Could Concur Admin assist me in locating this refund? Reed will attach the email chain from World Travel about this issue.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hi Reed,\nPlease update the $8 report to mirrored the original airfare report. The report type should be updated to \"Travel Expense\" and Travel Date to current date.\n\nThank you.\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "461": {
    "question": "I\u2019m receiving error code 4552c6c16cdd824e2d0b6b318642de4b when trying to access Concur. Can you assist?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hi Delaney,\nI've updated your account. please give email address djr2202@columbia.edu another try.\nThank you.\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "83": {
    "question": "KJA2103 has two requests for $1,872.07 and $832.07. She has one report for $832.07. She needs to consolidate this with the other report and create a new expense report for $1,872.07, consolidating it with that report. Can you assist with this process?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "1.  She needs to consolidate the $832.07 request to the report.\n2.  She needs to create an expense report for $1,872.07 and consolidate with the report for the same amount.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "81": {
    "question": "Luca Kolibius has not received his reimbursement, and it's still pending. Could you please advise on the next steps?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Report has been approved and sent for payment. Reopen or submit a new ticket if any additional questions, Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "411": {
    "question": "My Concur account is locked. How can I unlock it?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Reach out to the DA to be opted in for access.\nStudent access gets inactivated every time the semester ends and need to be opted in again",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "362": {
    "question": "My Concur profile address has not been updated. Can you advise on how to check my SSOL account to ensure that all updates have gone through?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Concur profile address has not been updated.  Advised to check SSOL account and make sure that all updates has gone through.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "91": {
    "question": "My UNI MD3605 report is missing receipts. How can I resolve this?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "He will need to submit/attach receipts for the line expenses or submit Missing Receipt Affidavit.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "512": {
    "question": "My UNI is ae2214. Can I get an update on my expense report status?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "It looks like the hotel has been itemized correctly based on the hotel folio.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "321": {
    "question": "My delegate is preparing a report for someone, but there's a meal expense under $50 without receipts. What should we do about the missing receipts?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "If less than $50, you may submit without receipts for meal expenses.\nIf more than $50, only the account user can submit Misssing Receipt Declaration form in Concur.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "67": {
    "question": "My department approver is requesting that I upload the event flyer for the Concur reimbursement that was returned.",
    "out-of-scope": "irrelevant question",
    "human_answer": "Advised to reach out the dept approver and explain that Agenda is uploaded which has all the event information and previously accepted by Central.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1044": {
    "question": "My expense reimbursements have been submitted but are stuck because they were routed to Mindaugas, who has retired. These two reimbursements have been pending approval for over a month. Can you please check and approve them?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Submit new ticket if any additional questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "553": {
    "question": "My expense report is stuck because it's routed to Ervis Dinkel, our former Director of Finance, after being approved by Jacqueline Jenkins, our current Director. Since Ervis is no longer with Columbia, how can I resolve this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The department has to assign another approver in place of Ervis and you can recall your report and resubmit\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "567": {
    "question": "My expense report was returned with Report Key: 293318. Can you tell me why it was returned?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Assisted with retuned expense reports",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "310": {
    "question": "My name is Chao Lu (cl4653@columbia.edu), and I'm a visiting student. I'd like to know why there is no profile in Concur for me and what my status is for receiving reimbursements for expenses related to the lab move of Ke Cheng.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Create a vendor profile and process reimbursement through concur",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "11": {
    "question": "My name is Stacey Bellamy and my Uni ID is sk5163. I got an error message when trying to log into Concur saying, \"Sorry, something went wrong. Failed to validate the signature of the SAMLResponse.\" Can you help me resolve this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "If you are still experiencing issues logging into Concur please reopen the incident.",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "603": {
    "question": "My profile is not active in Concur. What can I do about it?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Profile is now approved. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "638": {
    "question": "My report ID 23B60659542F43AEA4DC was returned by AP because of wrong travel booking. Can someone provide a valid explanation for the three flights? I have resubmitted the report with an explanation.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Report id 23B60659542F43AEA4DC returned by AP - Leonor Romero May 31, 2024 12:27 PM\nPlease provide a valid explanation for the three flights.  \nUser provided explanation and resubmitted report.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "470": {
    "question": "My student appointment is ending soon. How long will my profile remain active for processing reimbursements?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Student profile remains active up to 45 days from the last date of appointment",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "550": {
    "question": "My vendor ID is CNR0133026 and my name is Chloe Barlow with UNI CSB2206. Although my student profile is active in ARC, I can\u2019t load it into Concur. Can someone figure out why Chloe's profile isn't showing up in Concur and, if possible, fix it? I recently updated my profile, and maybe that's why it isn\u2019t visible right now. Thank you.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "CNR0133026 appearing in Concur on 8/14. If you experience any issues please reopen the incident.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "82": {
    "question": "One of our PIs is trying to submit an expense report on Concur but is having difficulties with the project she intends to charge. The project is not found, and I've attached a screenshot for reference. Could you confirm if there's a technical issue or an error on the project?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "There is no FY25 budget for UR013126. Concur only carries projects with valid fiscal year budget. Please work with the DA or Budget officer to have budget entered for FY25",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "526": {
    "question": "One of our students is receiving a message regarding her expense report submission, but I can't see her report since she hasn't submitted it to me yet. The message states she needs to attach a request for the report. What does this mean, and how should I advise her? She just wants to reimburse herself for airfare. Is there a specific submission area she needs to use? Her email is ccv2122 if you need more information.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Marvin,\nA Pre-Trip Request is required for all Students in order to be reimbursed for travel expenses. Some schools and departments may also require approved pre-trip requests for all travel. If you are required to obtain pre-trip approval, you will not be able to submit an Expense Report without the pre-trip approval attached.\nThis student should submit a pre trip request even though the trip has already taken place and once approved it should be attached to the expense . Below is direction hoe to do it\n\nhttps://www.finance.columbia.edu/content/submitting-pre-trip-request-concur\n\nOnce the request is approved it should be attached to the expense report\n\nhttps://www.finance.columbia.edu/sites/default/files/content/Training%20Documents/Concur/Job%20Aids/Job_Aid_Concur_Reconciling_Requests.pdf\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "77": {
    "question": "Our department is hosting a seminar speaker, and the speaker asked if there\u2019s a way to be reimbursed in advance for meal and taxi expenses. This is a first for me, and I can't think of any possible way this would be feasible. I want to ensure I\u2019m not overlooking anything before I tell the person no. Could you please advise? Thank you.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Expenses can not be reimbursed before trip end date",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1172": {
    "question": "Our department would like to have an in-house training for Concur. Can you assist with this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Advised to reach out to Kate Sheeran.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "386": {
    "question": "Please advise on how to get Estelle Gouriou to appear in Concur as a non-profiled payee, as she does not appear under outside party, but the ARC account was created with the profile number 0000270871.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Process through ARC due to wire payment method.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "405": {
    "question": "Please note that Dr. Delivette Castor's Concur profile shows 2 available expenses that need to be attached to an expense report for a canceled trip. How do I remove the available expenses? Should I just delete them? The upcoming trips still list them and state that they need an expense report withdrawn. Please advise, thank you.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "All posted transactions need to be reconciled whether a credit or debit",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "434": {
    "question": "RITM0253871 was approved for the Travel Arranger role. What\u2019s the next step?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "please log into Concur and complete your profile information. see email reply for more details.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "106": {
    "question": "Regarding the incident INC2720650, is there guidance on reconciling a cancelled trip? I heard that the original expense needs to be reconciled without a credit transaction appearing. Is that correct?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "There will not be a credit transaction that will appear under Available Expenses to reconcile. The original expense must be reconciled like any other expense with a comment entered that the trip was cancelled.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "699": {
    "question": "Regarding vendor 0000265334, this is the student profile for the outside party profile in Concur.",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "0000265334 - outside party profile, for the CNR this is the student profile",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "105": {
    "question": "Since Christopher will enter the itinerary, do I still need meal receipts for the per diem?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Christopher will enter the itinerary, no meal receipts needed for a per diem. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "128": {
    "question": "Since I am looking to reimburse a faculty member in a different department, should they set me up as their delegate or enter the report themselves?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Faculty could either set you up as their delegate or enter the report themselves.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "44": {
    "question": "Since my meeting ended early, how can I change my ticket?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Directed to  WTI # \n  1-855-961-0313                         ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "242": {
    "question": "Since the report is linked to a Cash Advance, I understand that no Initial Reviewer approval is required. However, can you clarify why I'm unable to insert approvers into the workflow and only other approvers can insert additional approvers?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Since the report is linked to a Cash Advance no Initial Reviewer approval is required. The payee is not able to insert approvers into the workflow, only other approvers can insert additional approvers.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "186": {
    "question": "Since there won't be an overnight stay, can I include these business expenses all in one expense report?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Since there is no overnight stay these would be business expenses rather than travel expenses and can all be included in one expense report.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "312": {
    "question": "Some expense reports for David Freedberg seem to be stuck in \"Cost object Approval.\" Can anyone tell me why they aren\u2019t moving forward?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Cost Object Approval = Financial Approval\nReach out to the Financial approver and get the expense approved",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "396": {
    "question": "Some of our financial approvers are having trouble when trying to add a Senior Business Officer as an ad hoc approver to an expense report in Concur. Once the SBO approves it, Central Accounts Payable says they can't approve it because the SBO has already approved it. Are we doing something wrong or is this a system glitch? Please refer to Report Key 300577.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Everything looks ok with how report 300577 will route now. However I know that sometimes ad hoc approvers get inserted after the \"Approval for Processing\" (AP) approval step instead of before. This job aid explains how to insert an Ad Hoc approver (which plus sign to click when inserting):\nhttps://www.finance.columbia.edu/sites/default/files/content/Training%20Documents/Concur/Job%20Aids/Job_Aid_Concur_Ad_Hoc_Approvers.pdf ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "394": {
    "question": "Students are buying groceries for event food. I want to know if this is reimbursable.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "If the students decide to buy groceries to prepare for events , it can be reimbursed",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "283": {
    "question": "The Concur report ewjjui needs to be resubmitted.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Please ask user to submit report for review and approval",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "616": {
    "question": "The department needs to reach out to Raquel Marin because Joanna has been opted into Concur but only has access to Expense and not Travel. What should we do?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Dept needs to reach out to Raquel Marin, Joanna was opted into Concur but was only given access to Expense, not Travel.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "437": {
    "question": "The expense type for lodging is not available on the report page. What can I do?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Expense type lodging is only available under CU Travel Expense",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "421": {
    "question": "The last 2 Concur reports I submitted have been routing to Kazue Tomiyama instead of Rebecca Hirade. We did not change anything on our end. What caused this change and how can it be fixed?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hi Harold,\nI see that some of your old reports had Rebecca approving for both as Initial Reviewer and Financial Approver. Systematically and separation of duties, that should not be permitted. i would say that's a glitch in the system. \nAs for your current report workflow, it is correct, it should go to Kazue first, then to Rebecca. One person should not be the report's full workflow.\nThank you.\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "187": {
    "question": "The report id VQHCAI paid Lauren $607.40 instead of the student who should have received it. Can you advise how she can return these funds back to CU? Does she need to create a new report in Concur to correct this and reimburse the student? This is urgent since the student has been waiting for their reimbursement. Thank you!",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hi Lauren, \nPlease see attached job aid (page 4) to create report on behalf of a Guest or Student. And yes, you will need to create another expense report, follow the instructions on page 4 to correctly direct the fund to the right person.\n\nAs for returning fund back to the University. Below is the link and the options to return funds.\n https://www.finance.columbia.edu/content/return-funds-university\nThank you.\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "697": {
    "question": "The training is partially completed, but my role is not granted. What can I do?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Training partially completed,  Requested role is not granted",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "10": {
    "question": "The vendor profile of full-time registered PhD student EMILY CARR is inactive. Could you activate it so that I can process a reimbursement?",
    "out-of-scope": "unsure",
    "human_answer": "Michael,\nStudent ARC profile is activated once the student enter local US mailing address in SSOL. Please advise student to do so\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "284": {
    "question": "The vendor with ID 0000266895 is set up for wire payments. Please process through ARC as a voucher, attaching the Wire Request form as one of the supporting documents.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Vendor is set up for wire payments. Please process through ARC as a voucher attaching the Wire Request form as one of the supporting documents.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1165": {
    "question": "There's a travel advance request for UNI LT2731 that was cancelled in June, but I\u2019m still receiving notifications to reconcile it. What should I do about this?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "needed evident for further investigation.\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "600": {
    "question": "There\u2019s a Concur Expense Report submitted by Tanya Pope for approval that went to David Greenberg, but he's not set up as an Approver. How can we fix this?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Tanya's supervisor in PAC is Peter, not David. If that is incorrect it would need to be updated in PAC. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "430": {
    "question": "This is my first travel to a conference, and I stayed after the conference dates. However, I'm having trouble obtaining a quote for comparison of the airfare cost. Can you advise me on how to resolve this issue? Thank you!",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hi Luminita,\nThe process to obtain quote comparison after the fact is as follows:\n1) Get the time gap of the original ticket. (date of purchase vs date of travel)\n2) Obtain present day quote with the same time gap in the future.\n\nThank you\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127  ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "236": {
    "question": "Tikku, mrignaina mt3763@columbia.edu is a delegate for JS4085 who has permission to submit reports in Concur, but she's unable to submit his reports now. The report for March 28-April 2 Travel Expense is significant, totaling $7,759.05. Could you assist with why this is happening?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hi Rita,\n\nThe submit option comes into play only with Concur account in inactive state. For active accounts, only account owners are permitted to submit reimbursements. Delegates can never permitted to submit reimbursements on behalf of someone else.\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "365": {
    "question": "To receive a cash advance, do I need to be opted in to Concur by the school DAF? Can you explain what this means regarding my access to Concur and reimbursements?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "In order to receive an advance the student employee will need to be opted in to Concur by the school DAF. Discussed what this means with regard to the student's Concur access and reimbursements.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "250": {
    "question": "To reconcile Central Air/Rail Transactions, how do I add to a new report, enter header information, enter information on transactions, and submit?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Add to a new report, enter header information, enter information on transactions and submit.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "36": {
    "question": "To whom it may concern: When I'm requesting per diems for meals, do I need to upload itemized receipts? Please advise. Thank you, Angela.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Dear Customer, \n\nWe have not heard back from you regarding your Service Now Incident. Because several days have passed, the Service Center has marked the incident as resolved. If you do not feel this issue was resolved, please re-open this incident and provide the required information.\n \nThank You\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "523": {
    "question": "Under my profile, I have an expense for a Poster Print costing $57.31. Since my Financial Approver is on leave and their delegated access has expired, can they extend it or can the department set up a new default Financial Approver?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The Financial Approver Idrija is out on a leave of absence. She set Daniel Alicea up as her approver delegate but this expired on 6/30/24.\nTwo options:\n1. If possible Idrija can extend the end date of the delegate access she gave to Daniel.\n2. Or department DAF can set up someone else as the default Financial Approver for this department.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "280": {
    "question": "Vivianna will ask Monica to check off the checkmarks to finish setting up my delegate access.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Vivianna will ask Monica to check off the checkmarks to finish setting up the delegate access.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "98": {
    "question": "We had multiple people at dinner, and I paid for my portion, which is 1/5th of the total bill. How should Bennett enter $75 for my meal and then correctly calculate 1/5 of the tax and tip? This amount will be less than what I paid.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Bennett will put $75 in individual meal and then calculate 1/5 of the tax and tip. This will be less that what the employee paid.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "390": {
    "question": "We have an event in Paris and I need to pay for lunch for participants.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "This is to be determined by the Grant's  policy &  guidance . Group lunch expense is reimbursable",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "18": {
    "question": "What are the allowed travel dates for international travel?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "They may travel one day before the business start date.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "324": {
    "question": "What are the available expenses I can claim in Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "All expenses if posted as available expense in concur, those need to be reconciled",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "498": {
    "question": "What are the receipts I need to provide for my expense report?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Per the travel and business expense policy found here: https://universitypolicies.columbia.edu/content/travel-expense-policy\nReceipts must be provided for all air, rail, lodging, and rental car expenses. For all other expense types, receipts must be provided if the expense is equal to or in excess of $50. Otherwise, Payee Justification and Financial Approval is required and a Missing Receipt Affidavit must be completed.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "583": {
    "question": "What are the rules for CONCUR claims regarding conference travel (airfare) to foreign countries? I have specific questions because we often use Non Sponsored Sources of Funding for these claims. For instance, if the longest flight segment exceeds 5 hours, can my PI automatically claim a Business Class ticket, or do we need to segregate the difference with Economy tickets? Also, when comparing ticket prices, is it only Economy allowed, or is Premium Economy acceptable? Thank you!",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Sean,\nIf the flight is more than 5 hours a business class ticket can be purchased but still the difference between the economy fare and the business class fare needs to be segregated to a non sponsored project unless the sponsored projects allows the purchase of a business class fare , you need to provide supporting document that shows the terms & regulations for the project which specifically allows that\nIf you purchased premium economy the difference between the economy and premium economy fare should also be segregated\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "359": {
    "question": "What do I do about cancelled hotel reservations on dh2994's corporate card?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Charges and credits all added to the same expense report netting to $0 with comment explaining the situation. Since this is lodging the expense report will not be able to be submitted until after the trip end date.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "299": {
    "question": "What do I need to do about my Concur receipts?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "When creating the report you can upload all receipts/documents in Concur.  Click Receipts icon to upload.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "565": {
    "question": "What do I need to do to set up a delegate in Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Setup as delegate for FH2170.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "806": {
    "question": "What do I need to do to use WTI to pay for a consultant's airfare?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "POLICY TEXT                                            \nMany members of the University's faculty, staff and students must travel out of town on University business. This includes travel to conferences, travel to meet with firms or individuals doing business with the University and travel to perform research. In such cases, the University will reimburse the traveler for necessary and reasonable expenses incurred while traveling.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "45": {
    "question": "What do I need to know about reconciling report for sm4680?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Please update expense from groceries to meal as advised. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "373": {
    "question": "What documents are needed when I use the mileage rate in my expense report?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Travel by Private Vehicle                                            \nWhen traveling for business purposes, a personal vehicle may be used in order to save time, transport equipment, reduce costs when several people are traveling together, or travel to locations within reasonable driving distance. If a personal vehicle is used primarily for the convenience of the traveler and the approved travel is to a location more than 500 miles beyond the point of origin, reimbursement will not exceed the lesser of the following: 1) the cost of per- mile reimbursement plus tolls; or, 2) the round-trip airfare between the nearest commercial airport serving the origin and destination cities, plus transfer costs to and from the airport.\n                                                                       \nFor the business-related use of a personal vehicle, the traveler will be reimbursed at a rate based on the Federal IRS approved highway mileage guides. Mileage reimbursement covers fuel, maintenance/repairs, insurance, transportation and operating costs, so these will not be reimbursed separately. The traveler will not be reimbursed for the cost of vehicle purchase or lease.\n                                                                       \nIn addition to the mileage allowance, tolls and necessary parking charges may be reimbursed.                                             \n\nThe University does not assume liability for damage to personal automobiles used on University business and does not assume liability for deductibles or any other uninsured loss to the vehicle. Expenses for vehicle repairs are not reimbursable. Under no circumstances will the University reimburse parking fines and moving violations on personal vehicle\n\n \n\nPersonal Vehicle Mileage Rate:\n\n$.655/miles for travel on or after January 1, 2023\n$.670/miles for travel on or after January 1, 2024\n                                                  ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1042": {
    "question": "What does vendor number 0000271000 refer to in Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Coming up now under outside party.",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "501": {
    "question": "What happens if my expense is over 120 days old?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Expense greater than 120 days  requires payee justification and Financial Approver acknowledgement",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "741": {
    "question": "What information can you provide about the Expense report with Report Key: 320635?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Report Key :320635\nPending submission",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "807": {
    "question": "What information do I need about Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Here is the link to the Government per diem rate\nhttps://aoprals.state.gov/content.asp?content_id=184&menu_id=78\nHere is also the link to the job aid on how to process a report with per diems\nhttps://www.finance.columbia.edu/content/using-diems-travel-expense-report-concur\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "532": {
    "question": "What information do I need regarding Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Wanted to ensure direct deposit was set up on her profile. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "522": {
    "question": "What is the Concur approval workflow for expenses that exceed the threshold?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "When something is over the threshold, the general workflow is  as followed: \napproved by the designated department  initiator \napproved by the designated SBO \nroutes to Central AP for review and approval \n\nYour department may have a different workflow. I would suggest reaching out to your supervisor and inquiring about that. \nHere is the workflow job aid: https://www.finance.columbia.edu/sites/default/files/content/Training%20Documents/Concur/Job%20Aids/Job_Aid_Concur_Approval_Workflow.pdf",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "191": {
    "question": "What is the Concur per diem?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Please find attached per diem jobaid. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "168": {
    "question": "What is the Concur process?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Dear Customer,\n\nWe have not heard back from you and because several days have passed , the Service Center has marked the incident as resolved. If you do not feel this issue was resolved, please re-open this incident and provide all of the required information.\n\nThank You",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "463": {
    "question": "What is the DAF for Dept 6413102?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "DAF for Department 6413102\nMICHELLE BAGGAN-BACCHUS (mb9) Phone: 212/854-5632 | TSHAYE MEAZA (tm24) Phone: 212/854-9581",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "25": {
    "question": "What is the current status of my Concur access?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "You are an initial reviewer and also have the travel arranger role. See attached.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "336": {
    "question": "What is the current status of my Concur reimbursement request?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "When submitting  reimbursement report please add as much information as possible for the car rental expense",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "155": {
    "question": "What is the government per diem rate that I should follow?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Melanie,\nHere is the link for the government per diem rate\nhttps://aoprals.state.gov/content.asp?content_id=184&menu_id=78\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "2": {
    "question": "What is the lodging allowance for domestic travel? Can you provide details?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Lodging is $350 /night excluding tips and taxes for domestic travel",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "241": {
    "question": "What is the lodging threshold for booking through Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hotel threshold is exceeding $350 night rate for a conference. Will provide backup showing no lower rates when submitting reimbursement. Give us a call if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "457": {
    "question": "What is the payment information for Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Go to the expense report and in Report Details tab select Payment Details.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "497": {
    "question": "What is the payment status for my expense report with Report Number: WAP4UM, Report Key: 293517, Voucher: 06437109, Check: 1002273307?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Provided information on finding the check number. Elizabeth will confirm student's address and submit stop payment.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1071": {
    "question": "What is the payment status for my expense report? The amount is $499.63 for Sarah Frances SCALE.",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "07/26/2024 36879 296428-2001307341 SARAH FRANCES $499.63\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "646": {
    "question": "What is the policy regarding a missing receipt for amounts under $50?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Receipt is needed when over $50. \nReceipts must be provided for all air, lodging, and rental car expenses. For all other expense types, receipts must be provided if the expense is equal to or in excess of $50. Otherwise, Payee Justification and Financial Approval is required and a Missing Receipt Affidavit must be completed.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "272": {
    "question": "What is the procedure for hotel expenses for sas68 that includes a meal?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Since sas68 paid out-of-pocket for the hotel and the dept is not reimbursing the alcohol put the alcohol, alcohol tax, and portion of the tip that will not be reimbursed into the Personal/Non-Reimburseable expense type on the itemization. sas68 does not need to write a check.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "834": {
    "question": "What is the process for handling Concur expenses for uni rb3784?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "uni associated with concur is rrb2135",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "507": {
    "question": "What is the process for handling Concur expenses that exceed the threshold for 120 days and 365 days?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "\nFor expenses over 120 days, you must enter a justification in the comments/justification box in Concur.\nFor expenses over 365 days, someone in your department must submit the reimbursement via ARC with a justification",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "297": {
    "question": "What is the process for pre-trip requests in Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "A pre-trip request is required for all Student Employees and Student Non-Employees with access to Concur in order to be reimbursed for travel related expenses.\n\nSome Schools / administrative units may also require approved pre-trip requests for all travel, not just student travel.\n\nIf you are required to obtain a pre-trip approval, you will not be able to submit an Expense Report without the pre-trip approval attached.\n\nhttps://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/content/travel-how-tos\n\nhttps://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/news/what-are-pre-trip-requests-and-travel-cash-advances",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1242": {
    "question": "What is the process for reconciling corporate card expenses?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Please reopen or give us a call if any additional questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1429": {
    "question": "What is the process for submitting an expense report in Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Expense type will be individual meal, separate the amount the faculty is requesting from the entire total. Give us a call or reopen if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "193": {
    "question": "What is the status of Erin Annunziato's expense report for the SER Conference totaling $1,943.86?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Report was just approved by your SBO David Declercq yesterday 10/2, please allow 1-2 business days for AP to review and approve the report.  Thank you.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "104": {
    "question": "What is the status of Expense Reports for uni lm2892?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "LRM - CTN $271.20\nPending Executive Expense Approver\nCarrie Marlin\n\nDublin & Paris 2024 $5,309.20  & \nCalifornia 2024 $1,092.82\nPending approval from Financial Approver\n\nLRM 9-12-24 $292.63\nPending Approval  from \nJustin Pearlman",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "698": {
    "question": "What is the status of INC06274076?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Duplicate incident",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "585": {
    "question": "What is the status of INC2670521?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Resolution on  INC2670521  by fg2491\n\n  On the itemization only put in one entry for $164.80 and in the \"Details\" section included a detailed explanation as to why you only put $164.80 on the \"Itemization\" page, as these two amounts must match.  ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1218": {
    "question": "What is the status of Report Key: 301877?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Report Key :301877\nPending Financial Approval",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "225": {
    "question": "What is the status of Vendor ID 0000271251?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Vendor ID  0000271251 is available through concur",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "644": {
    "question": "What is the status of Vendor# 0000269780 in Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Please make sure to scroll past the most recent searches and you will see the vendor's address. Give us a call if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1233": {
    "question": "What is the status of expense report CNR0034640?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "CNR0034640\nInactive ARC profile. Invitation will be sent to register through Payment Works",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "175": {
    "question": "What is the status of my cash advance request for jcs2276, which was department approved on 10/5 and is currently awaiting review by AP?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Department approved 10/5. Awaiting review by AP.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "723": {
    "question": "What is the status of my expense for TCC2140, Report Key: 317439?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Report Key : 317439  pending payment",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "529": {
    "question": "What is the status of my expense report CNR0107186?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "One pending report under ya2116, $1,436.78. Pending dept approval.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "579": {
    "question": "What is the status of my expense report pending James Singletary's approval?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Pending James Singletary's approval.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "611": {
    "question": "What is the status of the expense I submitted in June?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "There is no expense submitted in June, 24",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "251": {
    "question": "What is the time frame for submitting lodging expenses?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hotel/Lodging expense can not be reimbursed before the trip end date",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "114": {
    "question": "What is the travel expense reimbursement policy?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Here is what the policy says about the use of private vehicle\n\nTravel by Private Vehicle\nWhen traveling for business purposes, a personal vehicle may be used in order to save time, transport equipment, reduce costs when several people are traveling together, or travel to locations within reasonable driving distance. If a personal vehicle is used primarily for the convenience of the traveler and the approved travel is to a location more than 500 miles beyond the point of origin, reimbursement will not exceed the lesser of the following: 1) the cost of per- mile reimbursement plus tolls; or, 2) the round-trip airfare between the nearest commercial airport serving the origin and destination cities, plus transfer costs to and from the airport.\n\nFor the business-related use of a personal vehicle, the traveler will be reimbursed at a rate based on the Federal IRS approved highway mileage guides. Mileage reimbursement covers fuel, maintenance/repairs, insurance, transportation and operating costs, so these will not be reimbursed separately. The traveler will not be reimbursed for the cost of vehicle purchase or lease.\n\nIn addition to the mileage allowance, tolls and necessary parking charges may be reimbursed.\n\n\n\nThe University does not assume liability for damage to personal automobiles used on University business and does not assume liability for deductibles or any other uninsured loss to the vehicle. Expenses for vehicle repairs are not reimbursable. Under no circumstances will the University reimburse parking fines and moving violations on personal vehicle\n\n\n\nPersonal Vehicle Mileage Rate:\n\n$.655/miles for travel on or after January 1, 2023",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "194": {
    "question": "What should I do about Supplier ID 0000270665 being a non-profile payee?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Recapping our discussion.\nIf the vendor is an outside party with a domestic address, they can be processed via the non-profile payee report in Concur.\nThe mileage can be added via the personal mileage expense category.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1480": {
    "question": "What should I do about my Concur expense for a trip that was extended due to collaboration training approved by the department?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Please submit expenses in Concur with valid business purpose for the extended stay,",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "201": {
    "question": "What should I do about the non-profile expense report?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Students don't have default access to enter in expenses. I doubled check Nadav's status and he does not have access. The report will have to be entered in on as a non-profile payee on the student's behalf. Here are the instructions: https://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/news/how-do-i-create-expense-report-behalf-someone-else\nFollow the instructions under the section: To Submit an Expense Report for Non-Profiled Payee.\nIf you have any questions, you can respond to this incident.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "295": {
    "question": "What should I do if my Concur account with ID CNR0056506 is inactive?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Once faculty is onboarded it takes an additional 24 hours for Concur to be active.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "278": {
    "question": "What should I do if my Concur profile is inactive?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Current status shows as terminated. Will contact coordinator for more information. Give us a call if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "314": {
    "question": "What steps should I follow to create an Expense Report in Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Here is the link to the Job Aid -\n\nhttps://www.finance.columbia.edu/sites/default/files/content/Training%20Documents/Concur/Job%20Aids/Job_Aid_Concur_Creating_Expense_Reports.pdf\n\n",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "361": {
    "question": "What steps should a new hire take to set up their Concur profile?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "You can log into Concur and create your expense report.  You can assign a delegate (another person) to create your report in Concur, if needed.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "292": {
    "question": "When I act as a delegate, what type of report should I use for different expenses? Should it be Travel Expenses or Business Expenses?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Report type will be either Travel Expenses or Business Expenses depending on what the expenses are for.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "86": {
    "question": "When I click on Login to Concur to create an account, I get an error with the error code: 834aed069b6fa673226d35374dae2c1c. What should I do?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Very happy to hear that. You should be able to submit your own expenses. \n\nUseful information (may or may not be applicable) \n -Business expense report job aid (no overnight stay involved): https://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/content/video-creating-and-submitting-business-expense-report\n -Travel Expense report job aid (must have at least one overnight stay): https://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/content/video-creating-and-submitting-travel-expense-report\n-Concur Tips:  provides job aids for specific scenarios to help you navigate through an expense report: https://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/content/concur-tips ( you may \n  have to expand the page to see the full list of tips).  \n-Expense how-tos: https://travel-expense.finance.columbia.edu/content/expense-how-tos\n-If you need to transact on behalf of another employee or faculty member, they will have to assign you as a delegate.  Here is a job aid: \n   https://www.finance.columbia.edu/sites/default/files/content/Training%20Documents/Concur/Job%20Aids/Job_Aid_Concur_Profile_Delegates.pdf\n-If you need to transact on behalf of a student that does not have Concur access (most don't) or a guest you will need to submit a non-profile payee report\n  You can find instructions in the Concur Tips or Expense how-tos link (section 4). \n\nIf you need any of the following roles: Concur Initial approver, Concur Financial Approver, or Travel Arranger, an FSSA must be submitted to request the role: https://www.finance.columbia.edu/content/apply-access-finance-systems\n\nI will resolve this incident, but should you have any additional questions, please feel free to reopen within 3 business days. If it is beyond that, please open a new ticket or give us a call at 212-854-2122.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "112": {
    "question": "When I itemize the hotel bill, how should I put the personal nights under personal/non-reimbursable?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "When itemizing the hotel bill put the personal nights under Personal/Non-Reimburseable.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "406": {
    "question": "When I try to book a hotel or flights through Concur, an error message pops up after attempting to load. Can you help me resolve this? I have attached details for reference.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hi Maya,\nOur travels program director indicated that the Amtrak AAA discount number must be taken out. Columbia already has a discount agreement with Amtrak baked into Concur. They system does not permit for multiple discount programs.\n\nThank you\n\nKin Chiang\nColumbia University in the City of New York\nConcur Expense Administrator\n615 W. 131st, 3rd floor\nNew York, NY 10027\nPhone: 212-851-7127",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "624": {
    "question": "When I try to log into Concur I get a notification saying: Sorry, something went wrong. We encountered an error processing your request. If I continue to experience problems, should I contact my Company Administrator or Help Desk? The support id is 3433cfa356ffd458d3d8ff96dfe5c1e2.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "As a student, you do not have default access to login to Concur. There are two options to reimburse you:\n\n1. Your department can enter the expense report on your behalf using a \"non-profiled payee\" report type.\n\n2. Your department can request to have you \"opted in\" to Concur so that you can login to Concur and enter the expense report yourself.\n\nPlease follow up with your department to see which option they want to use. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "554": {
    "question": "When I'm submitting an expense report for reimbursement for a CU employee, do I need to provide an email that includes the PI's approval for the expenses and reimbursement?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Andrea,\nThat is not a concur requirement, however, if the PI is paying for the reimbursement from his project that is between him and his staff , not a concur requirement",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "466": {
    "question": "When booking international travel, do I really need to use a US carrier to comply with the Fly America Act, or are there exceptions? Can I get more details on this from Columbia's Fly America policy?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "When booking international travel, the use of a US air carrier is preferred but not required, except when traveling on Sponsored Funds or a government grant as travelers must also be sure to comply with the Federal government's Fly America Act. For additional information please reference Columbia's Fly America policy.                                           \n\nGovernment sponsored grants require the traveler to fly on a US owned airline (Fly America Act), or a US airline designated codeshare flight number (which is a flight that is shared between a US and a foreign airline). The US Flag Carrier Policy is available on the Research Administration website at http://research.columbia.edu/usflag-carrier-policy. Exceptions to this requirement are listed in the policy. If travel did not occur on a US carrier airline, the traveler must complete the Fly America Exception form and attach the form to their Expense Report. The Financial Approver in Concur will be required to acknowledge the Fly America Exception Reason.\n\nFor more information on Fly America Exception documentation please click here, https://www.gsa.gov/policy-regulations/policy/travel-management-policy-overview/fly-america-act\n\nhttps://universitypolicies.columbia.edu/content/travel-expense-policy",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "205": {
    "question": "When itemizing for a business class upgrade, can I put the entire amount under Airfare - Segregated and $0 under Airfare?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "On the itemizations tab put the entire amount under Airfare - Segregated and $0 under Airfare.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "664": {
    "question": "When my colleague Kyle Stearns (uni: ks3352) tries to log into Concur, he receives a message saying he is inactive. What can we do to fix this issue?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Hello,\nYour requested information was provided to you in this incident on 7/30  and we have not heard back from you for several days now and the Service Center has marked the incident as resolved. If you do not feel this issue was resolved, please re-open this incident for further assistance.\n\nThank you.\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "378": {
    "question": "When should I process reimbursement through Concur versus ARC?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "All reimbursements should be processed in Concur with the following exceptions:\n1. Vendor is classified as a supplier\n2. Regardless of classification, the vendor's default payment method is wire.\nEither of these scenarios have to be processed as a check or wire request in ARC.\n\nIf you are transacting on behalf of someone else, the following vendors would have to be submitted as a non profile payee:\n-Most students (if the student is opted in to Concur, then they would need to be processed as a delegate)\n-Outside parties who default payment method is not wire.\n\nThe following vendors reimbursements must be processed as a delegate in Concur:\n1. Faculty\n2. Students with Concur access (otherwise they should be entering their own reports)\n3. Employees with their own CNR profiles.\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "496": {
    "question": "Where can I find my Concur report? I submitted it on 8/14/24 for reimbursement of a furniture order for $50.85 and there is no record of it.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Yes, I can see how that can be confusing. Please reopen or submit new ticket if you have any additional questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "569": {
    "question": "Where should I indicate the payment location for my expense report?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Expense reimbursement will be dispersed in the same way employee receives payroll payment",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "200": {
    "question": "Who can I contact in the Leave Management office to approve business class airfare for a doctor due to a medical condition?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Gordon,\nYou can contact leave management here:\n\nContact:\n\nPhone: 212-851-0698\nSecure Fax: 212-851-7069\nEmail: leavemanagement@columbia.edu\n\n-John\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "152": {
    "question": "Who is able to insert SBO for the approval of an expense report?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Financial approvers can insert SBO for approval",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "192": {
    "question": "Why am I receiving reconciliation alerts mh2968?",
    "out-of-scope": "asking for individual status/ capability limitation",
    "human_answer": "Faculty has pending transactions that need to be reconciled. These can be done at the end of the trip. Give us a call if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1245": {
    "question": "Why am I unable to submit my report in Concur? It shows Concur tm2118.",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Please reopen ticket or give us a call. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "158": {
    "question": "Why can't I edit the reconciliation date in Concur for my travel expenses?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Please let approver know the transaction date cannot be edited this is prepopulated when using the travel card. Reopen or give us a call if any questions. Thank you",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "204": {
    "question": "Why can't I get into Concur to get paid for travel from 8/28-8/30 for the SPS IKNS residency? I am on Columbia Payroll.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "There is nothing that can be done to accelerate this. When your PAC profile is reinstated you will be able to access concur.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "177": {
    "question": "Why can't I log in to Concur using my UNI? After I log in, I see a message saying: Sorry, something went wrong. We encountered an error processing your request. If this issue continues, I should contact my Company Administrator or Help Desk, right? The support ID provided is 6b8f098f3edd769f90d562182e0db2c3.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Pei-Ting ,\nStudents do not get automatic access to concur.\nYour expense reimbursement should be processed by your schools administrative office , or if the department decides to give you access to concur they can do so by submitting a service ticket. Please reach out to your schools Finance Administrator or Senior Business Officer\nThanks",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "23": {
    "question": "Why can't NYP employees access Columbia's Concur for supervisor approvals?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "NYP employees do not have access to Columbia's Concur so couldn't be the supervisor approver in Concur. \nBill will discuss with his department which Initial Reviewer he should select when submitting his expense report.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "459": {
    "question": "Why do my foreign meals show up as domestic in the project?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": " Concur handles natural account assignments based on expense types, it is an automatic process that cannot be edited. If you are processing an expense report, you would need to process a Journal Voucher if they want to reallocate the natural account.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "199": {
    "question": "Why doesn't the project number PG013229 show up in CONCUR, even though it exists in FDS?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "I conferred with my team. The issue is that No budget exist using department 5218210 activity 01 for this project. You need to create a budget in ARC or the project won't show up in Concur. It's like it has to be \"pre budget checked\" so try entering the FY budget for your department and project combo then try in Concur tomorrow.\nI'll leave this open.\n",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "650": {
    "question": "Why have I not received the reimbursement that was approved?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "User has confirmed receipt of the reimbursement in July",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "1274": {
    "question": "Why is CNR0146719 not appearing in Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in-scope",
    "human_answer": "Address updated on 8/15 \nShould wait 48 hrs for data to integrate",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "304": {
    "question": "Why is my status as a second year student (wl2935@columbia.edu) not appearing in Concur for reimbursements?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Student added a local US address to their SSOL profile. Vendor profile CNR0139600 is now active and should appear in Concur starting tomorrow, 9/20. If you experience any problems tomorrow please reopen the incident.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "328": {
    "question": "Why is the Outside party ID not populating for Vendor ID 0000270468 in Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "As concur does not support wire payments, your department will have to process this reimbursement as a wire request via an ARC voucher. ",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "353": {
    "question": "Why is the chartstring not populating in Concur for 7581302-spons-GG013437-03-70003-rtm2 cr2101?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "She's using the wrong department number. It should be department 7581306. I was able to pull it up in Concur.\nLet me know if you have any other questions.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "190": {
    "question": "Why isn't my hotel listed in Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Select/type in \"Other\" and enter the hotel name in the Comments section.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "652": {
    "question": "Why isn't my project showing up in Concur for GG020205?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Concur only carries projects with valid budget.\nGG020205 doesn't have a budget for FY25",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "301": {
    "question": "Why isn't my status as a student (mh4198@columbia.edu) appearing in Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Per Zubaida student located in Concur.",
    "invalid_HA": 1
  },
  "237": {
    "question": "Why isn't the hotel listed in Concur?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The option \"Other\" can be selected when hotel is not listed in concur",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "198": {
    "question": "Why was Anna the only Initial Reviewer available for selection when I submitted my report? I submitted the report without selecting her, but it routed to her correctly.",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Dr. Soni submitted the report without selecting an Initial Reviewer and it has routed to Anna correctly.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "334": {
    "question": "Why was my report ma785 requiring Supervisor and Initial Reviewer Approval? Can you clarify this issue for me?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "Had ma785 recall the report and resubmit. Zobeida approved as Initial Reviewer and it is now routing correctly to Francina.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  },
  "246": {
    "question": "Why was user mp3921 allowed to use the Columbia Air/Rail option to book a flight?",
    "out-of-scope": "in scope",
    "human_answer": "The Columbia University's Air/Rail Central Pay is a method of booking air or rail travel that allows travelers to avoid out-of-pocket expenses. The University pays for travel booked using this method, which is also known as a Business Travel Account (BTA) and then the user/department reconciles the expense in the same manner you reconcile the corporate card expenses. It is an available payment method to all users who have the ability to book travel through Concur.\nLet me know if you have any questions.",
    "invalid_HA": 0
  }
}